The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Order, requiring one to be indoors at a certain time.
Curfew Money given on a regular basis for personal use.
Allowance To restrict one's activities, especially of a child.
Ground To unload someone as from a car, ship, etc.
Drop one off.
Let's try that faster.
Money given on a regular basis for personal use.
Allowance To restrict one's activities, especially of a child.
Ground Order, requiring one to be indoors at a certain time.
Curfew To unload someone as from a car, ship, etc.
Drop one off.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Can you drop me off at school on your way to work?
Drop me off at home after the movie, okay?
If you don't drop me off at the party now, I will scream.
Curfew My mother will be mad if I come home past my curfew.
Curfew There is a city-wide curfew for anyone under 21 years of age.
Curfew When I was younger, my curfew was at 11 o'clock at night.
Allowance Every week, I had to do my chores in order to receive my allowance.
Allowance My husband gave me a spending allowance of $5,000 a month.
Allowance The marketing budget gave a $1 million allowance for this quarter.
Allowance I broke my mother's favorite vase, so she grounded me.
Allowance Because there was so much snow, all the airplanes were grounded.
Allowance I received an F in math, so my father grounded me.