EnglishPod.com OK Sally, we have an artist here to help us.
We'll ask you questions about the bank robber you saw and Paul will draw a picture.
Are you ready?
Yes, well, he had brown hair, long hair, and he had some facial hair.
It was brown too.
Good!
OK, the facial hair, was it a beard or a moustache?
Both.
His moustache was very short and thin, just on the top of his lip.
Uh-huh.
Hmm, like this?
Yes, that's the moustache, but the beard isn't right.
I mean, it didn't cover his whole face.
I think it was just on his chin.
A goatee?
Was it like Paul's?
Uh, yes, that's it.
He had a goatee.
OK, now, what about sideburns?
Did he have sideburns?
Um, yes, they were long and thick, like yours.
All right.
There, was this the man you saw?
Yes, that's him.
Hmm, it looks a lot like you.
Hmm, why, yes he does.
Paul, where were you on Friday afternoon?
What?
That's ridiculous.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do anything.
I was over there doing the thing with the best man.
Thanks for watching!