The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Get someone's way.
To exhaust, discourage, or depress someone.
Get someone down.
To avoid or neglect.
To shirk.
The feelings one has after a specific event.
Impression.
Upset.
Frustrated.
Let's try that faster.
To avoid or neglect.
To shirk.
To locate or describe exactly or precisely.
To pinpoint.
A personal defect or failing.
Weakness.
Upset.
Frustrated.
To exhaust, discourage, or depress someone.
Get someone down.
Proceed according to one's plans or wishes.
Go someone's way.
The feelings one has after a specific event.
Impression.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Weakness.
I have a weakness for chocolate.
Let's discuss the program's strengths and weaknesses.
Weakness.
Impatience is a weakness that I am working to overcome.
To pinpoint.
Can the tech team pinpoint exactly where the problem lies?
Let's try to pinpoint the areas where we need to improve.
To pinpoint.
I need to prioritize my to-do list.
Would you help me pinpoint the items that are the most important?
Go someone's way.
Jessica can be immature at times.
She gets upset if things don't go her way.
Go someone's way.
Your alarm didn't go off and your taxi got in that accident.
Things just aren't going your way this morning.
Go someone's way.
I'm so frustrated.
Nothing is going my way.
Get someone down.
Oh, don't let Cheryl get you down.
She can be critical at times, but she means well.
Get someone down.
Man, this weather is so gloomy.
It's really getting me down.
Get someone down.
All the pressure at work got her down and she became depressed.
To shirk.
Derek does as little work as possible and often shirks his responsibilities.
You can't shirk your duties.
You're the master of ceremonies.
We need you.
To shirk.
He left his wife and family shirking his parental responsibilities.