EnglishPod.com Okay, Rebecca.
Well, I think you've given me a clear impression of your positive qualities, but let's talk a little bit about your weaknesses.
Okay.
Well, it's always more difficult to describe them, isn't it?
Definitely.
But if you had to pinpoint one weakness, what would it be?
Well, as I mentioned before, I do tend to get frustrated if I don't see progress in my work or career.
I suppose I'm quite a restless character.
My father always taught me to be a high achiever, so...
So would you say if things don't go your way at work, it could easily get you down?
Well, in a way, yes.
But I must say that even if I'm not completely happy in my work, I always give 110%.
I would never shirk my responsibilities.
I suppose sometimes I expect too much too soon.
Well, you know journalism is a highly competitive world, so you do need to keep pushing yourself, it's true.
Okay, well let's move on to talk about the job position here, shall we?
Yes, please.