EnglishPod.com Whoa!
What's going on?
Watch out!
Hey!
Watch where you're going!
Oh no!
I'm so sorry!
Are you alright?
I don't know.
I feel terrible.
I really didn't mean to knock you over.
My tire just exploded and I lost control of my bike.
Really, it was an accident.
Please accept my apologies.
Just let me try to stand up.
Why do birds suddenly appear?
Oh, wait a second.
You seem really familiar.
I think I know you from somewhere.
Yeah, that's right.
I think we've met somewhere before.
We met at Aaron's place last weekend.
What a coincidence.
But anyway, I'm glad to see you're not badly hurt and I should probably get going.
I've got a nine o'clock meeting.
But here's my number.
Call me and we'll exchange insurance information.
Ouch!
My ankle!
I think it's broken.
You can't just leave me like this.
Are you calling an ambulance?
Nope.
I'm canceling my appointment so that I can stay here with you.
Do you remember when we met?
Last day, I knew you were my friend.
I want to tell you how much I love you.