The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Examine the shop windows.
Window shop In addition to something else.
On top of When I look at what the whole situation amounts to.
When it comes down to it.
Looking cheap.
Having bad taste.
Tacky.
I agree.
I understand.
Tell me about it.
Let's try that faster.
Looking cheap.
Having bad taste.
Tacky.
Examine the shop windows.
Window shop When I look at what the whole situation amounts to.
When it comes down to it.
I agree.
I understand.
Tell me about it.
In addition to something else.
On top of Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Window shop My sister and I like to go window shopping every once in a while.
Window shop When my friend goes shopping, she never actually buys anything.
She only window shops.
Window shop He finds it so hard to window shop.
Because every time he sees something he likes, he wants to buy it.
On top of On top of everything else that is going on, you expect me to take care of you as well?
On top of Window shop There is no way I am going on a date with her.
She is obnoxious, prejudiced, talks too much.
And on top of that, she wears way too much makeup.
On top of Window shop On top of taking care of their kids, they expect me to clean the house for them as well.
When it comes down to it.
I guess I was really mean to her.
Everything she has done for us has benefited us.
Even though it didn't seem like it at first.
When it comes down to it.
You know, when it comes down to it, you're not such a wimp after all.
Tacky Her outfits are always really tacky.
Tacky That was a tacky thing to say.
Tacky I love tacky Christmas decorations.
They make me smile.
Tell me about it.
She's so annoying.
She never stops talking.
Tell me about it.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I had to sit through two lectures today with that professor.
He's so boring.
Tell me about it.
I couldn't believe it either when I heard that her parents had bought her a new car for Christmas.