EnglishPod.com Bill!
Bill!
You gotta help me!
What's wrong?
Slow down or you're gonna give yourself a heart attack.
Tomorrow's Christmas and I haven't bought my mom anything.
I'm such a bad son.
Take it easy.
Let's go to the mall, window shop a little, and see if there's anything she might like.
That's just it.
I don't know what to get her.
Last year I got her a ring that was two sizes too big and a pair of shoes five sizes too small.
I suck at getting presents for people.
That's where you're making a big mistake.
You can't just guess people's likes or sizes, especially with clothes or jewelry.
On top of that, I think that you should get your mom something that shows how much you love her.
At the same time, you should show her that you took the time and effort to look for something that she would really like.
Yeah, you're right.
When it comes down to it, I can be pretty tacky.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I know.
Your mom is trying to learn Spanish, right?
Why don't you get her a gift certificate for this great website I saw called SpanishPod?
Now that's a great idea.