EnglishPod.com Have you read all these crazy things that are going on around the world?
What do you mean?
I was reading about how some people get tricked or drugged in their hotel rooms and have their organs removed.
Then they're sold on the black market.
Don't tell me you actually believe all that.
Don't be so gullible.
They are just urban legends.
They are just stories people make up to scare you.
Well, I was also reading about how some popular songs have subliminal or even satanic messages if you play them backwards.
Can you believe that?
You really think an artist or songwriter is going to go through the trouble of putting subliminal or satanic messages in a song?
Don't be so naive.
Well, maybe you are right, but how about the story about how KFC has rows of headless chickens which are super grown in order to get bigger chickens faster?
Sounds a bit too far-fetched to be true, don't you think?