The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Any system in which goods are sold and bought illegally.
Black market Easily believing something that is not true.
Gullible Stories that are exaggerated or not true.
Urban legend Invent Makeup Something that persuades in a subconscious way.
Subliminal Relating to Satan or the Devil.
Satanic Having or showing a lack of experience, judgment.
Naive Improbable, not naturally pertinent.
Far-fetched Let's try that faster.
Invent Makeup Any system in which goods are sold and bought illegally.
Black market Something that persuades in a subconscious way.
Subliminal Improbable, not naturally pertinent.
Far-fetched Having or showing a lack of experience, judgment.
Naive Stories that are exaggerated or not true.
Urban legend Easily believing something that is not true.
Gullible Relating to Satan or the Devil.
Satanic Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Black market Guns and drugs are sold on the black market.
Black market Currencies and stolen goods are also sold in the black market.
Black market Many stolen cars are sold in the black market.
Gullible Gullible You are one of the most gullible people I have ever met.
Gullible Steve is really gullible.
He will believe anything.
Gullible Gullible You have to stop being so gullible, otherwise people will take advantage of you.
Makeup Gossip magazines will make up stories about celebrities.
Makeup Robert made up a story about why he was late for work.
Makeup Susan is always making up stories.
You can't really believe anything she says.
Naive Naive You have to stop being so naive.
Naive Linda is very naive and trusts people too much.
Naive Far-fetched I used to be very naive, but the older I got, the more I learned.
Far-fetched That is a very far-fetched story.
Far-fetched Far-fetched It seems a little too far-fetched to believe that Carl was a woman before.
Far-fetched People used to think that going to the moon was very far-fetched.