The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Stylish or fashionable Sharp Wide, a lot Broad Most wanted or preferred Preferably To go together with Accompany Let's try that faster.
Stylish or fashionable Sharp To go together with Accompany Most wanted or preferred Preferably Wide, a lot Broad Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sharp Dan looks really sharp today.
I think he has an important meeting.
Sharp I always try to look sharp on Mondays.
Sharp Broad The first class of day is very important, so everyone tries to look sharp.
Broad The store has a broad selection of mobile phones.
Broad The new Victoria's Secret catalog has a broad selection of clothes and lingerie.
Broad That store used to have a broad selection of digital cameras, but now they only sell camcorders.
Preferably You should buy some vitamins, preferably from a well-known supplement maker.
Preferably I would like a Coca Cola, preferably Diet Coke.
Preferably Accompany I would like to live in Chicago, but preferably in the downtown area.
Accompany The vice president accompanied the president to Peru.
Accompany She went to Europe accompanied by her colleague.
Accompany The tour guide will accompany us to our hotel.