The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Ranking with the best in the whole world.
World class.
The song that represents a country and that is played in ceremonies.
National anthem.
A person who controls and judges a baseball game.
Umpire.
Get ready to hit the ball.
Up at bat.
Get the energy to throw the ball.
Wind up.
A ball thrown on a curve, not straight, that is hard to hit.
Curve ball.
The player who throws the ball to the batter.
Pitcher.
The player behind home plate who catches the ball without being hit.
Catcher.
A hit that travels low along the baseline.
Line drive.
Do something quickly and in a disorganized way.
Scramble.
A player who plays in the area that is relatively far from the pitch.
Outfielder.
Successfully gets to the base.
Safe.
A hit that strikes the ball out of the field.
Home run.
A set of baseball containing a turn at bat and a turn infield for each side.
Inning.
The next in line to do something.
Up to bat.
An approximate number.
Ballpark figure.
To do something very well or very successfully.
Hit it out of the park.
Immediately without delay.
Off the bat.
An unusual, crazy, or eccentric person.
Screwball.
Let's try that faster.
Immediately without delay.
Off the bat.
The song that represents a country and that is played in ceremonies.
National anthem.
The player behind home plate who catches the ball without being hit.
Catcher.
Get ready to hit the ball.
Up at bat.
A ball thrown on a curve, not straight, that is hard to hit.
Curve ball.
An approximate number.
Ballpark figure.
To do something very well or very successfully.
Hit it out of the park.
A hit that strikes the ball out of the field.
Home run.
Ranking with the best in the whole world.
World class.
Do something quickly and in a disorganized way.
Scramble.
A player who plays in the area that is relatively far from the pitch.
Outfielder.
The next in line to do something.
Up to bat.
A set of baseball containing a turn at bat and a turn infield for each side.
Inning.
A hit that travels low along the baseline.
Line drive.
An unusual, crazy, or eccentric person.
Screwball.
Successfully gets to the base.
Safe.
The player who throws the ball to the batter.
Pitcher.
A person who controls and judges a baseball game.
Umpire.
Get the energy to throw the ball.
Wind up.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
World class.
That was a world class performance that the actors displayed tonight.
We are building a world class management team.
World class.
Our company aspires to be world class leaders in IT development.
Curveball.
My boss threw me a curveball today, so I have to stay and work late.
It was a huge curveball when she asked me how many kids I wanted to have.
How am I supposed to know?
Curveball.
I've been thrown so many curveballs this month with this new project.
I can't take it anymore.
Great job on that sales presentation.
You really hit a home run.
Our sales team hit a home run this month by doubling our revenue.
Janice hit a home run today with her great dissertation on consumer psychology.
Our team is ahead by five points.
We are going to win.
That runner is ahead of everyone else by more than two minutes.
Our sales team is ahead by more than $1,000 on this month's target sales.
Scramble.
I woke up late today and had to scramble to work as fast as I could.
When Mike's cat got lost, we all scrambled around the neighborhood looking for him.
Scramble.
I saw a mouse in the kitchen, but he scrambled under the stove before I could catch it.