The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Rural areas Country To feed in a meadow or pasture Graze Get the milk from a cow Milk Know little about Don't know the first thing about A building for the shelter and feeding of domestic animals, especially horses and cattle.
Stable Be able to manage or manage successfully Hack it Let's try that faster.
To feed in a meadow or pasture Graze Know little about Don't know the first thing about Get the milk from a cow Milk Rural areas Country A building for the shelter and feeding of domestic animals, especially horses and cattle.
Stable Be able to manage or manage successfully Hack it Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Country It took only 10 minutes of driving before we were out of the city and in the country.
Country My mom grew up on a farm out in the country, and met my dad one day when his truck broke down on the country road beside me.
Country I love being out in the country because it is so peaceful.
Don't know the first thing about I would be so scared to have a baby because I don't know the first thing about being a mom.
Don't know the first thing about Teaching I don't know the first thing about teaching, so there is no way I am going to look for a job teaching English.
Don't know the first thing about My sister is your babysitter, but she doesn't know the first thing about taking care of kids.
Graz The cows grazed in the field.
Graz I knew that something was wrong when I looked out over the countryside and saw only one horse grazing in the field.
Graz Every morning he takes the sheep out to graze.
Stable The little girl led the donkey back into the stable.
Stable He went into the stable to take a look at the new kittens.
Stable Your father put the new horse in the big stall in the stable.
Hack it I think the new employee is going to quit because he just can't hack it.
Hack it I can't hack it being a nanny because the kids won't listen to me.
Hack it She's not too sure if she could hack it in the city with all the people and all the noise.