The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
In humans, the young in the early stages of development within the womb.
Embryo, the outermost layer defining the physical limits of an object.
Wall, let's try that faster.
The discharge of semen by the male reproductive organs.
Ejaculation, the discharge of a mature ovum from the ovary.
Ovulation, the uterus of the human female.
Womb, the outermost layer defining the physical limits of an object.
Wall, in humans, the young in the early stages of development within the womb.
Embryo, now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Womb My mother said she would often sing to me while I was in her womb.
Womb He stroked his wife's protruding belly with love and affection, knowing she carried his child in her womb.
Womb After several attempts, finally her womb was opened and she conceived.
Ovulation One way to ensure getting pregnant is to keep track of your menstrual cycle and to use an ovulation calendar to pinpoint the day of your ovulation.
Ovulation Ovulation happens approximately 14 days before the start of your next menstrual period.
Ovulation A woman's chances of getting pregnant will be higher as she approaches ovulation.
Ejaculation Semen, which is a mixture of sperm and other secretions of the testes, is ejected from the penis during ejaculation.
Ejaculation If a man experiences problems with ejaculation, sperm may have to be collected outside of sexual intercourse in order for a couple to become pregnant.
Ejaculation As a man grows older, ejaculation may become more difficult as his erection ability decreases.
Embryo A zygote becomes an embryo upon its first cell division.
Embryo An embryo becomes a fetus at the end of the second month of gestation, when the body structures of the young organism are in the recognizable form of its kind.
Embryo Most abortions occur when the young organism is in the form of an embryo.
Wall The doctor says there is a hole in the lining of my stomach wall.
Wall An artery gets clogged when plaque accumulates on the walls of the arteries.
Wall Sometimes the placenta of the embryo attaches itself too deeply into the wall of the uterus, which can result in premature delivery.