EnglishPod.com Charlie, do you have a second?
Yeah, what's up?
Well, I went and paid the bills today and you still haven't given me your half.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.
I agreed we would go halves on all the bills, but frankly I think it's unfair.
Unfair?
Why?
Well, you have long hair and use the hair dryer every morning.
I don't.
You leave your computer on all night downloading torrents.
You see what I'm getting at here?
You leave the air conditioner on day and night.
You also take 30 minute showers, which means you're using way more gas and water than me.
Well, while we're on the subject, stop bringing your friends over for drinks every weekend.
You always leave a mess and keep me up all night.
Maybe you should just move out and find another place.
Maybe you should move out.