EnglishPod.com I have been looking at this online catalog for over an hour and I still haven't finished getting all the kitchen appliances that we need.
What are you getting?
Well, the first thing on my list is a new blender.
I decided to also get a juicer and a new coffee maker.
Don't forget to also get a new mixer.
I lent the old one to my brother and he broke it.
Yeah, I know.
I also decided to throw away the old toaster and get a new one.
I am also getting a rice cooker and a steamer to make some nice steamed fish or veggies.
I'm actually thinking of completely refurnishing the kitchen and getting a new stove, oven, dishwasher, and trash compactor.
That's a good idea.
The kitchen will look amazing.