The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A machine used for toasting bread.
Toaster.
A machine used for washing dishes.
Dishwasher.
Let's try that faster.
A machine used for mixing things.
Mixer.
A machine used for washing dishes.
Dishwasher.
A machine used for cutting food and ice and mixing.
Blender.
A machine used for making juice.
Juicer.
A machine used for toasting bread.
Toaster.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Walmart.
Walmart is a great place to buy home appliances.
I called the repairman because our new appliance wasn't working.
A stove is one of the first appliances you should buy.
How else will you eat?
Blender.
I am going to put yogurt, bananas, and strawberries into the blender to make a delicious smoothie.
Henry hates eating vegetables, so his mother puts the vegetables in a blender and makes juice.
Blender.
I forgot to put the lid on the blender, and now our kitchen is covered in food.
When my car broke down, I had to put the lid on the blender.
When it broke down, Bobby lent me his bike.
Be careful with that.
It's not mine.
Someone lent it to me.
If you lend Anna money, you shouldn't expect her to pay you back.
Many children don't like to eat their veggies.
I would rather eat chocolate than veggies any day.
You should eat every serving of fruits and veggies every day.
Blender.
They recently refurnished the hotel, so it's very nice.
Our house is a big mess right now because we're refurnishing, but when it's finished, it will look fabulous.
I think it may be time to refurnish our living room.
All the furniture and decorations are outdated.