EnglishPod.com I'm forming a music band.
Do you already know how to play an instrument?
Uh, yeah.
I told you a thousand times that I'm learning to play the drums.
Now that I know how to play well, I would like to form a rock band.
Aside from yourself, who are the other members of the band?
We have a guy who plays guitar and another who plays bass.
Although, we still haven't found anyone to be our singer.
You told me that you had some musical talent, right?
Yes.
I'm a singer.
Perfect!
So you can audition this weekend here at my house.
Great!
Wait here?
You don't have enough room for the amplifiers, microphones, or even your drums.
By the way, where do you keep them or practice?
Dude, what are you talking about?
It's right here.
All we need is my Nintendo Wii and we're set.