The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A device that is used to make music.
Instrument Many times A thousand times Create, organize Form To take part in a trial performance.
Audition We are ready.
We are set.
Let's try that faster.
Many times A thousand times Create, organize Form A device that is used to make music.
Instrument To take part in a trial performance.
Audition We are ready.
We are set.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Instrument I know a friend who knows how to play five musical instruments.
Instrument What kind of instrument is that?
Instrument Have you ever studied a musical instrument?
A thousand times You didn't remember to pick up the cake?
I've told you a thousand times that it's ready.
A thousand times I've told him a thousand times to pick up his room and he never listens.
I've had enough of this.
A thousand times I've told you a thousand times to lock the door and what do you do?
You leave it open again.
Form We are forming a band.
Want to join?
Form They just formed a book club.
It's been really successful so far.
Form I like to form my own opinions about movies so I never read reviews before I see them.
Audition Kim was nervous because she felt she hadn't practiced her lines enough before the audition.
Audition I'd like to audition for the University Orchestra but I'm too shy.
Audition His audition went really well.
The judges accepted him on the spot.
We are set.
I just have to add the finishing touches on the cake and then we're set.
Are we set to leave?
No, I left my purse in the house.
We are set.
The plans for the party are all set, now we just need to send out the invitations.