The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Act of sending a text message via a mobile phone.
Text Abbreviation for short message service.
SMS Amount of money that you have available to make calls.
Credit To completely finish or extinguish something.
Use it up.
Without limits or restrictions.
Unlimited Not surprisingly No wonder Let's try that faster.
To completely finish or extinguish something.
Use it up.
Not surprisingly No wonder Without limits or restrictions.
Unlimited Abbreviation for short message service.
SMS Amount of money that you have available to make calls.
Credit Act of sending a text message via a mobile phone.
Text Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Text Text Can you text me your brother's email address?
Text I can't text on this phone.
My fingers are too big.
Text Put your phone away.
You are always texting.
Credit I need to buy more credit for my phone.
Credit Can I use your phone?
I don't have any credit in mine.
Credit Credit Credit Make sure you always have credit on your phone.
Otherwise you can't make or receive any calls.
Use it up Did you use up all the glue?
Use it up We had to use up all the white paint so we need to buy more.
Use it up I used up all the detergent when I was doing laundry.
Unlimited The hotel offers unlimited wireless internet.
Unlimited The buffet includes unlimited food and drinks.
Unlimited This ticket is valid for unlimited entry to the cinema for one year.
No wonder No wonder the lamp doesn't work.
It's not plugged in.
No wonder No wonder you ran out of money.
You spent it all on clothes.
No wonder It's no wonder the dog barks every night.
There is a cat that comes out and teases him.