The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
For keeping a record of the content of the part filled out and torn away.
stub Of or relating to a form of government or a country in which power is divided between one central and several regional governments.
federal Amount of money that you receive.
income A sum of money or other resources whose principal or interest is set aside for a specific objective.
fund Needing no explanation, obvious.
self-explanatory Let's try that faster.
Of or relating to a form of government or a country in which power is divided between one central and several regional governments.
federal Needing no explanation, obvious.
self-explanatory For keeping a record of the content of the part filled out and torn away.
stub Amount of money that you receive.
income A sum of money or other resources whose principal or interest is set aside for a specific objective.
fund Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
stub Please hold on to your ticket stub so we can verify you later on if needed.
stub stub Be sure to make a note on each check stub so that we know what was purchased.
stub I'm sorry sir but I can't let you back in the theatre unless you show me the stub of your movie ticket.
federal I wish the federal government would do more to prevent inflation.
federal Federal taxes might seem to be high but without them our hospitals would be in a state of disrepair.
federal These federal reform policies are a breath of fresh air.
income I want to ask the boss for a pay increase as my income doesn't cover living expenses.
income I believe the income generated by renting out your houses will allow you to retire.
income He doesn't deserve the income that he receives.
fund Please tell me which fund you want to have this deposited in.
fund I think mutual funds are a waste of money.
I'd rather invest in an index fund.
fund fund My pension fund orbit disappeared after the financial crisis hit.
self-explanatory I've gone over this with you a thousand times.
I thought it was self-explanatory.
self-explanatory self-explanatory Okay, I understand.
This is pretty self-explanatory.
self-explanatory There are no instructions to assemble this bookcase but it should be pretty self-explanatory.