The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Long trip by car Road trip A part of an engine that moves up and down inside.
Piston A device in the engine that produces electric sparks.
Spark plug Stop working Break down The device which helps cars getting running.
Engine Pedal that you press before you change gear.
Clutch A device that slows down or stops something.
Brake Ordinary Regular Without problems or difficulties.
Smoothly Let's try that faster.
Long trip by car Road trip A part of an engine that moves up and down inside.
Piston Ordinary Regular Without problems or difficulties.
Smoothly A device in the engine that produces electric sparks.
Spark plug Pedal that you press before you change gear.
Clutch Stop working Break down A device that slows down or stops something.
Brake The device which helps cars getting running.
Engine Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I think that there might be a mechanical problem with my motorcycle.
Good news.
There were no mechanical issues with your car.
Even though the car is a little binged up from the crash, it's still in good mechanical condition.
My condition isn't very good because I've had a fever for two days.
Even though our house is old, it's still in very good condition.
Car My dad's car is still in perfect condition because he takes really good care of it.
The doctor recommends that you eat three or four servings of vegetables every day.
My teacher recommended that I practice my English more often.
Our friends recommended that we try the new French restaurant.
If you keep dragging your feet when you walk, you're going to wear down your shoes.
If you don't take care of your car, the engine will wear down.
Taking care of kids wears me out.
I'm exhausted.
The doctor told me he would need to do some more tests before you could determine what's wrong.
I can't determine whether I should go to Australia or not.
Once you have all the information, you can determine what you'll need to finish the project.
Thanks for watching!