The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning then say the vocabulary word.
Something that is spread all over an area.
Scattered.
In or to various places.
Here and there.
A particular space or area.
Spot.
Prepare.
Set up.
Assume a reclining position.
Lay down.
A light plastic disc for playing.
Frisbee.
A hand tool for lifting loose material.
Shovel.
A small model of a castle that is made of sand.
Sand castle.
Go in a direction that is away from a group.
Stray.
Having little depth.
Shallow.
Life saving appliance in the ocean.
Floaty.
A raised area of sand with a top.
Sand bar.
Let's try that faster.
Life saving appliance in the ocean.
Floaty.
A particular space or area.
Spot.
Assume a reclining position.
Lay down.
Something that is spread all over an area.
Scattered.
In or to various places.
Here and there.
Prepare.
Set up.
A light plastic disc for playing.
Frisbee.
Having little depth.
Shallow.
Go in a direction that is away from a group.
Stray.
A small model of a castle that is made of sand.
Sand castle.
A raised area of sand with a top.
Sand bar.
A hand tool for lifting loose material.
Shovel.
Lay down.
He laid down his jacket on the table and picked up the handwritten note.
We need to lay this blanket down on the ground before we sit down.
Lay down.
The child laid his towel down on the sand.
Sand castle.
At the beach today, we made a sand castle and decorated it with seashells.
The sand castle started to crumble when the sun dried out the sand.
Sand castle.
The best way to make a sand castle is to use wet sand and a bucket.
Shallow.
We played in the shallow water all day long.
My mom says I am only allowed in the shallow end of the pool.
Shallow.
We found all kinds of seashells in the shallow water over there.
Stray.
The dog strayed a bit from the yard.
The child strayed a bit too far from the path in the woods and couldn't find her way back.
Stray.
She strayed from her tourist group to take pictures from time to time.
Sand bar.
We knew the tide was coming in when the sand bar started to slowly disappear.
I could see the sand bar in front of me, but I knew I hadn't reached it yet because my feet still couldn't touch the bottom.
Sand bar.
The children tried to reach the sand bar, but it was too far for them to swim.