EnglishPod.com Oh George, what a beautiful day it is.
The sun is hot and there are just a few clouds scattered here and there.
What a perfect day to be at the beach.
The kids are going to have so much fun and will be able to relax in the sun while they're playing.
It does seem like the perfect day.
I'm glad we chose to get out of the city and enjoy the nice weather.
This looks like the perfect spot.
Okay kids, put on your sunscreen while your mom and I set up camp.
Here Mary, help me lay down these beach towels.
There we go.
Can you help me with the umbrella?
Perfect.
Okay kids, here's a beach ball and a frisbee, a pail and a shovel.
I want to see an impressive sandcastle by the time we leave.
Don't stray too far.
Wait, leave your sandals here or put on your wet shoes.
And stay in the shallow area.
I don't want to see you go any further than that sandbar.
It's too deep out there and we didn't bring your floaties.
You're back already.
The water was too cold, huh?
I'll tell you a secret.
Do you see that small pool of water over there?
It'll be warmer in there.
Go see if you can find some seashells or catch some minnows.
Ah!
What is that?
A jellyfish?
Jeremy, put that down right now.
It could sting you.
Ah!
Not on me!