The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A medical substance that protects people or animals.
Vaccine Acute viral disease, usually affecting children and young adults.
Polio An infectious, often fatal disease caused by a specific bacterium that enters the body through wounds.
Tetanus Inflammation of the liver, caused by a virus or a toxin.
Hepatitis A mild contagious viral disease characterized by fever, mild upper respiratory congestion, and a fine red rash lasting a few days.
Rubella A disease common of children, characterized by mild headache and fever, an eruption of blisters on the skin.
Chicken pox An acute infectious disease occurring mostly in children, red spots being a common symptom.
Measles Characterized by inflammatory swelling of the other salivary glands.
Mumps Let's try that faster.
An acute infectious disease occurring mostly in children, red spots being a common symptom.
Measles A disease common of children, characterized by mild headache and fever, an eruption of blisters on the skin.
Chicken pox A medical substance that protects people or animals.
Vaccine A mild contagious viral disease characterized by fever, mild upper respiratory congestion, and a fine red rash lasting a few days.
Rubella Inflammation of the liver, caused by a virus or a toxin.
Hepatitis Characterized by inflammatory swelling of the other salivary glands.
Mumps An infectious, often fatal disease caused by a specific bacterium that enters the body through wounds.
Tetanus Acute viral disease usually affecting children and young adults.
Polio Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Polio Polio was basically eliminated early in the 20th century.
Polio Jonas Salk created the first polio vaccine.
Polio If untreated, polio can cause paralysis.
Chicken pox Chicken pox My entire class got chicken pox when I was in the third grade.
Chicken pox Chicken pox is not a fatal disease, but it is very irritating.
Chicken pox Vaccine A person with chicken pox will have little rashes all over the body.
Vaccine Scientists are working on an AIDS vaccine.
Vaccine There are many vaccines for pets such as dogs or cats.
Vaccine The flu vaccine is very popular in winter.
Hepatitis The doctor will administer a small dose of heroin to ease the pain.
Hepatitis Only doctors can administer certain types of drugs.
Hepatitis An antibiotic may be administered orally or by an injection.
Measles Measles are also referred to as rubiola.
Measles People that have measles will have a fever, runny nose, cough, and red eyes.
Measles There was a recent outbreak of measles in Boston.