EnglishPod.com Hello Mrs.
Parker, how have you been?
Hello Dr.
Peters.
Just fine, thank you.
Ricky and I are here for his vaccines.
Very well.
Let's see, according to his vaccination record, Ricky has received his polio, tetanus, and hepatitis B shots.
He is 14 months old, so he is due for hepatitis A, chicken pox, and measles shots.
What about rubella and mumps?
Well, I can only give him these for now, and after a couple of weeks I can administer the rest.
Okay, great.
Doctor, I think I also may need a tetanus booster.
Last time I got it was maybe 15 years ago.
We'll check our records, and I'll have the nurse administer the booster as well.
Now, please hold Ricky's arm tight.
This may sting a little.