The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Very dirty.
Disordered.
Such a mess.
Put things in place.
Organize.
Tidy up.
Perfectly clean.
Spotless.
Busy doing something at the moment.
In the middle of something.
Common house tasks.
Chores.
Food that you buy at a store.
Groceries.
Careful, thorough house cleaning usually done in the spring.
Perfectly clean.
Having no dirt at all.
Immaculate.
Wash the dirty clothes.
Do the laundry.
Soap used to wash plates, knives, forks, bowls, etc.
Dish detergent.
Garbage.
American English.
Trash.
Garbage.
British English.
Rubbish.
Let's try that faster.
Perfectly clean.
Spotless.
Careful, thorough house cleaning usually done in the spring.
Put things in place.
Organize.
Tidy up.
Garbage.
British English.
Rubbish.
Common house tasks.
Chores.
Soap used to wash plates, knives, forks, bowls, etc.
Dish detergent.
Perfectly clean.
Having no dirt at all.
Immaculate.
Garbage.
American English.
Trash.
Wash the dirty clothes.
Do the laundry.
Very dirty.
Disordered.
Such a mess.
Food that you buy at a store.
Groceries.
Busy doing something at the moment.
In the middle of something.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Such a mess.
Your room is such a mess.
You need to clean it.
Such a mess.
The garage is such a mess.
I can't find anything in here.
Such a mess.
When you cook, you always make such a mess.
Tidy up.
I want to tidy up my closet today because my clothes are all over the floor.
Since I cooked dinner tonight, you can tidy up the kitchen.
Tidy up.
If you want to go outside and play, you need to tidy up your room.
Every morning, I tidy up my room before leaving for work.
Spotless.
I spend a lot of time in the kitchen.
I spent all morning cleaning my car, so now it's spotless.
Spotless.
You did a great job cleaning the kitchen.
It's spotless.
Spotless.
We need to make sure that the house is spotless before the guests arrive.
In the middle of something.
I'm in the middle of something right now, so I'll call you back in 10 minutes.
I can't go to lunch now.
I'm in the middle of something really important.
In the middle of something.
I hate it when people interrupt me when I'm in the middle of something.
Chores.
When I was younger, I used to help my mother with the daily chores.
I wish I could go with you guys, but I have to finish my chores.
Chores.
I hate doing chores, especially washing the dishes.
Groceries.
We need to go buy some groceries for this week.
I forgot the grocery list at home, but don't worry.
I remember everything that was on it.
Groceries.
Don't forget to buy some milk from the grocery store on your way home.