EnglishPod.com Honey!
The house is such a mess!
I need you to help me tidy up a bit.
My boss and her husband are coming over for dinner and the house needs to be spotless.
I'm in the middle of something right now.
I'll be there in a second.
This can't wait!
I need your help now!
Alright, alright.
I'm coming.
Okay, here's a list of chores we need to get done.
I'll do the dishes and get all the groceries for tonight.
You can sweep and mop the floors.
Oh, and the furniture needs to be dusted.
You know what?
I have to pick something up in the mall, so why don't you clean the floors and I'll go to the supermarket and get all the groceries.
Sure, that's fine.
Here's the list of all the things we need to get.
Don't forget anything!
And can you pick up a bottle of wine on your way home?
Hey honey, I'm back!
Wow, the house looks really good!
Great.
Can you set the table?
Just a sec.
I'm just going to vacuum this rug real fast.
Wait!
Don't turn it on!