The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
lack out of to choose and buy pick up Something done to make people aware of a product.
promotion Don't take what you just said into consideration.
Never mind.
In addition to all the foregoing.
Last but not least.
A shop selling ready to eat food products.
Deli Let's try that faster.
Deli out of Something done to make people aware of a product.
Promotion Don't take what you just said into consideration.
Never mind.
In addition to all the foregoing.
Last but not least.
To choose and buy.
Pick up.
Out of The pharmacy is all out of aspirin.
Out of We are all out of milk.
Out of The store is all out of beer.
Pick up I'll pick up the kids after school.
Pick up First I need to go pick up some bread from the bakery.
Pick up Could you pick up the clothes from the dry cleaners as well?
Promotion My favorite clothing is having a promotion today on all their pants.
Promotion The grocery store is having a promotion on all the leftover Valentine's Day candy.
Promotion The car dealership put on a promotion for their newest car last month.
Never mind.
The apartment has no furniture?
I will look for another place.
Never mind.
I'm not going if she's not going.
That breaking into abandoned buildings is illegal.
It's fun.
Last but not least Last but not least, as I were made, I need you to cook dinner three times a week.
Last but not least Last but not least, can you take a look at the breaks as well?
Last but not least Last but not least, we have Jillian, who played the part of Goose.