EnglishPod.com Honey, we're all out of wine and cheese.
Do you mind running to the deli and picking up a few things?
Can't wait.
I'm watching the game right now.
Your friends and family are coming over tonight and we still need to get a lot of things.
Fine.
What do you need?
Okay, pick up some cured meats to go with the wine.
Maybe a pound of Polish sausages, ham, liverwurst, salami and any other cold cuts that are on sale.
I think I saw a promotion for pastrami.
Also, get some coleslaw and a jar of olives.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Isn't that a bit too much?
I mean, how much is all this going to cost?
Never mind that.
Get some dips as well.
Get a jar of spinach and blue cheese dips and also some satsiki.
If they have bean dip, get that as well.
Last but not least, get some pickles.
Is that all, your majesty?
Very funny.
Get a move on.
People will be here any minute.
.