EnglishPod.com What seems to be the problem?
I have a really bad toothache.
My cheek is swollen and I can't eat anything.
Let's have a look.
Mmm, this doesn't look too good.
I think we may have to pull out your wisdom tooth.
It's pressing against your molars and that's one of the reasons you are experiencing so much pain.
When you pull my tooth, will you also have to extract the nerve and the root?
First we will take some x-rays and see what we're dealing with.
I also noticed a small cavity up front here, so you are going to need a filling.
I guess that's what I get for not flossing or brushing my teeth three times a day.
It could be that, or maybe you are eating too many sweets.
In any case, I'll administer an anesthetic and you won't feel a thing.