The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Increase in size with liquid or internal pressure.
Swollen One of four rearmost molars on each side of both jaws.
Wisdom tooth Have the experience of, undergo, feel.
To experience That is what one deserves for.
That is what one gets for.
To clean with a brush.
To brush.
To give or apply as a remedy or relief.
To administer.
Let's try that faster.
Increase in size with liquid or internal pressure.
Swollen That is what one deserves for.
That is what one gets for.
One of four rearmost molars on each side of both jaws.
Wisdom tooth To give or apply as a remedy or relief.
To administer.
To clean with a brush.
To brush.
Have the experience of, undergo, feel.
To experience.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Swollen I got a mosquito bite on my arm and now it's swollen.
Swollen Tim's leg is swollen from the infection.
Swollen Someone punched him yesterday so his lip is slightly swollen.
Wisdom tooth I need to go to the dentist to get my wisdom teeth removed.
Wisdom tooth My wisdom tooth is really annoying me.
I keep on biting the inside of my cheek.
Wisdom tooth She couldn't eat for a few days after the dentist pulled her wisdom teeth.
To experience.
I have been experiencing really bad headaches lately.
Your chair is broken.
That must be the reason why you have been experiencing so much discomfort.
To experience.
To experience love is a wonderful thing.
I'm falling asleep at my desk.
I guess that's what I get for staying up to watch the World Cup.
To experience.
I just bought this purse yesterday and it's already broken.
That's what you get for buying something so cheap.
To experience.
I failed my math exam.
That's what I get for goofing off the entire semester.
To experience.
It is important to brush your teeth at least two times a day.
She is sitting in front of the mirror brushing her hair.
He brushed the breadcrumbs off the table.
To administer.
The doctor administered some painkillers to me after my operation.
The governor administers the law in this area.
To administer.
It is important for the government to administer justice.