Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A dirty or untidy place.
Pigsty.
To cause water to clean a toilet.
Flush.
Disgusting.
Gross.
Saying to indicate someone's idea or actions is unbelievable or crazy.
For example, are you out of your mind?
You can't fight a bear.
Are you out of your mind?
Likes to have every element of their life tidy and in order.
Neat freak.
Let's try that faster.
Disgusting.
Gross.
To cause water to clean a toilet.
Flush.
A dirty or untidy place.
Pigsty.
Likes to have every element of their life tidy and in order.
Neat freak.
Saying to indicate someone's idea or actions is unbelievable or crazy.
For example, are you out of your mind?
You can't fight a bear.
Are you out of your mind?
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Pigsty.
Mike never cleans his room.
It's like a pigsty in there.
Pigsty.
The kitchen looked like a pigsty after the party.
Don't use that washroom.
It's like a pigsty.
Flush.
Someone forgot to flush the toilet.
It's so disgusting.
Flush.
Make sure you flush the toilet when you're done.
Robert is training his cat how to flush the toilet.
Gross.
The bathroom is so gross.
Can you clean it please?
Gross.
That guy's wearing a bikini brief.
It's so gross.
Gross.
I saw some worms on the floor.
It's so gross.
Are you out of your mind?
This is going to cost you a fortune.
She's dating a married man.
Is she out of her mind?
Are you out of your mind?
I can't believe he's going to quit.
He must be out of his mind.
Neat freak.
Lily is such a neat freak.
She cleans her bathroom three times a day.
Neat freak.
My mom is a neat freak.
She asks me to clean my room three times a day.
Neat freak.
Johnny organises all his CDs and books alphabetically.
What a neat freak.