The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
thorough or complete stop in a relationship clean break prenuptial agreement, a contract prior to marriage prenup the act of keeping safe or guarding custody to acknowledge, often reluctantly, as being true concede proceed for an extended period of time drag this out set or keep apart in the relationship go our separate ways let's try that faster to acknowledge, often reluctantly, as being true concede proceed for an extended period of time drag this out set or keep apart in the relationship go our separate ways prenuptial agreement, a contract prior to marriage prenup thorough or complete stop in a relationship clean break, the act of keeping safe or guarding custody now say the word and hear it in a sentence clean break I don't care if he wants to keep the house and the car.
I just want a divorce and a clean break so I never have to see him again.
clean break A clean break can only occur if both parties are financially independent.
clean break go our separate ways You are not able to divorce with a clean break at the moment because your husband can't work and needs financial support.
go our separate ways I think it is better if we go our separate ways.
go our separate ways they decided to end the relationship and go their separate ways.
go our separate ways I proposed we go our separate ways but she didn't want to.
custody I am fighting for custody of my dog.
custody The court gave custody of the children to the father.
People always have custody battles when they get divorced.
concede After three hours of fighting, she conceded to him the computer.
concede I find it hard to concede when people are right.
concede He conceded me the right to use the car every day.
Drag this out.
I hate it when people drag out a conversation for hours.
I don't want to drag out this argument any longer.
Drag this out.
The weatherman said that this bad weather will drag out for another three days.