The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Try on to put clothing in order to judge its appearance and fit.
Try on.
Affording little or no extra room, fitting closely.
Tight.
To go into or through a particular space.
Fit.
Bulges of fat at the sides of the waist.
Love handles.
Get someone to pay attention.
Show.
Let's try that faster.
Get someone to pay attention.
Show.
Affording little or no extra room, fitting closely.
Tight.
To go into or through a particular space.
Fit.
Try on to put clothing in order to judge its appearance and fit.
Try on.
Bulges of fat at the sides of the waist.
Love handles.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Try on.
She tried on a lot of clothes and in the end, she didn't buy anything.
Let me try this on and see if it fits.
Try on.
This dress is so lovely, can I try it on?
Fit.
This shirt looks really tight on you, are you sure this is the right size?
I don't like clothes that are too tight.
Fit.
This pair of shoes are a bit tight, do you have a larger size?
Tight.
I don't like clothes that are too tight.
This pair of shoes are a bit tight, do you have a larger size?
Tight.
This shirt looks really tight on you, are you sure this is the right size?
Show.
Sheena's showing off her new handbag again.
The cutting of this shirt really shows off my curves.
Show.
He bought that sports car just to show off.
Love handles.
I'm afraid your love handles are showing.
Julie is working hard to get rid of her love handles.
Love handles.
She likes to wear loose t-shirts to hide her love handles.