Hello, English learners.
Welcome back to EnglishPod.
My name is Marco.
And I'm Erica.
And today we're going to be bringing you a great lesson about calling the office.
Yeah, that's right.
So in this lesson, we're going to teach you some great words that you can use when you need to call your office to solve a problem.
Right.
So you are at home, you have a problem, maybe you can't go to the office.
So you have to call them and tell them that you're not going to be able to go.
Yes.
Alright, so we're not going to preview anything today because the dialogue is relatively easy.
So let's listen to the dialogue for the first time and then we'll come back and look at some words.
Actually, I'm a pretty easy dialogue.
Yeah, pretty simple.
Alright, so there are a couple of words that we want to look at.
So let's start with language takeaway.
Language takeaway.
Alright, well today we're looking at three interesting words.
The first one is ooflay.
Ooflay.
Marco, what is the ooflay?
Alright, so when you have the ooflay, it means that you are sick.
You have, it's very similar to a cold.
Right, but just worse, right?
Worse, yeah.
So when you have the ooflay, it'll keep you in bed for a while, for maybe a week or two.
So you have a fever, your body is hurting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're really sick.
Yeah, you're really sick.
Okay.
So, ooflay.
Alright, well what about our next word?
Well, actually the next word is a phrase that you can use when you're calling the office.
Alinkai in iksei.
Okay, this is a really useful phrase and I think it would help us to hear some examples of what it sounds like so we can understand the meaning.
Example one.
Oofay iplpay aldke in iksei udetei.
Example two.
If ooyei aldke in iksei on one ormei aintei oryei airdfei.
Example three.
Imatnei ilingfei aloue.
Ossei imalenkei in iksei.
So with this phrase, you're basically saying that you are not going to the office.
Exactly.
So let's take a look at our last word for language takeaway.
Ikovarei.
Okay, so it's a pretty simple word.
Ikovarei means to get better, to start feeling healthy again.
Okay, so kind of to recharge your batteries.
Exactly, so this is a great verb to use when you want to say I'm going to feel better.
Okay, ikovarei.
So some really great words, some really interesting phrases.
So let's listen to this dialogue again and then we'll come back.
All right, Marco, have you ever found yourself in a situation like this?
Well, yeah, a couple of times that I haven't been able to really make it to the office and I've had to call.
So yeah, I would have to call and tell them that I'm not going to make it or maybe then I'm going to be a little bit late.
All right, well, yeah, happens to all of us.
And now you guys have all of this useful language next time you face this problem.
Exactly.
So if you have any questions or comments, be sure to visit our website EnglishPod.com.
Marco and I are there to respond to your questions and comments.
As well, there are also lots of other great lessons for you to check out on the website.
Exactly, so be sure to check out some of our first lessons.
I'm sure you'll find them useful as well.
Yes.
Okay, well thanks for listening everyone and until next time.
Bye.