The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A machine outside a bank which people use to get money from their account.
ATM Put something into something.
Insert A narrow place to put in a card or paper.
Slot Personal identity number.
PIN The push button marked with a hash key.
Pound key The action of getting money from an account.
Withdrawal Get money from an account.
Withdrawal To move money from your account into others.
Transfer Government organization which keeps the order of a certain place.
Authority To put money into a bank account.
An amount of money that is used for a special purpose.
Fund A strong metal box with a lock that is used to store money or valuable things.
Safe The amount of money that is left in your bank account.
Balance A request for information.
Inquiry Let's try that faster!
The amount of money that is left in your bank account.
Balance Government organization which keeps the order of a certain place.
Authority A strong metal box with a lock that is used to store money or valuable things.
Safe Put something into something.
Insert To put money into a bank account.
Deposit The push button marked with a hash key.
Pound key To move money from your account into others.
Transfer A narrow place to put in a card or paper.
Slot A machine outside a bank which people use to get money from their account.
ATM A request for information.
Inquiry Get money from an account.
Withdraw The action of getting money from an account.
Withdraw An amount of money that is used for a special purpose.
Fund Personal Identity Number PIN Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Slot Excuse me, can you help me?
This coin doesn't fit in the slot of that slot machine.
Slot The mailbox slot is too small for this package.
I will leave it next to the door.
Slot The coin slot is jammed with gum and now I can't buy a soda.
Insert Banks allow you to withdraw maximum $500 a day.
To open the main door, you have to insert this key and turn it clockwise.
Insert Select I like the modern hotel rooms where you have to insert a key card to open the door.
Withdraw Insert a picture into your report.
It will make it look nicer.
Withdraw I tried to withdraw money from my bank but my card was blocked.
Withdraw Fortunately, you can withdraw money at the ATM machine at any time.
Transfer Bank of London doesn't allow international transfers.
Transfer My cousin wanted to transfer the deed of his house over to me, but it was a complicated process.
Transfer If you want to make a money transfer, you need to fill out these forms, please.
The container is sealed airtight to prevent food from spoiling.
We had to hire someone to seal our windows because cold air was coming in.
The police has sealed off all the exits so that no one can go in or out.