EnglishPod.com Pin code followed by the pound key.
Thank you.
Please select an option.
You have selected withdraw.
Yeah, yeah, I know what I selected.
Just give me my money.
Please type the amount you would like to withdraw.
Thank you.
You want to transfer.
10,000 US dollars to the World Wildlife Foundation.
If this is correct, please press 1.
No, no.
Stupid machine, what are you doing?
No.
Confirmed.
Thank you for using our bank.
Please remove your card from the slot.
Goodbye.
No way.
What happened?
Give me my money.
Danger.
The exits have been sealed and the doors will remain locked until the local authorities arrive.
Thank you for using our bank.
Have a nice day.