The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Please come in.
Come on in.
The person that rents a house.
Tenant.
Disorder, unorganized.
Mess.
The owner of the apartment.
Landlord.
Spacious so that air moves freely.
Airy.
Showing how big one's space is measured in feet.
Square footage.
Electric equipment found in a house.
Appliance.
Good enough to satisfy professional use.
Professional grade.
A stove that uses gas to cook.
Gas range.
Large, having lots of space.
Spacious.
A room contained in a bedroom for storing clothes.
Walk-in closet.
A bathroom within the main bedroom.
Ensuite bathroom.
A room or space that is just below the roof of a building and that is often used to store things.
Attic.
The parts of a building that is entirely or partly below the ground.
Basement.
An area of ground, such as the ground around a house or in a garden or park, that is covered with short grass.
Lawn.
The business of selling land and buildings.
Real estate.
To allow someone to use something for a period of time in return for payment.
Lease.
Let's try that faster.
Disorder.
Unorganized.
The person that rents a house.
Tenant.
To allow someone to use something for a period of time in return for payment.
Lease.
A room or space that is just below the roof of a building and that is often used to store things.
Attic.
Spacious so that air moves freely.
Airy.
An area of ground, such as the ground around a house or in a garden or park, that is covered with short grass.
Lawn.
The owner of the apartment.
Landlord.
The business of selling land and buildings.
Real estate.
The parts of a building that is entirely or partly below the ground.
Basement.
Please come in.
Come on in.
A stove that uses gas to cook.
Gas range.
Electric equipment found in a house.
Appliance.
Good enough to satisfy professional use.
Professional grade.
A room contained in a bedroom for storing clothes.
Walk-in closet.
Large.
Having lots of space.
Spacious.
Showing how big one's space is measured in feet.
Square footage.
A bathroom within the main bedroom.
En suite bathroom.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I had to renovate my kitchen because I accidentally burned everything while cooking.
The city recently renovated the local church.
John is planning on renovating his night club so as to make it more modern.
Airy.
I'm glad we took out all the extra furniture.
Now this room is a lot more airy.
Airy.
The living room looks great.
That big window really makes it feel more airy.
Airy.
Our office has a high ceiling and big windows so it feels really open and airy.
Square footage.
As a civil engineer I have to calculate the square footage of the construction site.
Robert is worried that the square footage of the house wasn't big enough for his family.
Square footage.
What's the square footage of the living room?
Appliance.
In this store you can buy any type of kitchen appliance such as a toaster, a blender, etc.
All of our electrical appliances were damaged by the thunderstorm.
Appliance.
My cousin is selling all her household appliances because she is moving to China.
This job offer is amazing.
It's almost too good to be true.
I can't believe you got this car for free.
I think it sounds too good to be true.
I found the perfect boyfriend.
He cooks, cleans, and treats me well.
It's almost too good to be true.