EnglishPod.com Hi, we are the Christiansons.
We're here to see the apartment.
Oh, hi.
Sure.
Come on in.
Well, as you can see, the place has just been renovated.
The previous tenants left a huge mess here, so the landlord has done everything.
It looks great.
It's so bright and airy.
What great light.
I really love these hardwood floors.
What's the square footage of this place?
Well, it's about 120 square meters, or 1,300 square feet, more or less.
Oh, the landlord has also installed new kitchen appliances.
There's a new dishwasher and a professional-grade gas range.
Really, at this price, this place is an amazing deal.
I love it.
But wait, what are the payment terms?
First and last month rent as deposit, and rent is due on the first of every month.
Considering the amount of money invested into the apartment, it's a very good deal.
Yes, it is.
Too good to be true.
The living room and dining room are quite spacious, as you can see.
And down this hall, here's the master bedroom.
It has a huge walk-in closet and an en suite bathroom.
We can't go in there yet as the police, uh, I mean, the cleanup crew hasn't finished yet.
Uh, what do you mean?
What's in here?
Ahhhhhh!