The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The aggregate of courses of study given in a school, college, university, etc.
Curriculum Device, drug, or chemical agent that prevents conception.
Contraceptive A thin sheath worn over the penis during sex.
Condom To stop from happening.
To prevent.
To get or acquire as by exposure to something contagious.
To contract.
Let's try that faster.
To stop from happening.
To prevent.
To get or acquire as by exposure to something contagious.
To contract.
A thin sheath worn over the penis during sex.
Condom The aggregate of courses of study given in a school, college, university, etc.
Curriculum Device, drug, or chemical agent that prevents conception.
Contraceptive Curriculum If you follow our curriculum, we guarantee you will lose 10 pounds this week.
Curriculum My school curriculum requires that all students need to take 12th grade English.
Curriculum The curriculum for this course is intense.
Contraceptive Even with the variety and effectiveness of contraceptives today, there are still numerous cases of unwanted pregnancies every year.
Contraceptive The most effective methods of contraception involve surgery, not contraceptives.
Contraceptive My wife's contraceptive of choice is the pill.
To prevent She takes a birth control pill in order to prevent an unwanted pregnancy.
To prevent Diabetes I am genetically prone to developing diabetes so in order to prevent it, I need to start watching what I eat.
To prevent I am grateful to my best friend because he stepped in and prevented me from doing something that I would regret.
To contract I just learned that a friend of mine recently contracted an STD.
To contract My mom contracted a disease that is causing her to lose her sight.
To contract I am very paranoid about contracting STDs from toilet seats.
Condom Using a condom will protect against contracting STDs and getting pregnant.
Condom Condoms nowadays come in all different textures, colors, and flavors.
Condom The effectiveness of a condom disappears the moment there is a tear in the condom.