EnglishPod.com Alright, settle down everyone.
As part of this school's curriculum, we'll be covering sex ed this week.
Oh boy, yeah.
Now, I want everyone to take this class seriously.
Sexual education is very important, and I want you to ask as many questions as you can think of.
Remember, there are no stupid questions here.
Ms.
Carleton, what exactly is sexual education?
Are you going to teach us, like, Kamasutra and stuff like that?
No, Jason, that's not actually what sex ed is.
Basically, we will talk about sexually transmitted diseases, contraceptives, and how the male and female bodies work.
My older sister is in college, and she takes what she and her friends call the pill.
I never really understood what that is.
But I know it has to do with sex or something.
Good point, Jason.
This will be the topic of our first class, contraceptives.
As you mentioned, the pill is one of the many that exist.
The birth control pill is taken daily by a woman in order to prevent unwanted pregnancy, but it does not protect her from contracting STDs from an infected person.
Another popular method is using condoms.
This is probably the best method if you have sex, since it not only prevents a woman from getting pregnant, but also protects you from STDs.
Yes, Jason?
What are condoms made out of?
How is it exactly that a woman gets pregnant?
Condoms are usually made out of an elastic material called latex.
As for your other question, that's a whole new class.