The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The written words from a film.
Screenplay.
The activity of an actor in a play.
Performance.
Have the confidence to say.
Dare to say.
The main person in a movie.
Central character.
Story in a movie or book.
Plot.
According to law.
Rightfully.
Used to describe the camera work in a movie.
Cinematography.
Having a lot of knowledge, especially gained from studying.
Erudite.
The feelings one has after a specific event.
Impression.
To describe, show, especially in art or pictures.
Depict.
Beautiful story about animals that has a moral or lesson.
Fable.
Lasting forever.
Eternal.
Action of claiming something is wrong.
Accusation.
Practice of copying others' ideas.
Plagiarism.
Attractive, holding one's attention.
Enchanting.
Written work showing notes of music.
Score.
Easy for others to foresee what is going to happen.
Predictable.
The act of showing or describing something, especially in art.
Portrayal.
Unpleasant.
Grim.
Moving in logical way, from start to end.
Linear.
Something that is too often used so that it loses meaning or importance.
Cliche.
Something that survives the testing of time.
Time-honored.
Not critical enough.
Soft.
Let's try that faster.
Used to describe the camera work in a movie.
Cinematography.
The feelings one has after a specific event.
Impression.
The main person in a movie.
Central character.
The written words from a film.
Screenplay.
According to law.
Rightfully.
Action of claiming something is wrong.
Accusation.
Lasting forever.
Eternal.
Something that is too often used so that it loses meaning or importance.
Cliche.
Attractive.
Holding one's attention.
Enchanting.
Written work showing notes of music.
Score.
Have the confidence to say.
Dare to say.
To describe, show, especially in art or pictures.
Depict.
The activity of an actor in a play.
Performance.
Easy for others to foresee what is going to happen.
Predictable.
Story in a movie or book.
Plot.
Not critical enough.
Soft.
Having a lot of knowledge, especially gained from studying.
Erudite.
Something that survives the testing of time.
Time-honored.
Unpleasant.
Grim.
Moving in logical way from start to end.
Linear.
Beautiful story about animals that has a moral or lesson.
Fable.
The act of showing or describing something, especially in art.
Portrayal.
Practice of copying others' ideas.
Plagiarism.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Impression.
I don't know where, but I have the impression that we have met before.
I get the impression that he is a very organized person.
Impression.
Somehow, Jim got the impression that I was gay.
Did you tell him that?
Our company lacks the manpower for this new project.
The problem with our school is that it lacks the infrastructure for so many students.
I like these paintings, but I think they lack creativity and passion.
Dare to say.
I would dare to say that your report is completely erroneous.
She dared to say that I had no class.
Can you imagine that?
Dare to say.
I would dare to say that this is the most beautiful city in the world.
Come on.
Are you really going to quit?
You don't want to really break up with your girlfriend.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Don't be so rude to the waitress.
Rightfully.
The king is claiming that France should rightfully belong to England.
Dan found a dog on the street, but returned it to its rightful owner.
Rightfully.
I rightfully took back what belonged to me from the thief.