EnglishPod.com Very good.
Now I have a couple of final questions.
I hope they're not too hard.
Well, why should we hire you?
I think that I would be a perfect fit in this company.
I have a unique combination of strong technical acumen with outstanding soft skills.
I excel at building strong, long-term consumer relationships.
For example, when I headed the customer support department in my previous company, our team resolved about 70% of our customers' problems.
I decided that we needed better information and technical preparation on our products.
So after I implemented a series of training sessions in coordination with our technical department, we were able to solve 90% of our customers' issues.
Given the opportunity, I could bring this kind of success to this company.
Impressive.
So what would you consider to be your greatest weakness?
To be honest, I struggle with organization and time management.
Punctuality has never been a strength of mine.
I find it hard to organize my time effectively.
I've actually addressed this weakness recently by attending a workshop on efficient time management.
It helped me a lot by providing me with great insights on how to get organized and use my time efficiently.
So I think I'm getting better now.
Great.
Well, let me tell you that I am very pleased with this interview.
We are short-listing our candidates this week.
And next week, we will inform our short-listed candidates of the day and time for a second interview with our CEO.
Great.
Thanks a lot.
I hope to hear from you.
Goodbye.
Thank you.