EnglishPod.com Tom, how are you?
Hey, we missed you at the party last night.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
I didn't really feel like going out.
I guess I'm feeling a little homesick.
Come on.
We've been through this already.
Look, I know the adjustment was hard when you first got here, but we agree that you were going to try and deal with it.
I was.
It's just that the holidays are coming up, and I won't be able to go home because I can't afford the airfare.
I'm just longing for some of the comforts of home, like my mom's cooking and being around my family.
Yeah, it can get pretty lonely over the holidays.
When I first got here, I'd get depressed and nostalgic for anything that reminded me of home.
I almost let it get to me, but then I started going out, keeping myself busy, and before I knew it, I was used to it.
I see what you mean, but I'm still bummed out.
Okay, how does this sound?
Let's get you suited up and hit the dance club tonight.
I hear that an awesome DJ is playing, and there will be a lot of pretty single girls there.
You know, I could really go for that.
You don't mind being my wingman for tonight.
Not at all.
It'll be fun.
It will be like a boy's night out.
Well, kind of.
Great!
I must warn you though, whatever happens, don't let me go on a drinking binge.
Trust me, it's not a pretty picture.