The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Sad because you're away from home.
Homesick.
Bare the cost of.
Afford.
Showing a strong desire for something.
Longing for.
Home sick.
Nostalgic.
Disappointed.
Bummed out.
Let's try that faster.
Homesick.
Nostalgic.
Sad because you're away from home.
Homesick.
Bare the cost of.
Afford.
Disappointed.
Bummed out.
Showing a strong desire for something.
Longing for.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Homesick.
After six months living abroad, Ben started feeling homesick.
The best cure for homesickness is a phone call home.
Homesick.
I became homesick after looking at our family pictures.
Afford.
Unfortunately, I can't afford to spend money on entertainment these days.
You can't afford to miss this opportunity.
Afford.
We were too poor to afford a doctor.
Longing for.
We are all longing for a peaceful world.
After three months of separation, he longed for his wife.
Longing for.
I'm longing for the summer to end.
Nostalgic.
The old friends shared many nostalgic memories.
Away from nostalgia swept over me after seeing my childhood home again.
Nostalgic.
She spoke nostalgically about her school days.
Bummed out.
He is bummed out because his girlfriend dumped him.
Don't be bummed out about the bad weather.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Bummed out.
Our team lost.
What a bummer.