EnglishPod.com Hey Carl, can you make a copy of this contract for me please?
And when you have it ready, send it out ASAP to our sub-branch.
Sure.
I think I broke this thing.
Maxine, can you help me out here?
I'm not really a tech guy.
Yeah, sure.
I think it's just out of toner.
You can go use the other one upstairs.
On your way up, can you fax this while I try and fix this thing?
Sure.
Damn it!
Everything in this office seems to be breaking down.
I'll send the stupid fax later.
Oh great!
Is someone playing a practical joke on me?
This is ridiculous!
The elevator has some sort of malfunction.
Just take the stairs dude.
What floor are you going to?
I have to go up 15 floors!
Never mind.
Made it.
There's a copier.
No!
Thanks for watching!