The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Relax.
Become calm.
Settle down.
Part.
Aspect.
Origin.
Beginning.
Understand deeply.
Comprehend.
The day that all people in a country will be on holiday.
National holiday.
Terrible.
Horrible.
Shocking.
Appalling.
Showing no interest in.
Indifference.
The attitude of treating something as enemy.
Hostility.
Relating to legal system.
Legislative.
Sudden and severe.
Drastic.
A formal document stating the wishes of a group.
Resolution.
Form.
Consist.
Constitute.
Violent treatment or behavior.
Brutality.
Shoot guns into a place.
Fire into.
Describing an event that is done to honor and remember a person or event in history.
In commemoration of.
Know.
The lowest socioeconomic class.
Workers.
Proletariat.
A public meeting of a large group of people to support or oppose something.
Rally.
An official statement made by a person who has power.
Proclamation.
Something like a statue built to remember a person or event from history.
Memorial.
Let's try that faster.
Shoot guns into a place.
Fire into.
Terrible.
Horrible.
Shocking.
Appalling.
Form.
Consist.
Constitute.
Relax.
Become calm.
Settle down.
Violent treatment or behavior.
Brutality.
Relating to legal system.
Legislative.
The attitude of treating something as enemy.
Hostility.
The lowest socioeconomic class.
Workers.
Proletariat.
Describing an event that is done to honor and remember a person or event in history.
In commemoration of.
Know.
Sudden and severe.
Drastic.
Part.
Aspect.
Origin.
Beginning.
Genesis.
A formal document stating the wishes of a group.
Resolution.
Something like a statue built to remember a person or event from history.
Memorial.
The day that all people in a country will be on holiday.
National holiday.
An official statement made by a person who has power.
Proclamation.
Showing no interest in.
Indifference.
A public meeting of a large group of people to support or oppose something.
Rally.
Understand deeply.
Comprehend.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Genesis.
How did you get started on this project?
What was its genesis?
Genesis.
We need to identify the genesis of this problem.
I'm studying the genesis of the feminist movement.
Appalling.
The way those poor children have been treated is just appalling.
I'm absolutely appalled by your behavior.
Appalling.
The service in that restaurant was appalling.
It took 45 minutes for them to bring us our wine.
Legislative.
We can't just rely on self-enforced policy.
We must find a legislative solution.
Legislative.
I don't know much about the legislative process in the US.
The president can't decide the laws.
That's the responsibility of the legislative branch of government.
Resolution.
The board will vote on a resolution asking the president to resign.
The UN Security Council passed a resolution regarding the Middle East.
Resolution.
A resolution was introduced in the Senate supporting states' rights.
We've got to take drastic measures.
I think we should cut off his leg.
This calls for drastic measures.
I'm declaring a state of emergency.
We've got to take drastic measures.
We have to take drastic measures to cut our costs.