EnglishPod.com Thank you, Jonathan.
It really is a pleasure to be here today.
It has been three years since I visited Beijing and it's clear to me that operations here are obviously going from strength to strength.
The Alpha brand continues to grow in leaps and bounds in China and that is certainly down to the hard work of all of you here.
So congratulations to all of you.
I'd like to start by outlining the key points of my presentation this afternoon and giving you an idea of the topics that will be discussed.
The presentation today is divided into five main parts.
First of all, I'd like to briefly touch on the background of the new X420 line.
How the whole concept has come about and how the new product fits into our existing brand line.
Secondly, I'd like to present data on projected sales for the X420.
We will then go on to discuss our key rivals in this sector.
Then I would like to go on to outline the campaign concept for the X420.
Finally, I'm happy to open up the discussion for any questions or points you may have for me.