The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Reduce in value Devalue Showing insight and undertaking Discerning The latest and most advanced in technology State of the art Showing realization and perception Awareness To subvert or weaken insidiously or secretly Undermine Let's try that faster Showing realization and perception Awareness Reduce in value Devalue The latest and most advanced in technology State of the art Showing insight and undertaking Discerning To subvert or weaken insidiously or secretly Undermine Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Devalue How can we make our service more accessible to the masses without devaluing our product?
Devalue With the devaluation of the dollar, traveling overseas is now much more expensive.
Devalue Discerning Many luxury brands never have sales for fear of devaluing their product.
Discerning To the discerning shopper, quality is always better than quantity.
Discerning Sandra is known for her discerning taste in music and the arts.
Discerning The discerning drinker knows the difference between this wine and the cheaper wine.
State of the art State of the art We installed new state of the art machines in our factories to fulfill the recent surge in demand.
State of the art This company uses the most state of the art technology to make their computers.
State of the art The doctors use the state of the art technique to operate on her heart.
Awareness How can we achieve top of mind awareness in our field if we don't distinguish ourselves from our customers?
Awareness Through years of advertising and expansion, McDonald's has top of mind awareness when it comes to fast food chains.
Awareness Marlboro has top of mind awareness around among cigarette companies.
Undermine He is a ruthless politician who likes to undermine his rivals in his advertising campaigns.
Undermine Your unthoughtful actions are undermining the legitimacy of this organization.
Undermine Even if you don't want to work here anymore, there's no reason to undermine the company by bad-mouthing it to your peers.