EnglishPod.com Okay everyone, let's begin.
I called you here today to evaluate our marketing strategy during this recession.
I wanted to re-emphasize our corporate mission of aiming to give our customers the best coffee and service in a clean and welcoming atmosphere.
Several other shops have been reducing their prices for their coffees and they are drawing in more customers.
Why aren't we doing the same thing?
I know that recent sales have been slow, but we are not going to reduce our prices to the level of our competitors.
We offer a superior product and our focus is on long-term growth rather than short-term sales.
If we lower our prices, we run the risk of devaluing our product.
Customers don't care about coffee anymore.
They only care about price.
I disagree.
Highly discerning customers know that our coffee is far better than the coffee you buy at the other places.
Our coffee beans are artisan roasted and we use state-of-the-art equipment to brew our coffees.
When you compare the coffees side by side, our coffee wins the taste test every time.
We have never sought to appeal to the mass market with cheap coffee drinks, and we will not do so now.
That's true.
We've certainly achieved top-of-mind awareness when it comes to the best tasting brews, and it's important to distinguish ourselves from the competitors.
I think the main question is, how can we show our appreciation to our customers?
That's the main question I would like to discuss today.
Money is tight for everyone these days, so even our most loyal customers may be reconsidering the money they pay for their morning coffee.
Since the superiority of our coffee beans is one of our core competencies, why don't we sell the beans for people to brew coffee at home?
That could definitely be a way we could expand our company, but would we be undermining the essence of the company that way?
Let's brainstorm some more ideas and do some research.
The customer always comes first, and what the customer wants, the customer gets.
Maybe it's time we started selling coffee beans.