The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A tall lamp with a base that stands on the floor.
Floor lamp A large wardrobe or cabinet Armoire A set of shelves usually used for holding clothes.
Dresser A small table or stand placed at a bedside.
Nightstand Small sofa that seats two people.
Love seat An armchair that can be reclined.
Recliner During the time you are there.
While you are at it.
Let's try that faster.
A large wardrobe or cabinet Armoire An armchair that can be reclined.
Recliner During the time you are there.
While you are at it.
Small sofa that seats two people.
Love seat A set of shelves usually used for holding clothes.
Dresser A tall lamp with a base that stands on the floor.
Floor lamp A small table or stand placed at a bedside.
Nightstand Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Armoire My sister prefers armoires to dressers because she can see everything at once.
Armoire My room doesn't have a closet so I use an armoire instead.
Armoire He gazed longingly at the antique armoire with its carved wood and faded paintings.
But he only had $50 in his pocket.
Dresser Please make sure you put your clothes away in your dresser.
Dresser He took some change out of the piggy bank on his dresser.
Dresser I opened up the dresser door and hid my diary underneath the clothes.
Love seat My parents have a wooden love seat on their front porch.
Love seat Love seats are much cozier than couches.
Love seat I curled up next to my husband on the love seat.
While you are at it While you are at it can you take the clothes out of the dryer.
While you are at it While you are at it can you make sure the dogs have enough water in their bowl.
While you are at it Can you pick up some coffee while you are at it.
Recliner After a hard day's work my father would always sink into his leather recliner and watch the news.
Recliner A recliner is a special chair designed so that you can sit upright or recline back with your feet up.
Recliner It wasn't until a few hours later that I discovered the chair I was sitting on was a recliner.