The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Start anew.
Turn over a new leaf.
Start over.
Wipe the slate clean.
Chance.
Opportunity.
Start.
Adopt the study.
Take up.
To be thrifty.
Pinch pennies.
Support you.
With you.
To state openly or publicly one's homosexuality.
Come out of the closet.
Let's try that faster.
To be thrifty.
Pinch pennies.
Chance.
Opportunity.
Start.
Adopt the study.
Take up.
To state openly or publicly one's homosexuality.
Come out of the closet.
Start over.
Wipe the slate clean.
Start anew.
Turn over a new leaf.
Support you.
With you.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Turn over a new leaf.
The dragon decided to turn over a new leaf by opening a new bar and grill restaurant instead of burning and eating humans.
My sister has really turned over a new leaf since the last time I saw her.
She doesn't get angry easily anymore and is more thoughtful.
Turn over a new leaf.
EnglishPod decided to turn over a new leaf and offer learning English in Chinese to its users.
Wipe the slate clean.
I was unhappy with the way I was living so I decided to wipe the slate clean and start again.
By wiping the slate clean, he was able to forget the troubles of his past and go on with living his life.
Wipe the slate clean.
She hoped that by starting this new business she could wipe the slate clean and be accepted back into the community.
Now that I've graduated, this is my opportunity to make a difference in the world.
When it was his turn to sing karaoke, he jumped at the opportunity to show his friends how good he was.
When they were finally alone on the beach watching the sunset, he took the opportunity to tell her that he loved her.
Take up I decided I wasn't good at the piano so I took up guitar instead.
Take up Are you going to take up dancing this year or are you going to stick to gymnastics?
Take up I am going to take up learning Chinese as my New Year's resolution.
With you You think he was guilty?
I'm with you on that one.
Were with you to the death.
Take up I'm with you when you say that life's not fair.
But I don't agree that we should just sit around and feel sorry for ourselves when life gets tough.
Thanks for watching!