EnglishPod.com Hello everyone and welcome back to our show.
Today we are going to learn how to cook the perfect Thanksgiving turkey.
I will share a secret that I have kept for over 30 years on how to cook the perfect, most mouth-watering, juiciest turkey in the world.
Let's get started.
First of all, we must bring out our key ingredient.
Whiskey.
You see, the grains used to make whiskey along with the alcohol brings out the flavor of the turkey meat.
Let's pour one cup of whiskey on the turkey and serve yourself a cup as well.
Cheers!
That's good 12-year whiskey right there.
Okay, back to our turkey.
Preheat your oven to 475 degrees Fahrenheit.
Now have another cup of whiskey.
Now that the oven is hot, we place our bird on a rack inside a roasting pan.
Let's add some whiskey to give it some extra flavor.
Let's have another cup.
That hit the spot.
There we go.
We can leave it in there for the next 45 minutes.
In the meantime, let's have another sip of whiskey and start with our delicious pumpkin pie.
Lightly whisk together two eggs and the extra yolk in a large bowl.
Once that's ready, we can put sugar, spices such as cloves, grated nutmeg, and cinnamon with some cream and dark rum into a saucepan.
Slowly bring up to simmering point, stirring occasionally.
Now you may notice that we are using some dark rum in this pie.
This is because the richness of the pumpkin is beautifully enhanced by the dark rum.
So to celebrate this great occasion, pour yourself a glass.
Cheers!
Now that we have finished with the filling, let's bake the pie for 45 to 50 minutes until the filling has puffed up around the edges and the center is almost set.
All done!
A cup of rum to celebrate the completion of this great Thanksgiving dinner.
After waiting for an hour and having a couple of drinks, it's time to check on our turkey.
Take the turkey out of the oven.
Pick the turkey off of the ground.
Don't worry, it will add flavor to this recipe.
Now also remove the pie from the oven and serve while still hot.
Cheers and Happy Thanksgiving!