The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Requiring skill or caution Tricky A series of musical notes Scale The speed at which a musical piece is played Tempo Very quickly By leaps and bounds The skill of performing music Musicianship A specific musical tone Note Changes in how loudly a piece of music is played Dynamics A button to press with fingers to produce sounds Key Let's try that faster Changes in how loudly a piece of music is played Dynamics Requiring skill or caution Tricky The speed at which a musical piece is played Tempo Very quickly By leaps and bounds A series of musical notes Scale A button to press with fingers to produce sounds Key The skill of performing music Musicianship A specific musical tone Note Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Note The crowd cheered wildly when she hit the high note at the end of the song.
Note This tune represents a fluttering butterfly so the note should be played lightly and fluidly.
Note The two sixteenth notes were followed by a quarter note and an eighth note.
Tempo As soon as the band picked up the tempo, several groups of people began dancing on the dance floor.
Tempo This week, I want you to practice this section at a slow tempo, hands separately.
Tempo There are no markings indicating the tempo in this piece but I think it sounds best when played adante.
By leaps and bounds Tempo Your musicianship has been improving by leaps and bounds recently.
By leaps and bounds The value of his investments kept increasing by leaps and bounds.
By leaps and bounds Tempo The construction work on the new apartment complex was advancing by leaps and bounds.
Dynamics The dynamics in this piece are few but there are many changes in time signature.
Dynamics Watch out for the dynamics and remember to get softer here and louder in this section.
Dynamics Sometimes when I play a piece of music, I ignore the marked dynamics and play it the way I feel it should be played instead.
Key The piano has black keys and white keys.
Key He stroked the keys beautifully as he played.
Key The child giggled at the sound that was made when he pressed down on the piano keys.