The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Way to clean clothes without water using chemicals.
Dry clean To allow something to fall from the container.
Spill Marked or dyed or discoloured with foreign matter.
Stained Stiffen, clothes, etc.
with starch.
Starch To smooth clothes with a heated iron.
Iron Let's try that faster.
Marked or dyed or discoloured with foreign matter.
Stained To allow something to fall from the container.
Spill Stiffen, clothes, etc.
with starch.
Starch Way to clean clothes without water using chemicals.
Dry clean To smooth clothes with a heated iron.
Iron Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Dry clean I need to dry clean my skirt.
Dry clean I picked up your clothes from the dry cleaners.
Dry clean The tag on this shirt says dry clean only.
Spill She spilled her juice all over her homework.
Spill He was in such a hurry that he spilled his coffee all over the front of his shirt.
Spill Spill There was an oil spill just off the coast.
Stained Her children had grass stains on their pants.
Stained Stained I'm never going to be able to get the stain out of this shirt.
Stained The wine he spilled stained his pants.
Starch Starch Can you starch my shirt?
Starch He starched his dress shirts so that they were nice and crisp.
Starch You can starch your jeans as well.
Iron He irons his shirt before putting it on.
Iron I need to iron the laundry.
Iron Every night my mom does the ironing while watching TV.