EnglishPod.com Valerie, hi.
Wow, how have you been?
It's been such a long time.
Darlene, indeed it's been a while.
How have you been?
Wow, you look amazing.
I love what you've done with your hair.
Really?
Thanks.
I went to that hair salon you told me about, but enough about me.
Look at you.
God, you haven't ate just a day.
Hey, what is your secret?
Come on.
Well, I've been watching what I eat, and I work out three times a week.
By the way, I heard your son recently graduated.
Yes, my little Paul is finally a doctor.
They grow up so fast, you know.
He is such a handsome guy.
He gets his looks from his mother, of course.
Thank you.
What about your daughter, Pamela?
I heard she passed the bar exam and married recently.
Oh yes, she had a beautiful wedding in Cozumel, Mexico, and we all attended.
Such a lovely girl.
I hope my Paul is lucky enough to find a girl like that someday.
But of course.
Well, it's been great talking to you, but I have to get going.
Same here.
We'll catch up soon, maybe over coffee.
That would be great.
Give me a call.
See you soon.
Bye.
Ugh, I cannot stand that woman or her obnoxious daughter.
Thank you.