The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Short, friendly, unimportant conversations.
Small talk.
You haven't gotten older.
You look young.
You haven't aged a day.
Speak badly of someone without them knowing.
Talk behind someone's back.
Pretend to like someone when you don't.
Be hypocritical.
Two-faced.
Do something unkind to a friend.
Stab someone in the back.
Talk about the details of other people's lives.
Gossip.
I really like the design or change you made.
I love what you have done with.
Do physical exercise.
Work out.
Phrase used to shift to another topic.
By the way.
The exam to qualify as a lawyer.
Bar exam.
Leave.
Get going.
Really annoying.
Obnoxious.
Let's try that faster.
Really annoying.
Obnoxious.
The exam to qualify as a lawyer.
Bar exam.
Speak badly of someone without them knowing.
Talk behind someone's back.
Pretend to like someone when you don't.
Be hypocritical.
Two-faced.
I really like the design or change you made.
I love what you have done with.
Talk about the details of other people's lives.
Gossip.
Do something unkind to a friend.
Stab someone in the back.
Phrase used to shift to another topic.
By the way.
Short, friendly, unimportant conversations.
Small talk.
Do physical exercise.
Work out.
Leave.
Get going.
You haven't gotten older.
You look young.
You haven't aged a day.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I am trying to discover a formula that will prevent me from aging.
You haven't aged a day.
It's inevitable.
Your skin ages quicker when exposed to direct sunlight.
You haven't aged a day.
I don't mind aging.
It's a natural process of life.
Wow, Laura.
This is such a beautiful home.
I didn't study last night and this is such a hard exam.
I hate Luke.
He's such a jerk with people sometimes.
I love what you have done with.
I love what you've done with your room.
It looks great.
I love what you have done with.
I really love what you've done with your hair.
I think green hair is so cool.
I love what you have done with.
Dorothy, I must admit I love what you've done with your office.
It looks so much better this way.
You know what?
I heard that Tom has a new girlfriend.
I heard that you are getting married.
Is that true?
From what I heard, there will be a managerial position open in the company next month.
We discussed the merger plan over lunch this afternoon.
I think the best way to do business is over a nice meal.
Kathy and Richard talked about their wedding plans over a romantic dinner.