The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Get comfortable and feel like you are in your own home.
Make yourselves at home.
Tips, advice, hints.
Pointer.
Refers to liking nice things.
Good taste.
The way something smells.
Aroma.
The way something tastes.
Flavor.
Opposite of sweet.
Bitter.
Faint.
Loose consciousness.
Pass out.
Containing a lot of sugar.
Sweet.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Have a seat.
To add alcohol or drugs to a food or drink.
Spike.
Having an acid taste that is like the taste of a lemon.
Sour.
Only allowing people from a high social class.
Exclusive.
Let's try that faster.
To add alcohol or drugs to a food or drink.
Spike.
Containing a lot of sugar.
Sweet.
Faint.
Loose consciousness.
Pass out.
Only allowing people from a high social class.
Exclusive.
Get comfortable and feel like you are in your own home.
Make yourselves at home.
Tips, advice, hints.
Pointer.
Having an acid taste that is like the taste of a lemon.
Sour.
The way something tastes.
Flavor.
Refers to liking nice things.
Good taste.
The way something smells.
Aroma.
Sit down.
Take a seat.
Have a seat.
Opposite of sweet.
Bitter.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Make yourselves at home.
Come on in.
Sit down.
Make yourself at home.
Make yourselves at home.
You'll get there before me, so just go on in and make yourself at home.
I hope you don't mind, but I just made myself at home.
Pointer.
I'm going to give a presentation tomorrow.
Do you think you can give me a few pointers?
Pointer.
Here, let me give you a few pointers about learning English.
You gave me some great pointers.
They were really helpful.
Aroma.
This coffee has a lovely aroma.
Each morning I was woken up by the aroma of fresh baked bread.
Aroma.
This wine has an aroma almost like grass.
I feel terrible.
I think someone poisoned me.
Many people got sick after something poisoned the water.
The pollution is poisoning the air.
Pass out.
I'm so hungry, I think I'm going to pass out.
After finishing the marathon, she fell to the ground and passed out.
Pass out.
What's happening?
Why am I on the ground?
Did I pass out?