The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Appears or is Seem to be Try very hard Struggle Perfect eyesight Twenty-twenty vision See Make out See faraway things more clearly than things nearby.
Farsighted Have really poor vision As blind as a bat Ability to see things Vision Not clear Blurry Choose Pick out A message written by a doctor that tells people what medicine to take.
Prescription Let's try that faster!
See faraway things more clearly than things nearby.
Farsighted Perfect eyesight Twenty-twenty vision Try very hard Struggle Have really poor vision As blind as a bat See faraway things more clearly than things nearby.
Farsighted Have really poor vision As blind as a bat Appears or is Seem to be Choose Pick out Not clear Blurry See faraway things more clearly than things nearby.
Farsighted Choose Pick out See Make out Perfect eyesight Twenty-twenty vision Not clear Blurry Appears or is Seem to be Have really poor vision As blind as a bat Perfect eyesight Twenty-twenty vision See Make out Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Seem to be Trevor seems to be getting sick.
He has a fever.
Struggle She was struggling to find a new job.
Make out I can't make out what this says.
The writing is too small.
Prescription Here's your prescription.
Make sure you take the right amount of pills every day.
Struggle She was struggling to find a new job.
Make out I can't make out what this says.
The writing is too small.