The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Organization of the business Legal structure To put into effect, carry out To execute Reports on financial stability and profitability Financial analysis Profit made from one's investment Return on one's investment A great deal of trouble, difficulty, nuisance Hassle Let's try that faster Profit made from one's investment Return on one's investment To put into effect, carry out To execute Reports on financial stability and profitability Financial analysis A great deal of trouble, difficulty, nuisance Hassle Organization of the business Legal structure Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Legal structure The legal structure of a business includes proprietorship of the business, whether it be one person, a partnership or a company.
Legal structure Legal structure When he wrote up his executive summary and considered the type of legal structure, he decided that he would need to get liability insurance.
Legal structure Legal structure When they presented their business plan, they highlighted the legal structure of the business, which they considered to be innovative.
To execute To execute Having looked over the business plan one more time, the partners agreed that it was time to execute their plan.
To execute The execution of the new marketing technique would begin in the new year.
To execute The captain of the ship decided that it was time to execute Plan B.
Financial analysis Financial analysis A financial analysis is not only performed when a business is starting up, but also throughout the lifetime of the business.
Financial analysis The management of a business will consult the financial analysis to make sure the business is making profits and all the finances are in place, as well as deciding where to spend money to improve the business.
Financial analysis When the financial analyst presented his financial analysis, he highlighted that the business was making ten times the profits it was making at the same time last year.
Return on one's investment I got a huge return on my investment with that company.
Return on one's investment In my experience, investors are fickle and change loyalties very quickly depending on how often and how much return is made on their investment.
Return on one's investment This company is fast becoming a big name in the industry, so I would suggest investing in them.
It is pretty much guaranteed you will get a good return on your investment.
My boss wants me to take over my co-workers responsibilities on top of my own during her sick leave.
It is going to be such a hassle.
I am going to save myself the hassle of going to court and just pay her the damages.
I hope taking care of my dogs while I am away won't be too much of a hassle for you.