The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A meal that serves as both breakfast and lunch.
Brunch.
To some extent, somewhat, rather, sort of.
Kind of.
A thin, flat cake of batter fried on both sides.
Pancake.
With maximum effort using all one's resources.
To go all out.
A preserve of whole fruit slightly crushed, boiled with sugar.
Jam.
Let's try that faster.
A preserve of whole fruit slightly crushed, boiled with sugar.
Jam.
A thin, flat cake of batter fried on both sides.
Pancake.
With maximum effort using all one's resources.
To go all out.
A meal that serves as both breakfast and lunch.
Brunch.
To some extent, somewhat, rather, sort of.
Kind of.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Brunch.
Every Saturday, my mom prepares a huge brunch for us.
This hotel offers a Sunday brunch buffet from 10am to 2pm.
Brunch.
I always feel very sleepy after I eat a huge brunch.
Kind of.
I kind of feel like going to the movies today.
A raspberry kind of looks like a strawberry, but it tastes very different.
Kind of.
My dad is kind of like a huge teddy bear.
Pancake.
I can make really good pancakes when I use a pancake mix.
But I can't make them from scratch.
Pancake.
Some places call pancakes flapjacks.
I wish I could flip a pancake in the pan just like that chef.
To go all out.
My brother went all out when he planned his girlfriend's birthday party.
They went all out to win the war.
To go all out.
I went all out to finish my project before the weekend.
Jam.
My granny makes her own strawberry jam from scratch and gives us each a jar.
He spread peanut butter and blueberry jam on his toast.
Jam.
The restaurant had about a dozen of flavors of jam in it.
There are two types of jam and marmalade to choose from.