Thank you for coming tonight, Mr.
Weber.
As a teacher, it's great seeing the kid's parents assist our parent-teacher conference night.
Of course.
I'm very interested to know how my child is doing and also get some insight from you as to how he can improve.
Well, Alan is a great student.
He's a hard worker and very well behaved.
However, he does struggle a bit with math.
I guess he gets that from me.
I never did well in math when I was a kid.
What can I do at home to complement what he is learning in the classroom?
Well, it's important that you sit with him and review his homework assignments and help him with math.
I would also recommend he stay after school twice a week for tutoring sessions.
It will really help a lot.
Thanks a lot.
I will definitely do that.
Is there anything else?
Um, yes.
Here's a notice from our financial department.
Seems your child's tuition is overdue.
Oh, yes, I...