EnglishPod.com Oh man, I had the best supper last night.
My wife made a stir-fry and it was amazing.
I love stir-fry.
Crispy bite-sized vegetables covered in a mixture of soy sauce and oyster sauce.
Wilted greens and fresh bean sprouts.
Throw in some onion and garlic and ginger.
Mmm.
It's almost lunch time.
I would die for a plate of stir-fry right now.
Well, you can keep the vegetables.
I'll take the meat.
The stir-fry my wife made was really hearty.
With chunks of beef and slivers of bell peppers and onion.
What?
You call that a stir-fry?
More meat than vegetables?
That's the worst insult you could throw at a Chinese stir-fry.
What a disgrace to the wok she fried it in.
What you had is equivalent to a fajita without the wrap.