EnglishPod.com Okay everyone, shall we begin?
Sorry Maggie, but we're missing a few people.
Can we hang on a sec?
Well, I did say eleven o'clock sharp, and it's now five past, so...
Hi everyone, I'm so sorry I'm late.
It's raining cats and dogs outside, and I had to wait ages for a taxi.
Okay James, take a seat quickly please.
Right, the subject of the meeting is the importance.
Hi guys, please excuse me, I was held up in traffic.
Right, as I was saying the subject of the meeting is...
Hi Maggie, I'm terribly sorry, the traffic is murder out there.
Sit down, Brono!
Okay now, as you're aware, the topic for the meeting is the importance of being punctual.
Who would like to start?