The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning then say the vocabulary word.
Hold on.
Hang on a sec.
Wait for a very long time.
Wait ages.
Stuck.
Hold up.
Very sorry.
I am terribly sorry.
Pardon.
Please excuse me.
Let's try that faster.
Very sorry.
I am terribly sorry.
Wait for a very long time.
Wait ages.
Hold on.
Hang on a sec.
Pardon.
Please excuse me.
Stuck.
Hold up.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Hang on a sec.
Now hang on a sec.
Where does this order button fit into this web page?
Hang on a sec.
I'll talk to you as soon as I've finished my report.
Let's take another look at this.
Wait ages.
It was raining and he waited ages for a taxi.
I waited ages for a hamburger.
I'll never come back to this restaurant again.
Wait ages.
You must have waited ages.
I'm sorry about that.
Hold up.
Don't let me hold you up if you are busy.
We can chat later instead.
Hold up.
They were held up by fog.
Sorry, I was held up by the meeting.
Please excuse me.
I was held up by the train delays.
I have to go to the bathroom.
Please excuse me.
I was stuck in traffic.
I am terribly sorry.
I'm terribly sorry that I messed up your order.
We're terribly sorry that we misprinted your details.
I am terribly sorry.
I am terribly sorry for being late.