The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Tell somebody to stop.
Cut that out.
You must be making jokes with me.
You've got to be kidding me.
Chat.
Shoot the breeze.
Gathered.
Accumulated.
To release excess energy, emotion etc.
Let off steam.
Carry on.
Keep up.
Stop feeling anger and decide to let it go.
Forgive and forget.
Stop fighting.
Call a truce.
Thinking about the feelings of other people.
Considerate.
To eat or drink something noisily.
Slurp.
Let's try that faster.
Stop feeling anger and decide to let it go.
Forgive and forget.
You must be making jokes with me.
You've got to be kidding me.
Tell somebody to stop.
Cut that out.
To release excess energy, emotion etc.
Let off steam.
To eat or drink something noisily.
Slurp.
Stop fighting.
Call a truce.
Chat.
Shoot the breeze.
Thinking about the feelings of other people.
Considerate.
Carry on.
Keep up.
Gathered.
Accumulated.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Cut that out.
Can you cut that damn music out?
It's annoying.
Cut that out.
Hey, cut it out.
You know I'm ticklish.
Cut that out.
Let's cut the funny business out and get back to work.
Slurp.
It's considered rude to slurp your soup.
The dog slurped the whole meal down at once.
Slurp.
He always slurps his coffee.
Let off steam.
You can talk to me anytime if you need to let off steam.
Sometimes exercise is the best way to let off steam.
Let off steam.
Letting off steam is essential for good mental health.
Keep up.
If you keep up the good work, you could get promoted.
This is a horrible paper.
If you keep it up, you will fail the class.
Keep up.
Let's hope this good weather keeps up.
Consider it.
Sending a thank you card is very considerate.
Mary is a caring and considerate person.
Consider it.
It was very considerate of you to offer to help.
Thank you for watching.