Hey, Mary, can you cut that out?
Cut what out?
I'm not doing anything.
The tapping of your pen on your desk?
It's driving me crazy.
Fine.
By the way, would you mind not slurping your coffee every time you have a cup?
I don't slurp my coffee.
And plus, how can you hear it when you're shouting into your phone all the time?
You've got to be kidding me.
You're complaining about me talking on the phone when you go out for a cigarette break ten times a day to shoot the breeze?
Look, we have a lot of accumulated anger from working in these conditions, and it's probably okay to let off steam once in a while.
But it's probably not a good idea to keep it up.
I'm willing to forgive and forget if you are.
Fine.
Let's call a truce.
I'll try to be more considerate and keep the noise down.
Yeah, I'll try to do the same.
So, I was wondering, do you want to go out to dinner Friday night?