The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Have holidays.
Vacation.
Feeling resentment against someone because of that person's rivalry, success, or advantages.
Jealous.
Meet each other.
Catch up.
One of the many levels of a building.
Floor.
Deal with.
Take care.
Phrase of agreement.
For sure.
Let's try that faster.
Deal with.
Take care.
Have holidays.
Vacation.
Meet each other.
Catch up.
Feeling resentment against someone because of that person's rivalry, success, or advantages.
Jealous.
Phrase of agreement.
For sure.
One of the many levels of a building.
Floor.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Catch up.
We haven't seen each other in ages, we really need to catch up.
Next time we catch up, remember to bring the kids.
Catch up.
It's always fun to catch up with mates and watch football.
Jealous.
My brother is jealous because I'm rich and he isn't.
Jealous people can do stupid things.
Jealous.
Everyone is jealous of how beautiful I am.
Vacation.
I really need to go on vacation, I'm too stressed out.
I wish I could go on more vacations, I need more money though.
Vacation.
My boss is always going on vacation, it's not fair.
For sure.
For sure I will go to the movies with you.
Next time let's go to the beach, okay?
For sure.
Do you think it's a good idea to drink all this beer?
For sure, why not?
Floor.
Could you please deliver this package to the boss on the fifth floor please?
I hate living in an apartment building, I have to climb all these floors.
Floor.
I don't want to live on the thirteenth floor, it's unlucky.