EnglishPod.com Hey, Michelle.
Good to see you.
Are you at lunch?
Oh, hi, Jim.
No, I just got back.
I thought you were on vacation now.
No, I wish I was.
I just got back from Spain, actually.
Oh, wonderful.
Have you been there before or was it your first time?
My first time.
I've traveled around Europe a lot, but this is my first time to Spain.
It was amazing and the weather was just beautiful.
No rain and just sun, sun, sun.
I'm so jealous of you.
I've never been anywhere in Europe.
I've always dreamed of traveling around and seeing the sights.
Well, I really recommend Spain.
You really should go.
Anyway, it's been great to catch up, but I must be going.
This is my floor.
Speak again soon, I hope.
For sure.
Take care.