EnglishPod.com Okay, so now the last point on our agenda.
Jill, let's go over the profit and loss statement.
Great!
Well, the main issue here, as you can see, is that our expenses are through the roof.
These numbers are off the charts.
What's going on here?
Well, sir, the company expenditures on entertainment and travel are out of control.
Look at these bills, for example.
Just this month, we've paid over $20,000 for hotel charges.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I'll look into it.
The list goes on and on.
Here, this is a bill for $5,000 for spa treatments.
Thank you.
That will be all.
I'll take care of it.
Look at this one, sir.
$8,000 were expensed in one night at a place called Wild Thing.
Okay, I get it.
Thank you for your very thorough analysis.
Music.