The air conditioning is not working.
We need to call a handyman before we start to fry in here.
Dan is on top of that.
I think they are also getting the handyman to fix the bathroom toilet that keeps clogging up.
That would be convenient.
They might as well ask him to fix the electrical wiring.
The circuit breakers keep going out all the time.
It's really annoying.
Yeah, you're right.
This office is falling apart.
Frank told me the other day that the gutters outside were clogged and that's why the parking lot was flooded.
I know.
I was in ankle-deep water trying to get to my car that day.
The handyman definitely has his work cut out for him.