The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
air conditioning handyman on top of that clog up wiring fall apart gutter let's try that faster air conditioning gutter on top of that clog up fall apart handyman wiring Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
handyman My dad is a handyman.
He can fix anything around the house.
handyman The handyman came in yesterday to fix the leaking roof, and he also replaced the leaking faucet.
handyman We should call in a handyman to fix the broken door and replace the broken window.
on top of that I have so much work this week.
I have two separate projects due on Friday.
A proposal to write, an interview to do, and on top of that I have to make a presentation to my boss.
on top of that on top of that Sarah must be really stressed.
She's taking classes at NYU, working two jobs, and on top of that, she still has to take care of her parents.
on top of that on top of that Kevin is so sweet.
For our anniversary, he took me to a surprise dinner, gave me a bottle of my favorite perfume, and on top of that, bought me a hundred roses.
The sink will clog up if you keep on dumping your food in there.
The streets are clogged up with traffic every morning and evening.
I am going to Walmart to buy something to fix that clogged drain.
I am free any day of the week, so you can come in whenever it's convenient for you.
Ever since they opened the new shopping mall down the street, it's become very convenient for me to buy clothes.
Would it be convenient for you to pick up some bananas on the way home?
If you're going to come to Shanghai, you might as well go see the expo.
I am going to the convenience store, so I might as well get some dinner.
Jennifer and Janice wear the same kinds of clothes, like the same bands, and even eat the same things.
They might as well be twins.
Thanks for watching!