The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Give good wishes to something or someone.
Bless Live Abide You.
Old use or formal use?
The Get married, old use or formal use?
Wed Something that represents a certain idea.
Symbol Little finger Pinky The finger beside the thumb.
Index finger The short, thick finger on the side of a hand.
Thumb The finger which is in the middle of the five.
Middle finger The finger between the middle finger and the little finger.
Ring finger Ring you receive when you get married.
Wedding band The fingers on the feet.
Toe Smallest finger on your hand, synonym for pinky.
Baby finger A ring a man gives to his girlfriend when he asks her to marry him.
Engagement ring The hard part at the end of your finger that keeps growing.
Fingernail Let's try that faster.
The finger between the middle finger and the little finger.
Ring finger Give good wishes to something or someone.
Bless A ring a man gives to his girlfriend when he asks her to marry him.
Engagement ring Smallest finger on your hand, synonym for pinky.
Baby finger Something that represents a certain idea.
Symbol The fingers on the feet.
Toe Old use or formal use The Live Little finger Pinky Get married, old use or formal use Wed Ring you receive when you get married.
Wedding band The finger which is in the middle of the five.
Middle finger The finger beside the thumb.
Index finger The hard part at the end of your finger that keeps growing.
Fingernail The short, thick finger on the side of a hand.
Thumb Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Abide People in this country all abide in peace and happiness.
Abide Do you abide in your own house now?
Abide You must abide by the law or we will take you to prison.
Raising a child is a big commitment.
She isn't ready to make a life-long commitment to her boyfriend.
Are you afraid of making a commitment?
Pinky She was cutting some vegetables and she cut her pinky.
Pinky Pinky rings are really popular these days.
Pinky She slipped the ring onto her pinky.
Index finger Don't point at me with your index finger.
Index finger Some people think that the longer your index finger, the more success you will have in life.
Index finger Ring finger I lost my left index finger in a car accident.
Ring finger Do you see the diamond ring on her ring finger?
Ring finger The wedding ring doesn't go on the index finger.
It goes on the ring finger.
Ring finger Please fit the ring to the exact size of my ring finger.