EnglishPod.com I hate working on Christmas Eve.
Whoa, get a load of this guy.
Come in Central.
I think we got ourselves a situation here.
License and registration, please.
Have you been drinking tonight, sir?
I had one or two glasses of eggnog, but nothing else.
Step out of the vehicle, please.
Sir, what do you have in the back?
Just a few Christmas gifts.
Tis the season, after all.
Don't take that tone with me.
Do you have an invoice for these items?
Oh, no.
I make these in my workshop in the North Pole.
You are under arrest, sir.
You have the right to remain silent.
You better not pout.
You better not cry.
Anything you say can and will be used against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can't afford one, the state will appoint one for you.
Do you understand these rights that have just been read to you?
You can't take me to jail.
What about my sleigh?
It's Christmas Eve.
I have presents to deliver.
Rudolph, Prancer, Dancer, get help!