The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Look at, informal.
Get a load of.
Official document that shows you have permission to drive a car.
License.
Traditional Christmas drink containing eggs, cream, sugar, and rum.
Eggnog.
Machine used to carry people, i.e.
a car or truck.
Vehicle.
Briefly go out of a place.
Step out.
Speak in that tone of voice.
Take that tone.
Official document that shows you have paid for something you bought.
Invoice.
The act of legally taking someone to jail.
Arrest.
Push out your lips to show that you are unhappy.
Pout.
Large, open vehicle that is pulled by horses over snow or ice.
A set of two metal rings that are used to join a person's hands together, especially by police.
Handcuffs.
A building where criminals are kept as punishment.
Prison.
Tell someone their legal rights, especially when they are arrested.
Read someone's rights.
Driving under the influence of alcohol or drugs.
DUI.
A piece of paper the police give you if you are driving too fast.
Speeding ticket.
Let's try that faster.
Speak in that tone of voice.
Take that tone.
Traditional Christmas drink containing eggs, cream, sugar and rum.
Eggnog.
A piece of paper the police give you if you are driving too fast.
Speeding ticket.
Large, open vehicle that is pulled by horses over snow or ice.
Slay.
A set of two metal rings that are used to join a person's hands together, especially by police.
Handcuffs.
Briefly go out of a place.
Step out.
Official document that shows you have permission to drive a car.
License.
The act of legally taking someone to jail.
Arrest.
A building where criminals are kept as punishment.
Prison.
Tell someone their legal rights, especially when they are arrested.
Read someone's rights.
Look at.
Informal.
Get a load of.
Machine used to carry people, i.e.
a car or truck.
Vehicle.
Push out your lips to show that you are unhappy.
Pout.
Driving under the influence of alcohol or drugs.
DUI.
Official document that shows you have paid for something you bought.
Invoice.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
License.
I can't drive your car.
I don't have a driver's license.
License.
Finally, I pass my driving test and I got my license.
If you get a speeding ticket, you have to show the police officer your driving license.
Step out.
Please step out of your car.
I just stepped out of the office to get a coffee.
Step out.
Please.
Will you step out in the hall for a moment?
I need to talk to you.
Vehicle.
Four vehicles were involved in the car accident.
There are a lot of vehicles on the road today.
Vehicle.
If more people drove electric vehicles, there would be less pollution.
Take that tone.
When you take that tone, I feel upset.
Don't take that tone with me.
I'm your boss.
Take that tone.
I couldn't believe he took that tone with her.
It was so rude.
Arrest.
After the riot, 75 people were taken under arrest.
John Doe is under arrest for armed robbery.
Arrest.
If you commit a crime, you will be taken under arrest.
Pout.
She started to pout, then began to cry.
Come on.
Don't pout.
Put a smile on your face.
Pout.
You've been pouting all day.
Is something wrong?
Thank you.