EnglishPod.com Now, a key question you might ask yourself is what differentiates the new X420 line with our previous models?
And also, of course, with some of our competitors.
In other words, what makes the X420 stand out from all the others?
This is a key question and is something I'd like to explore in a little depth.
Firstly, the X420 has a range of USPs that really make it a cut above the rest.
The first thing to mention is that the X420 is the first in a new generation of ultra-light laptop computers.
It is only two pounds, which compares very favorably with all our key competitors.
In terms of computer performance, for such a light machine, it's very powerful.
Four gigabytes of RAM with an ultra-fast processor.
The most advanced video and sound cards on the market are installed with a crystal clear 15 inch LCD display.
The X420 really stands out as a next generation laptop.
Compared with our previous X540 range, it really is in a league of its own.
Now, if we go on to look at projected sales for the X420, we can see that sales revenue for 2010 is expected to hit at least $20 million.
Now, this is really a conservative estimate.
If our marketing campaign is successful, I'm confident that we could see a doubling of this figure at the very least.
Now, please bear in mind that this is only for the first year of production.
I'm certain that in the coming three years, the X420 will actually overtake all our existing products, both in terms of sales and revenue.
Okay, now let's move on to discuss our marketing concept and look more closely at our key competitors.