EnglishPod.com I will come clean as soon as we get to safety, okay?
For now, you have to trust me.
Please, I would never do anything to hurt you.
Steven, I- Okay, run!
Steven!
I haven't been completely honest with you, Veronica.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a fireman.
I'm not even from the United States.
I'm a spy for the Indian government.
What?
Why didn't you tell me before?
What are you doing here?
When I was a young boy, I used to play cricket with my father back in my hometown of Hyderabad.
It was a peaceful town, and my father was a renowned chemist.
One day, he was approached by members of the CIA, claiming that my father had made the discovery of the millennium in his small lab back at the university, where he taught biochemistry.
I never saw him again.
I vowed to discover the whereabouts of my father, and consequently joined the Indian Intelligence Bureau.
What does that have to do with those men shooting at us?
And most importantly, why did you lie to me?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't supposed to meet you.
I wasn't supposed to fall in love with you.
But you have to believe me when I tell you that what I feel for you is real.
I can't believe this.
Why are all these things happening to me?
I can't take it anymore.
Let me out of the car!
Veronica, wait!