The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Happening Go on Confess.
Tell everything.
Tell the truth.
Come clean Truthful and moral in behavior.
Trustworthy Honest A person employed to find out secret information about other countries or organizations.
Spy Well-known Renowned To assert as a fact Claim 1000 years Millennium Promised Vow The approximate place where a person or thing is.
Whereabouts Well-known for some bad reason Notorious Done or acting in secret Undercover Federal Bureau of Investigation FBI An unimportant small lie White lie Tell false information to for fun Pull someone's leg Let's try that faster An unimportant small lie White lie Well-known Renowned 1000 years Millennium Well-known for some bad reason Notorious Tell false information to for fun Pull someone's leg Truthful and moral in behavior.
Trustworthy Honest Federal Bureau of Investigation FBI A person employed to find out secret information about other countries or organizations.
Spy The approximate place where a person or thing is.
Whereabouts Done or acting in secret Undercover Promised Vow To assert as a fact Claim Happening Go on Confess.
Tell everything.
Tell the truth.
Come clean Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Come clean The murderer came clean and confessed everything to the police.
Come clean Carl's teacher caught him cheating on his exam and so he had to come clean with the principal.
Come clean I decided to come clean with my parents and tell them that I quit school.
Renowned This is a restaurant renowned for its fine wine.
They have over 200 wines from all over the world.
Renowned Stephen Hawking is a world renowned physicist who has done extensive research on black holes.
Renowned I had dinner with a renowned photographer from the National Geographic.
Claim Carl, there's a boy outside claiming to be your son.
Claim The World Wildlife Federation claims there are less than 430 Siberian tigers left in the world.
Claim Santa Claus There is a drunk man outside the school claiming he is Santa Claus.
Max wasn't supposed to know about his surprise birthday party.
You ruined the surprise.
Claim I wasn't supposed to study architecture.
I accidentally chose it on my registration form.
You are not supposed to be here.
Your classroom is down the hall.
Doris is always complaining about her boyfriend.
I can't take it anymore.
Children, please be quiet.
Tomorrow I'm going to quit my job.