EnglishPod.com Hey, you're early.
Where is everyone?
Well, I told them not to come.
I made a reservation just for the two of us.
I thought we could have a quiet evening all to ourselves.
Oh, why?
Jennifer, there's something I want to ask you.
Sure, what is it?
Okay, here's the thing.
I've always seen you as more than just a friend, and I can't take it anymore.
I know you better than anyone.
I know the pros and cons of your personality.
I even know what side of the bed is yours.
I think we would be great together, don't you?
Are you serious?
We've been friends for years.
We can't just change that overnight.
I know.
I never had the guts to tell you.
Until today.
So what do you say?
Are you willing to give me a shot?
Ah.