The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
You and me Two of us Just for us and no one else All to ourselves Phrase used to begin explaining a situation or problem Here's the thing Good things and bad things about a person Pros and cons Courage, brave Guts To let someone have a try Give someone a shot Phrase used to indicate that you are dating someone Going out To become someone's boyfriend or girlfriend Get with To ask someone to join you on a romantic date Ask out Having a very close relationship, very warm and friendly Intimate To kiss Make out Let's try that faster You and me Two of us Phrase used to indicate that you are dating someone Going out Having a very close relationship, very warm and friendly Intimate To ask someone to join you on a romantic date Ask out Good things and bad things about a person Pros and cons To let someone have a try Give someone a shot Phrase used to begin explaining a situation or problem Here's the thing Courage, brave Guts To kiss Make out Just for us and no one else All to ourselves To become someone's boyfriend or girlfriend Get with Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Good evening sir, do you have a reservation?
Hi, I'm calling to make a dinner reservation I have a reservation for a group of four The man next door is so loud, I can't take it anymore My boss always yells at me I can't take it anymore, I'm going to quit I couldn't take her complaining anymore, so I broke up with her Are you serious?
Why do you suddenly want to move out?
You're getting married?
Are you serious?
He said he loves you?
Guts I don't have the guts to go skydiving Guts I don't have the guts to give a speech Guts I never had the guts to say no to my boss What do you say we go for dinner?
Let's move to Hawaii, what do you say?
So, what do you say?
Will you come?