EnglishPod.com Hey John, I haven't seen you in ages.
What's new?
What have you been up to?
Pete, nice to see you.
Well, on top of the norm, you know, life and kids and work, I've actually gotten into doing some trading.
Trading?
You a big guy?
What are you trading?
Currencies.
Currencies?
As in euros, dollars, pounds and rupees?
It's called Forex, foreign exchange.
The great thing about it is that I don't have to invest a huge amount.
I put in a margin deposit and then I can buy and sell up to a hundred times that much.
I don't understand.
You're buying and selling money?
You got it.
Just last night I made 150 US dollars.
Last night?
Yeah, it's a 24-hour market.
I had bought some RMB earlier at a low asking price, but last night it appreciated drastically.
So I made a split-second decision and sold all of my RMB at an amazing bid.
I've also done some trading with Swiss francs and Australian dollars and Hong Kong dollars.
I've made some good profits, but I've also suffered some losses.
Depends on a lot of factors, just like any other market.
In total, I've made about 500 US dollars in the past few months.
You're kidding!
I'm on.
Where do I sign up?