The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something is usual or expected.
Norm The money that a country uses.
Currency The sum of money required to reinstate.
Margin deposit Taking effect rapidly.
Drastically Very quickly, just a second.
Split second An offer to pay a particular amount of money.
Bid Let's try that faster.
The sum of money required to reinstate.
Margin deposit Something is usual or expected.
Norm Very quickly, just a second.
Split second An offer to pay a particular amount of money.
Bid Taking effect rapidly.
Drastically Currency Norm Norm What's the norm in this company concerning protocol?
Norm This is the norm so you'd better get used to it.
Norm Delivery McDonald's and street vendors are the norms around here.
Currency Before I went to France, I had to change some of my Canadian currency into Euros.
Currency What's the currency in this country?
Currency My country's currency is worth next to nothing in USD.
Margin deposit He decided to start with a margin deposit of GBP 100.
Margin deposit I can't believe that I can trade with USD 1 million deposit when I've only put in a margin deposit of USD 10,000.
Margin deposit Margin deposit One has to be careful with trading using a margin deposit because the risk of losing more money than one has are high.
Split second The gang members were closing in on me fast so I made a split second decision to run instead of fight.
Split second My heart pounded as I made a split second decision and took hold of her hand.
My split second decision to try a trick on my bicycle in order to impress my friends didn't end well.
Bid The current bid ask for EUR USD is 1.3998-79 Bid Bid I bought EUR at an ask of 1.4235 dollars and sold British Ponds at a bid of 1.5001 dollars.
Bid Bid Bid The bid for Japanese Yen and the ask for Hong Kong dollars are really good right now if you trade in US currency.