The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To change the color of something such as hair or clothing.
Dye Place with washing machines and dryers, usually coin-operated and self-service.
Laundromat A machine Contraction To press and smooth clothes with a heated iron.
Iron To accomplish the desired task.
Do the trick To stiffen clothes with a chemical compound.
Starch Ready, prepared All set A cord, rope or wire on which clothes may be hung to dry or air.
Clothesline A way to clean clothes without water.
Dry clean Basket or space where dirty clothes are put.
Clothes hamper Let's try that faster!
A way to clean clothes without water.
Dry clean A cord, rope or wire on which clothes may be hung to dry or air.
Clothesline To change the color of something such as hair or clothing.
Dye Basket or space where dirty clothes are put.
Clothes hamper A machine Contraction To press and smooth clothes with a heated iron.
Iron Ready, prepared All set To accomplish the desired task.
Do the trick Place with washing machines and dryers, usually coin operated and self service.
Laundromat To stiffen clothes with a chemical compound.
Starch Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Dye Nicole goes to the beauty salon every three months to get her hair dyed.
Dye My friend likes to dye her t-shirts different colors.
They look really nice.
Dye Why did you dye your hair green?
Contraction He tried to fly over the Atlantic in a homemade contraption.
Contraption What does this contraption do?
Contraption Leonardo da Vinci was a great inventor that designed many different contraptions.
Do the trick If we use a piece of cork it might stop the leaking and do the trick.
Do the trick The soup is too salty so I added some potatoes which did the trick.
Do the trick If the sauce tastes a bit sour, add a teaspoon of sugar.
That should do the trick.
All set All set All set.
I finished doing all the laundry.
All set We have our luggage and passport so we are all set to go to the airport.
All set The preparations for the wedding are all set.
Dry clean If you want to remove that stain, you need to have that dry cleaned.
Dry clean I try and avoid having my clothes dry cleaned.
It's too expensive.
Dry clean Dry clean I took my favorite leather jacket to the dry cleaners and they lost it.