The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
In a difficult situation.
Fall on hard times.
People who need practical or emotional support.
Needy.
Almost not.
Hardly.
Willing to give away one's money, time, etc.
Generous.
Set to work vigorously.
Pitch in.
Let's try that faster.
Give something for free to a good cause.
Donate.
Willing to give away one's money, time, etc.
Generous.
Almost not.
Hardly.
Set to work vigorously.
Pitch in.
Willing to give away one's money, time, etc.
Generous.
Be in a difficult situation.
Fall on hard times.
People who need practical or emotional support.
Needy.
Set to work vigorously.
Pitch in.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Donate.
Every week I donate four hours of my time to play with the kids at the orphanage.
Can you donate some of your time to help us out at the soup kitchen?
Donate.
We have many volunteers who regularly donate their time to talk with the elderly in the nursing home.
Generous.
They gave a generous donation to the organization.
This restaurant is very generous with their portion sizes.
Generous.
He is known to be a generous person.
Fall on hard times.
I talked with several homeless people and most of them are on the street because they fell on hard times.
My friend has fallen on hard times and has to sell her house.
Fall on hard times.
I hope we won't fall on hard times during this economic crisis.
Needy.
The needy are numerous in this city.
We need to help the needy in our country.
Needy.
There are many needy people in my city.
Hardly.
I make hardly enough money to feed my family.
You are hardly in need of another pair of shoes.
Hardly.
With five kids, I hardly get any peace and quiet.