Thanks a lot for pitching in once again, Judy.
We really appreciate your help.
It seems that at this time of year, there are more and more people who are struggling to make ends meet.
There aren't many professional chefs like you who are so generous with their time.
Don't be silly, Mark.
I'm more than happy to donate my time to a good cause.
Volunteering at the soup kitchen has been really rewarding for me.
You know, it's satisfying to provide good meals for those who are less fortunate.
I feel like I'm really making a difference in some small way.
Well, your skills are definitely appreciated here.
The people who come here have fallen on hard times, and a delicious hot meal can really bolster their spirits.
Wow, that smells great.
The needy are sure lucky to have you.
Thanks, Mark.
Here you go.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you, my dear.
Oh, this looks lovely.
You're welcome.
Hello, sir.
Today, we have George.
What are you doing here?
Hey, Judy.
I'll have a little of everything.
Thanks.
Smells great.
George, seriously, what are you doing here?
I haven't seen you since our divorce was finalized.
You've got no right to be here.
You're hardly homeless.
Don't be like that, Judy.
I really miss your home cooking.