The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Rural, country, or jungle.
Boonies.
Keep in existence and maintain.
Sustainability.
Sudden and severe.
Drastic.
Capable of being done with means at hand.
Feasible.
Add new parts.
Refit.
Prepare and equip for additional use.
Available source of wealth.
Resource.
Share the car with others to work.
Carpool.
Let's try that faster.
Sudden and severe.
Drastic.
Capable of being done with means at hand.
Feasible.
Maintain in safety from injury, peril, or harm.
Preserve.
Prepare and equip for additional use.
Refit.
Unintelligible or incomprehensible language.
Mumbo jumbo.
Share the car with others to work.
Carpool.
Rural, country, or jungle.
Boonies.
Keep in existence and maintain.
Sustainability.
Available source of wealth.
Resource.
Gain heat or get hot.
Heat up.
Add new parts.
Refit.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Mumbo jumbo.
That's a load of mumbo jumbo.
There is no such thing as aliens.
Mumbo jumbo.
That's a bunch of mumbo jumbo.
You guys like each other and get along well together so you should at least try one date.
Mumbo jumbo.
Some people say that what the Bible teaches is a bunch of mumbo jumbo but I think there is some truth to it.
Preserve.
By living responsibly we can preserve our planet for generations to come.
If you don't start preserving your relationship with your sister now I'm afraid it will only get worse.
Preserve.
This historical building has been preserved since the 19th century.
Refit.
My sister had her living room refitted with a new entertainment system.
The mountain climbers arrived at the base camp, got refitted and set off again the next morning.
Refit.
For my birthday my wife surprised me by refitting my car with a leather interior.
Sustainability.
Sustainability consists of living one's life in a way that sustains the earth.
Sustainability is starting to catch on and many companies are finding greener ways to make their products.
Sustainability.
This store is all about sustainability.
They sell clothes made from organic materials, purses made from recycled aluminum and plastic, as well as notebooks made with recycled paper.
Resource.
We need to start finding alternative energy sources because our resources of carbon and oil are limited.
The way we are living is rapidly depleting many of our natural resources.
Resource.
Solar electrical device connected solar cells and wind turbines are becoming more and more common because they are renewable resources in order to produce electricity.