So, what's your guys' take on all this global warming hysteria in the media?
It's pretty serious, man.
There have been tons of scientific studies and the scientific community says that the Earth is heating up.
We need to make some drastic changes to our lifestyle if we want to preserve our planet.
I don't know.
It sounds like a bunch of mumbo jumbo if you ask me.
Well, I don't really know if I believe in global warming either or whether or not it was our doing or natural change the Earth is going through.
But you have to admit that we're living pretty irresponsibly here in the West.
I guess.
I think the issue at hand is sustainability.
We've only got this one Earth we can live on and our resources are quickly disappearing because of our own carelessness and our inability to think of anyone but ourselves and anything but the present.
So like I was saying, we need to change the way we live.
We need to reduce our carbon footprint.
But it doesn't have to be that drastic.
Hybrid vehicles and solar panels are too expensive to be feasible right now and we don't have to be hippies living off the land and buying everything organic either, though it helps.
I carpool to work every day with some buddies of mine.
I have a rain barrel outside my house I used to water my plants and my lawn in the summer and I make sure I always bring reusable bags with me when I get my groceries.
And we just started using biodegradable plastic made from corn oil for takeout orders at my family's restaurant.
Remember the three R's?
Reduce, reuse, recycle.
Exactly.
It's just small simple changes.
Like buying energy-saving light bulbs, starting a compost bin, recycling bottles and papers, using reusable water bottles, stop using disposable cups and cutlery.
Like the ones we're drinking out of?
Yeah.