EnglishPod.com Now that we've been over the gory details of our disastrous first quarter, Ed, give us some good news.
How are things looking for us in terms of sales this month?
Well, would you like the bad news first or the really bad news?
What?
Ed, don't tell me you only have bad news.
Well, sir, our sales have dropped.
No plunged.
50% in the past month alone.
We are currently overstocked and overstaffed and our profits are falling fast.
The market is in recession and we have no way of moving our inventory or getting rid of our staff.
If we consider redundancies, it would cost us a fortune because of the new regulations governing compensation packages.
It's a real mess.
You're crying out loud.
How fast are we losing money?
Um, um, how can I put this?
Let's just say that at this pace, we will be filing for Chapter 11 in less than three months.
What?
Jeez, how could this have happened?
So what's the bad news?
Oh, that's the really bad news.
Our supplier suffered QC problems and, well, half of our production is faulty.
We're going to have to recall all items sold in the last quarter and the worst part, we're going to have to shoulder this cost.
Are you joking?
Get the supplier on the line now.
They have to assume the cost of this mess.
We tried that, sir.
The factory has gone under and the owner apparently has fled the country.
Well, we're doomed.
There's some really good news, though.
Really?
What?
I got offered a new job.