The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The minimum return below which an enterprise becomes unprofitable.
Margin The entire amount of income before any deductions are made.
Revenue Having no money.
Informal Broke The lowest possible level or absolute bottom Hit rock bottom Cause to rise rapidly and suddenly Sky rocket All the small details Gory details Tell me the bad news Lay it on me Drop down suddenly and quickly Plunge Very bad.
Having bad results Disastrous Regarding.
About In terms of Having too many things to sell To be overstocked Have too many employees Be overstaffed The amount of products you have to sell Inventory Remove or take away something that is annoying Get rid of Layoffs.
Ending employment of staff for money reasons Redundancies Be responsible for the cost Shoulder the cost Rule Govern Use to express anger or annoyance For crying out loud Bankruptcy.
Owing more money than you can pay Chapter 11 The process of controlling the quality of production Quality control Quality control.
Let's try that faster Regarding.
About In terms of Tell me the bad news Lay it on me Having too many things to sell To be overstocked Use to express anger or annoyance For crying out loud Rule The amount of products you have to sell Inventory The process of controlling the quality of production Quality control The entire amount of income before any deductions are made All the small details Layoffs.
Ending employment of staff for money reasons Redundancies Remove or take away something that is annoying Get rid of Cause to rise rapidly and suddenly Sky rocket Very bad.
Having bad results Disastrous Having no money.
Informal Broke Be responsible for the cost Shoulder the cost The lowest possible level or absolute bottom Hit rock bottom bankruptcy.
Owing more money than you can pay Chapter 11 Have too many employees Be overstaffed The minimum return below which an enterprise becomes unprofitable Margin Drop down suddenly and quickly Plunge Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Gory details Without going too much into the gory details of the current economy, you should know that we expect business to slow down in the next few months Gory details Spare me the gory details How are we going to survive this financial crisis?
Gory details Tell me all about your pregnancy.
Sparing me the gory details, of course We need to protect the environment.
Therefore, there will be new policies governing corporate levels of pollution starting next month I don't agree with the regulations governing income taxes People shouldn't have to give away their hard-earned money The lack of regulations governing city transportation has led to many traffic accidents Our insurance for a financial crisis expired six months ago, so we are going to have to shoulder the cost of this loss We are going to have to shoulder the majority of the costs for this project Many of our investors pulled out You are going to have to shoulder the costs if you break that vase For crying out loud, when I tell you to have the report done by Wednesday, that means I expect it to be on my desk by the end of the day We've got to figure out a new marketing strategy for crying out loud For crying out loud For crying out loud You just got your driving license and you already got in an accident?