The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A greeting phrase used after two friends have not seen each other in a while.
Long time no see.
Nothing new.
Same old, same old.
New position.
Promotion.
Meeting new people.
Networking.
Leave here.
Split.
Let's try that faster.
Nothing new.
Same old, same old.
Leave here.
Split.
Meeting new people.
Networking.
A greeting phrase used after two friends have not seen each other in a while.
Long time no see.
New position.
Promotion.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Long time no see.
Hey, long time no see, I've missed you.
Long time no see, I thought you would never come back.
Long time no see.
My old uncle, long time no see.
Promotion.
After putting a consistent effort at work, he was awarded with a promotion.
Now that my friend got a promotion, he can afford to buy that new car.
Promotion.
He was not awarded a promotion because of his unruly behaviour at the staff Christmas party.
Same old, same old.
How have you been?
And you?
Same old, same old.
How is the report going?
Same old.
I can't seem to think of anything new.
Same old, same old.
My father has been same old, same old.
Still doing nothing but playing poker.
Networking.
I think I'll go to that networking event tonight.
Maybe I'll land a job.
Networking.
You should try networking online by using a site such as LinkedIn.
I think the most important thing when networking is confidence and a business card.
Split.
After five months together, I decided to split with my boyfriend.
I decided to split with my business partner to start my own venture.
Split.
If you don't treating me properly, we will split and you'll never see me again.