EnglishPod.com Have you seen this news article?
Apparently, an organization has made a list to name the new seven wonders of the world and people could vote for them online.
Wow, that's really interesting.
So, who won?
Well, the Great Wall of China, the Taj Mahal in India.
I've been there.
It really is an amazing work of architecture and art.
The entire complex is made of white marble and in the interior of the tomb, the walls are covered with gems and emeralds.
Cool.
Also amongst the winners is Petra in Jordan, Machu Picchu in Peru, and the Pyramid in Chichen Itza in Mexico.
Wait a minute.
It also says that the Christ Redeemer statue in Brazil and the Colosseum in Rome are wonders.
I would love to go to Italy and see the Colosseum.
Stay in the middle like a gladiator.
Well, let's see if we can find some cheap airfare and we can go towards the end of the year.
Good idea.