The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A mausoleum located in India, made entirely of white marble.
Taj Mahal An extensive wall in China that kept invaders at bay.
Great Wall The art and science of designing buildings.
Architecture A historical city in Jordan which was carved out of the mountain.
Petra An ancient Incan city set high in the Andes Mountains in Peru.
Machu Picchu A structure where the outer surfaces are triangular and converge at a point.
Pyramid An ancient amphitheater located in Rome.
Colosseum A monumental human creation that is amazing.
Wonder A person trained to entertain the public by engaging in mortal combat.
Gladiator A grave or other place of burial.
Tomb Let's try that faster.
The art and science of designing buildings.
Architecture A person trained to entertain the public by engaging in mortal combat.
Gladiator A structure where the outer surfaces are triangular and converge at a point.
Pyramid An ancient amphitheater located in Rome.
Colosseum An extensive wall in China that kept invaders at bay.
Great Wall A historical city in Jordan which was carved out of the mountain.
Petra A mausoleum located in India made entirely of white marble.
Taj Mahal An ancient Incan city set high in the Andes Mountains in Peru.
Machu Picchu A grave or other place of burial.
Tomb A monumental human creation that is amazing.
Wonder Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Architecture The architecture of this town is very bizarre.
Architecture I wish my city was designed better.
The architecture looks like it comes from outer space.
Architecture Architecture My friend wanted his new house to have architecture like that of Japan.
Tomb When the king died he left all his treasure in the tomb.
Tomb His tomb is so big that you could fit a bus in there.
Tomb If anyone breaks into a tomb they will have a curse put upon them.
Wonder Wonder I think the temples of Angkor Wat should be considered as one of the wonders of the world.
Wonder My dream is to visit all the wonders of the world before I die.
Wonder The only surviving wonder of the ancient world is the Pyramid of Giza.
Pyramid This building complex is very big.
Pyramid The temple complex of Angkor Wat has over a dozen temples.
Pyramid They are building a new housing complex next to my office.
Great Wall The prize is round-trip airfare to a destination of your choice.
Great Wall Airfare is set to increase with the higher cost of fuel.
Great Wall The UK has one of the highest airfare taxes in all of Europe.