The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A greeting phrase.
How are you?
An informal way of calling a person.
Man.
Long time, no see.
For a long time.
In ages.
A phrase you use to respond to a greeting.
I am doing great.
Meeting someone accidentally.
Run into.
Learn about recent past events.
Catch up on.
Show a lot of emotion but not be able to control emotions.
Freak out.
Screaming in a very high voice.
Shriek.
Look at something for a long time with great attention.
Stare.
Very amusing.
Hilarious.
Lose control of your emotions.
Show strong negative emotions.
Lose it.
Go crazy, lose control of yourself.
Go nuts.
A very fun time or a funny event.
A riot.
Very silly or unreasonable.
Ridiculous.
Very strange or unusual.
Bizarre.
A short, amusing story.
Anecdote.
Let's try that faster.
Learn about recent past events.
Catch up on.
Look at something for a long time with great attention.
Stare.
Very silly or unreasonable.
Ridiculous.
Meeting someone accidentally.
Run into.
A short, amusing story.
Anecdote.
A phrase you use to respond to a greeting.
I am doing great.
A greeting phrase.
How are you?
An informal way of calling a person.
Man.
A very fun time or a funny event.
A riot.
Show a lot of emotion but not be able to control emotions.
Freak out.
Screaming in a very high voice.
Shriek.
Very strange or unusual.
Bizarre.
Lose control of your emotions.
Show strong negative emotions.
Lose it.
For a long time.
In ages.
Very amusing.
Hilarious.
Long time, no see.
Go crazy.
Lose control of yourself.
Go nuts.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I've been waiting here for ages.
It's been ages since I saw you.
I lived in France ages ago.
Lose it.
When I told my boss that I would be late, he totally lost it.
If you do that one more time, I'm going to lose it.
Lose it.
I found out that the flight was cancelled and I started crying.
I completely lost it.
Freak out.
Oh my gosh, I'm going to meet Justin Timberlake.
I'm totally freaking out.
Freak out.
Why did you freak out when I told you I'd be late for dinner?
Don't freak out.
We can solve this problem in five minutes.
Run into.
I have not seen Sally for five years.
Then I ran into her at the park.
Run into.
I'm sure we'll run into each other next week.
If you run into Tom, don't tell him that you know me.
Stare.
I know that dog has three legs, but stop staring at him.
The painting is so beautiful, I could stare at it for hours.
Stare.
He stared into my eyes and then told me he loves me.