The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Call someone to feel admiration.
Impress A general description A brief overview To calm down Settle down Hand in Pass on Feel relaxed Feel free Let's try that faster Hand in Pass on A general description A brief overview Feel relaxed Feel free To calm down Settle down Call someone to feel admiration Impress Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
A brief overview George, would you give us a brief overview of what the marketing team has been working on this week?
A brief overview This guidebook doesn't have a lot of detailed information about Paris, it just provides a brief overview.
A brief overview A brief overview Before we talk about the specific job description, let me give you a brief overview of what we do here at ABC Corporation.
Impress Well, Jeff, I'm really impressed with your photography skills.
These pictures are beautiful.
Impress On my first trip to Hong Kong, I was really impressed with the efficiency of the subway system.
Impress Good job with that sales meeting, Ellen.
I think the client was really impressed.
Pass on We're all going to the Sichuan restaurant for lunch.
Pass it on.
We want to have a large group.
Pass on Linda, after you add the most recent QC figures to the report, please pass it on to Mr.
Wang.
Pass on Thanks for your feedback.
I'll pass your suggestions on to the design team.
Feel free Excuse me, may I use your bathroom?
Oh please, feel free.
Feel free Welcome to our art gallery.
Feel free to look around.
Feel free Thank you After listening to this EnglishPod lesson, please feel free to post your questions and comments on our website.
Settle down Children, children, settle down please.
It's time to begin class.
Settle down He was something of a playboy in the past, but now he's ready to get married and settle down.
Settle down After living in the city so long, I'd really like to settle down in a small town.