EnglishPod.com Now, Miss Child's passed on your resume to me and I've had a chance to look it over.
I must say, I'm quite impressed.
Thank you very much.
I've tried to keep it short and clear.
If there are any questions, please feel free to ask me.
Well, yes, I do have a number of questions, but perhaps first you could give me a brief overview.
I'd like to get a little bit of an idea of your background.
Yes, of course.
Well, as you can see from the resume, I'm 27 and grew up in Brooklyn, New York, although our family moved to London when I was quite young, at around 16.
Ah, I see.
So you were actually educated in Europe.
Yes, precisely.
Although I was born in the US, I would definitely call London home.
But as you see, I've actually spent a lot of my life moving from country to country.
My father was in the oil business before he retired, so we also spent a number of years in Saudi Arabia, too.
Very interesting.
So it seems you had quite an adventurous childhood.
Absolutely.
We were never still for too long, but now I'm really looking to settle down.
I see.
Okay, well, let's move on to discuss your education, shall we?
Sure.