The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A meal cooked out of doors over an open fire.
Barbecue Be soaked in marinade.
Marinate A group of twelve.
Dozen Pieces of roasted meat, fish, and vegetables on a skewer.
Kebab Utensil with a metal grate.
Parallel metal bars for cooking over a fire.
Grill Portable shelter of canvas held up by poles, rope, and pegs.
Tent A small square of cloth or paper.
Serviette A container, vessel, or apparatus for cooling.
Cooler Furniture, intended for use outside in the yard.
Lawn furniture A round bun shaped to hold a hamburger patty.
Hamburger bun Let's try that faster.
A round bun shaped to hold a hamburger patty.
Hamburger bun A meal cooked out of doors over an open fire.
Barbecue A container, vessel, or apparatus for cooling.
Cooler Be soaked in marinade.
Marinate Utensil with a metal grate.
Parallel metal bars for cooking over a fire.
Grill Portable shelter of canvas held up by poles, rope, and pegs.
Tent Pieces of roasted meat, fish, and vegetables on a skewer.
Cabob Furniture, intended for use outside in the yard.
Lawn furniture A group of twelve.
Dozen A small square of cloth or paper.
Serviette Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Barbecue How about we have a barbecue tomorrow night?
Barbecue Barbecue In the summertime at dinner, there is always the smell of someone in our neighborhood having a barbecue.
Barbecue Barbecue Can you smell the barbecue?
My mouth is watering.
Marinate Marinated Marinated steaks are much more tasty and juicier than regular steaks.
Marinate Marinate The only thing I know about my friend's secret recipe is that she marinates the chicken breasts overnight.
Marinate Marinate Marinating meat makes the meat more tender.
Lawn furniture Lawn furniture We have a whole bunch of lawn furniture and a swimming pool in our backyard.
Lawn furniture The home store down the road is having a sale on lawn furniture.
Lawn furniture The party ended abruptly when people started throwing the lawn furniture into the pool.
Grill My favorite food is steak done on the grill.
Grill After you finish cutting up the vegetables, wrap them in some aluminum foil and place it on top of the grill.
You should always clean the grill after you use it.
Cooler Cooler We brought a cooler with us to the beach so that we could keep the drinks and the sandwich meat cold.
Cooler Cooler He filled up a cooler with ice and then placed the medical specimen carefully inside.
Cooler When we go camping, we always have a cooler or two to keep food cold.