EnglishPod.com Okay, now I'd like to find out more about your last job.
I see you spent almost four years at the London Weekly, is that right?
Yes, that's right.
To be honest, the first year was quite tough for me.
I was really just treated more like an intern, I didn't have many responsibilities, and I found it quite frustrating.
So, what changed?
Well, slowly but surely, I proved myself, and the new editor liked me, so he promoted me to features writer.
Wow, a real step up.
Yes, I was responsible for restaurant and food reviews mostly.
I spent three years in that position.
But, to be honest, it wasn't an area of journalism I wanted to stay in long term.
I see, so why did you decide to leave finally?
I just felt that the paper couldn't offer me any new opportunities.
I really needed a more challenging role, to be honest.
.