The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
12 a.m.
Midnight The annual festival of the Christian church commemorating the birth of Jesus.
Christmas A figure of Christmas who brings presents to kids.
Santa Disobedient, mischievous Naughty A black or dark brown mineral Coal Large sock, traditionally Christmas gifts are put in the stocking.
Stocking A sweet baked food Cookie A usually vertical structure that allows the passage of smoke.
Chimney To observe secretively Spying Let's try that faster.
12 a.m.
Midnight A figure of Christmas who brings presents to kids.
Santa The annual festival of the Christian church commemorating the birth of Jesus.
Christmas A usually vertical structure that allows the passage of smoke.
Chimney A sweet baked food Cookie Large sock, traditionally Christmas gifts are put in the stocking.
Stocking A black or dark brown mineral Coal Disobedient, mischievous Naughty To observe secretively Spying Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Spying I caught my cat spying on me.
I wonder what he is up to.
Spying I love spying on my neighbor.
I'm just curious.
Spying Spying on me with your computer is a serious crime.
Christmas I love Christmas.
I always get lots of presents.
Christmas Every Christmas me and my family go to the beach.
Christmas This Christmas I want to get a teddy bear for a present.
Midnight I make sure to go to bed and sleep before midnight.
Midnight Someone rang me at midnight.
How annoying.
Midnight It's almost midnight and I still can't get to sleep.
Naughty If you are naughty you won't get to watch cartoons.
Naughty Naughty My son was very naughty so I sent him to his room.
Naughty My kids can be so naughty sometimes.
Santa Santa I don't believe in Santa anymore.
I know it's just my dad in a suit.
Santa Santa likes to drink beer instead of milk at my house.
Santa Santa I wish I was Santa.
I'd give all the presents to myself.