The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The result of mixing two or more things together.
Combination.
Filled with food, no longer hungry.
Stuff.
Having the ability to think of new ideas.
Creative.
A person not native to or naturalised in the country or jurisdiction under consideration.
Foreigner.
Tasty.
Delicious.
Food.
Dish.
Let's try that faster.
The result of mixing two or more things together.
Combination.
Having the ability to think of new ideas.
Creative.
Filled with food, no longer hungry.
Stuff.
Tasty.
Delicious.
A person not native to or naturalised in the country or jurisdiction under consideration.
Foreigner.
Food.
Dish.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Stuff.
I ate so much last night, I'm so stuffed.
Don't stuff yourself with too much candy, we still have dinner left.
Stuff.
My friend stuffed himself with cake, now he can't move.
Creative.
Your cooking is so creative, I wish I was good as you.
This movie is very creative, the director is very smart.
Creative.
I like people who are creative, who think outside the box.
Combination.
This is a great combination, the flavours really work well together.
Yuck, I don't like the combination of salt and pepper.
Combination.
I wonder if the coach has thought of any new combinations for the match.
Foreigner.
I don't like foreigners, they are always disrespectful to local culture.
It is important as a foreigner living overseas to at least attempt to learn the local language.
Foreigner.
We should make foreigners feel welcome and safe in our home country.
Delicious.
This lunch was delicious, thank you very much.
I love eating at this Italian restaurant, they always make delicious pasta.
Delicious.
My favourite food is mango, it's so delicious.