EnglishPod.com What did you cook?
Well, as you know, I was in Thailand last month and I took a cooking class.
So, I prepared some of my favorite dishes.
Great idea, as long as I don't get food poisoning.
So, what is on the menu tonight?
Okay, for starters, we have tam yum soup.
It's a bit spicy, but really good.
This is delicious.
The ginger and lemongrass really give it a nice taste.
Now, this next dish is one of the most famous.
Foreigners call it papaya salad, but the proper name is tom sam.
It is a spicy salad made from a mix of fresh vegetables, including shredded, unripened papaya and tomato.
This is delicious.
The combination of sour and spicy is really interesting.
I could have this every day.
Okay, now for the last and best dish, in my opinion.
This is called pad thai.
It's stir-fried noodles with eggs, fish sauce, tamarind juice, red chili pepper, plus bean sprouts, shrimp and tofu, garnished with crushed peanuts and coriander.
It's practically Thailand's national dish.
Wow, this is great.
I never knew Thai food was so creative and delicious.
Want some more?
I'm stuffed.