The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Fall asleep.
Go to sleep.
A drug that calms or relaxes someone.
Sedative.
A dream that cause horror.
Nightmare.
The regular time of sleeping.
Sleeping pattern.
Accomplish the desired task.
Do the trick.
People who have a medical disorder of the sleep.
Sleeping disorder.
Fall asleep.
Get to sleep.
Let's try that faster.
A dream that cause horror.
Nightmare.
Fall asleep.
Go to sleep.
A drug that calms or relaxes someone.
Sedative.
The regular time of sleeping.
Sleeping pattern.
People who have a medical disorder of the sleep.
Sleeping disorder.
Accomplish the desired task.
Do the trick.
Fall asleep.
Get to sleep.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sometimes I need to put on some music in order to get to sleep.
Get to sleep.
I got to sleep really late last night because I couldn't stop worrying about my presentation today.
I couldn't get to sleep until after midnight.
Nightmare.
I've had the same nightmare night after night for the past month.
I woke up from my nightmare just before I found out what was behind the door.
Nightmare.
I never have dreams but every so often I get nightmares.
Sedative.
They gave me a sedative before I went into surgery.
I often use a mild sedative in order to calm myself down when I get anxious.
Sedative.
I've heard that some people put sedatives in other people's drinks at bars in order to rob them.
Sleeping pattern.
My sleeping patterns have been all over the place recently.
I have a consistent sleeping pattern and I intend to stick to it.
Sleeping pattern.
I managed to regulate my sleeping pattern so now I can't even sleep in if I wanted to.
Do the trick.
If you start getting tired while studying, drinking some coffee should do the trick.
Just add some more salt to the soup and that should do the trick.
Do the trick.
If you turn up the volume of the microphone a bit, it should do the trick.