The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Publicly or generally known, as for a particular trait.
Notoriously The way something smells Aroma Invigorating Crisp No moisture, dry Bone dry Fine or delicate Subtle Let's try that faster.
Invigorating Crisp Fine or delicate Subtle No moisture, dry Bone dry The way something smells Aroma Publicly or generally known, as for a particular trait.
Notoriously Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Aroma This wine has a very strong aroma of fruit.
Aroma I think their aroma is spicy and woody.
Aroma Their aroma is very subtle, it's hard to smell.
Notoriously This is a notoriously hard wine to produce due to the weather.
Notoriously He notoriously stole all the money from the bank last summer.
Notoriously They are notorious in the way they do business with foreigners.
Crisp This wine has a very crisp flavour.
Crisp My mum always makes my shirts crisp and clean.
Crisp The air is nice and crisp today.
Subtle There was a subtle hint of anger in his voice.
Subtle He gave me a subtle clue to why he committed the murder.
Subtle This wine has a very subtle spicy taste.
Bone dry I love his bone dry humour.
Bone dry This lake is bone dry, there hasn't been any rain in ages.
Bone dry This wine is too bone dry for my liking.