Hello there, welcome to Wine World.
Let me know if I can help you out at all.
Um, yes, please.
I could really use some help.
I'm going over to my boss's house for dinner tonight and I don't know what kind of wine I should bring.
Okay.
Do you know what kind of food will be served?
Well, his wife is Japanese.
He said she makes really good sushi.
That's a bit of a challenge.
Sushi is notoriously difficult to pair with wine.
Well, let's see.
It'll have to be a white wine, of course.
Why?
Wouldn't a red wine go well with sushi?
No, I don't think so.
Sushi is a very delicately flavored food and red wine would be a jarring contrast.
You need a white wine which has more subtle flavors to complement the fish.
I see.
So I should get a bottle of Chardonnay.
That's a white wine, right?
Yes, Chardonnay is a white wine, but I'm not sure it'd be your best bet.
Chardonnay is one of the more full-bodied whites and tends to be a bit oaky.
I'd suggest you go for something brighter like the Sauvignon Blanc from New Zealand.
Oh, the Sauvignon Blanc?
What's that?
That's another varietal or type of grape, just like Chardonnay.
Let's see.
The label says it's got attractive citrus and grassy aromas that give way to crisp mineral flavors and a bone-dry finish, served chilled.
Oh no, how long will it take to chill the wine?
I'm on my way to dinner now.
Oh, it's okay.
Don't worry.
We'll just choose a wine from the cooler.
We don't have quite as extensive a selection over here, but this Rhone Valley white would be lovely.
All right, what varietal is that?
Well, this is a French wine, so they don't always specify the varietal on the label.
The French believe that the soil a grape is grown in is one of the most important factors in the final flavor of the wine.
This wine is probably a blend of a few different types of grapes, mostly Viognier, I'd guess.
And do you think this is a good wine?
Yes, this is one of our best sellers.
It's not quite as dry as the Sauvignon Blanc we were looking at earlier, which means it's more approachable.
It's light and crisp with a bit of a vanilla aroma.
Perfect.
I'll take it.