The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
What do you think?
How about employees staff accustomed or habituated to used to to be available to work at any time on call 9 a.m.
to 5 p.m.
9 a.m.
Let's try that faster.
employees staff What do you think?
How about to be available to work at any time on call 9 a.m.
to 5 p.m.
9 to 5 accustomed or habituated to used to Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
9 to 5 I've had a couple of part-time jobs before, but this is my first 9 to 5.
9 to 5 9 to 5 9 to 5 Nurses often work odd hours.
It's not a 9 to 5 kind of job.
9 to 5 We keep the usual working hours.
9 to 5 How about I know the shrimp dumplings are tasty here, but how about this restaurant's barbecue pork buns?
How about I'm not sure John is right for this project.
How about How about All right.
If you don't want to vacation in Thailand, how about I think we should add three more staff members to our sales team.
Staff Our company has a staff of about 55.
Staff The staffs of both Mercyhurst College and the University of Yunnan must cooperate fully for this plan to work.
Used to Beijing Beijing seemed really crowded to me when I first moved here, but now I'm used to it.
Used to Be patient with the new receptionist.
She isn't used to our system yet.
Used to I used to drive my car to work every day, but now that I live in China, I'm not used to commuting like that anymore.
On call I have to keep my cell phone handy.
I'm on call tonight.
On call Some doctors and nurses are on call around the clock.
On call Journalists are always on call.
Like they say, the news never sleeps.