EnglishPod.com Could you tell me a little about the organization?
For example, how big is your office here?
Well, in total we have around 150 employees based in Hong Kong with another 400 in our head office in Beijing.
The news desk staff in Hong Kong has around 80 staff.
You see.
And how about the working hours?
Well, as you know, Rebecca, in journalism work hours are not exactly 9 to 5.
You could be on call at any time but we do have to work very unsociable hours at times.
Well, I'm used to that, Mr Parsons, so that's not really a shock for me.
Good, as long as you understand that.
And when do you need to fill the vacancy, Mr Parsons?
Yesterday, but no.
We are hoping to start from the beginning of next month.
That sounds ideal.
Thanks for watching!