The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To be in the place of someone.
Be in your shoes.
To lose one's nerve, become suddenly anxious.
Freak out.
An instance of spending the night as a guest at another's home.
Sleep over.
To request a date.
Ask someone out.
Suppositional, uncertain.
Hypothetical.
Put in a mental hospital.
Commit.
Rumor or talk of a personal, sensational, or intimate nature.
Gossip.
To join in marriage.
Get married.
To have dreamlike musings or fantasies while awake.
Daydream.
A romantic meeting.
Date.
Let's try that faster.
Suppositional, uncertain.
Hypothetical.
To join in marriage.
Get married.
Rumor or talk of a personal, sensational, or intimate nature.
Gossip.
To have dreamlike musings or fantasies while awake.
Daydream.
To be in the place of someone.
Be in your shoes.
Put in a mental hospital.
Commit.
A romantic meeting.
Date.
An instance of spending the night as a guest at another's home.
Sleep over.
To request a date.
Ask someone out.
To lose one's nerve, become suddenly anxious.
Freak out.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Ask someone out.
When asking someone out, choose your moment carefully.
And practice what you might say in advance so that you don't appear tongue tied.
Ask someone out.
I heard you ask your new neighbor out on a date.
I really want to ask Jeff out, but what if he says no?
Freak out.
Oh my gosh.
I'm going to meet Justin Timberlake.
I'm totally freaking out.
Freak out.
Why did you freak out when I told you I'd be late for dinner?
Don't freak out.
We can solve this problem in five minutes.
Commit.
The judge had him committed to a mental institution.
If you get committed to an asylum, can you eventually get out?
Commit.
He was committed to 50 hours of community service for his crimes.
If I won a million dollars, I would buy you a diamond ring.
We wouldn't be so late if Nick drove faster.
I would get a divorce if I were you.
If it's sunny today, we will go to the park.
If you study hard, you will pass the test.
Mary will be very sad if Joe leaves.