EnglishPod.com What the heck is going on?
Did you see that?
What was that thing?
I don't know.
I'm just glad we made it out.
Look, there's a police car.
Help!
Please, please stop!
Howdy ma'am.
What seems to be the problem?
Is this man bothering you?
Officer.
There is, like, a witch creature back there.
We tied her up, but she broke free, and she was about to have us for dinner.
Okay, calm down.
Calm down.
Let me see your eyes, please.
Have you been drinking tonight, son?
We're telling the truth.
She's in there.
We suspected her being a kidnapper or a rapist, but it turns out she's an alien or something.
Okay, calm down.
Calm down.
Let me see your eyes, please.
Ugh!
Seriously!
Are you going to help us out or not?
Okay, let's go have a look, shall we?
Hello?
Is anyone in there?
Be careful.
She might be hiding.
It's perfectly safe.
There isn't anyone.
Ahh!