The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Hell in a more polite form.
Heck Able to escape or flee.
Make it out.
A living thing.
Creature.
Get out of something.
Break free.
Let me.
Lemmy.
Regard someone as a criminal or to be guilty.
Suspect.
The kind of criminal that catches someone and asks the family for money.
Kidnapper.
The kind of criminal who forces someone to have sex.
Rapist.
Take a glance.
Have a look.
Act of stealing something.
Larceny.
The act of killing another person.
Homicide.
Want to.
Wanna.
Going to.
Gonna.
Abbreviation for driving under the influence.
To drive while being intoxicated.
DUI.
Let's try that faster.
Let me.
Act of stealing something.
Larceny.
The kind of criminal who forces someone to have sex.
Rapist.
The act of killing another person.
Homicide.
Regard someone as a criminal or to be guilty.
Suspect.
Want to.
Wanna.
Hell in a more polite form.
Heck.
Make it out.
The kind of criminal that catches someone and asks the family for money.
Kidnapper.
Going to.
Gonna.
Have a look.
Creature.
Abbreviation for driving under the influence.
To drive while being intoxicated.
DUI.
Get out of something.
Break free.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
We tied up the dog, but he is trying to break free.
Break free.
I am glad that I broke free from that horrible relationship.
I want to break free from all my daily responsibilities.
Creature.
There is a strange creature under my bed.
I think that rabbits are the cutest creatures in the world.
Creature.
Susan hates cats.
She thinks they are lazy creatures.
Suspect.
The police suspected him of being a bank robber.
We suspect our dog is responsible for this mess.
Suspect.
The neighborhood suspected that our neighbor was selling drugs.
Donna thought she didn't pass her exam, but it turns out she did.
My car broke down last week and it turns out that I need a new gearbox.
Daniel bought an expensive watch and it turns out that it was fake.
Lemmy.
Let me have a look inside the car.
Let me go out tonight, Dad.
Please?
Lemmy.
Lemmy think about it and I will give you an answer tomorrow.