EnglishPod.com Alright Officer McGraw, give it to me straight.
What are we looking at here?
Detective McGee, we're glad to see you.
We could sure use your expertise on this one.
It's a break-in, but nothing seems to have been stolen.
We received a call from the Baer family at around 10.30 this morning.
They had gone out for a walk before breakfast and came home to this mess.
Broken chairs and porridge all over the place.
Apparently Mama Baer had made the porridge a little too hot, you see.
They were waiting for it to cool down.
Okay then, let's start examining the evidence.
Have the forensics team been in yet?
Yes sir.
They found some fingerprints on the bowls and are analyzing them back at the lab as we speak.
Hopefully they will be able to identify the burglar soon.
Hmm.
Aha!
What's this?
A strand of golden hair.
This is a very important piece of trace evidence, McGraw.
It tells me the suspect has long golden hair, and very few men have long golden hair.
So our criminal could be a woman.
A woman?
Was she working alone?
Did she have an accomplice?
An accomplice?
No, no McGraw.
She was definitely working alone.
See here, there are footprints in the porridge.
Here on the floor, small footprints.
This tells me that our suspect is small, and could possibly be a child.
A child?
Surely not, sir.
We must follow the clues, McGraw.
The evidence doesn't lie.
Now, let's reconstruct the crime.
The suspect came in, sat in each chair, breaking the smallest one into little pieces.
Next, the porridge.
She obviously tried to eat it, and because it was so hot, she dropped it on the floor.
Making this mess.
Hmm.
Interesting.
These footprints seem to lead upstairs.
McGraw, did your officers clear the scene?
Well, there was no one down here.
Maybe we forgot to check upstairs.
Hey, what's with all the noise?
I'm trying to sleep up here.
There she is!
Get her!