The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Written agreement between two or more people.
Contract.
Hope for luck.
Fingers crossed.
Price.
Deal.
Good wishes.
Regard.
Top boss.
Head.
Let's try that faster.
Hope for luck.
Fingers crossed.
Price.
Deal.
Written agreement between two or more people.
Contract.
Good wishes.
Regard.
Top boss.
Head.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Fingers crossed.
Fingers crossed that we win at poker tonight.
I hope my team will win the football match tonight.
Fingers crossed.
Contract.
Let's hope, fingers crossed, that we have the day off tomorrow.
If we can get that new contract for distributing our product, we will all get commission.
Contract.
The new contract signed between our firm and the government will ensure we make profit for the next decade or so.
The player is facing a lawsuit for breaching his contract clause.
Head.
I'm going to meet the head of our company today to ask for a raise.
The head boss of the firm rejected the rumours about his retirement.
Head.
The head director of the movie quit over a paid dispute.
Deal.
The deal made between the two companies ensures a joint meeting every two months.
I made a deal with my parents that I get paid every time I do the washing.
Deal.
I don't think this deal is fair.
I want a bigger incentive.
Regard.
Give my regards to your husband for me.
I'm sorry to hear of your loss.
My regards go to you and your family.
Regard.
Please give my kind regards to your parents when you see them.