EnglishPod.com Mmm, doesn't look good.
What do you mean?
My daddy gave me this car for my birthday last month.
It's brand new.
Well Missy, the white smoke that you saw is steam from the radiator.
You overheated your engine so now the pistons are busted and so is your transmission.
You should have called us and we could have told you over here when your car died.
Ugh, so how long is this going to take?
An hour?
I'm afraid a bit more than that.
We need to order the spare parts.
Take apart your electrical system, fuel pump and engine and then put it back together again.
You're going to have to leave it here for at least two weeks.
What?
How am I supposed to go to school or go shopping?
This is not happening.