The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To flow out of something in a fast and forceful way.
Spew The metal casing enclosing a set of gears in a motor vehicle.
Gearbox To stop working or running while in use by someone.
Die on A tubular acoustic device inserted in the exhaust system that is designed to reduce noise.
Muffler Broken Busted Control mechanism for keeping an automobile at a set speed.
Cruise control To remove all the pieces.
Take apart To pass after catching up with another vehicle on the road.
Overtake Introduces request or suggestion.
How about A device that is locked on the wheel of a car by the police to prevent it from moving.
Boot Let's try that faster.
Broken Busted To flow out of something in a fast and forceful way.
Spew To remove all the pieces.
Take apart Introduces request or suggestion.
How about To pass after catching up with another vehicle on the road.
Overtake To stop working or running while in use by someone.
Die on Control mechanism for keeping an automobile at a set speed.
Cruise control A tubular acoustic device inserted in the exhaust system that is designed to reduce noise.
Muffler The metal casing enclosing a set of gears in a motor vehicle.
Gearbox A device that is locked on the wheel of a car by the police to prevent it from moving.
Boot Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Spew Spew Everyone in the village was evacuated when the volcano started spewing lava.
Spew After 10 hours of constant interrogation the suspect finally spewed the truth.
Spew Frank had too much to drink and spewed all over the car.
Die on My CD player died on me and I had to listen to the radio.
Die on Get that medicine over here fast or this guy is going to die on me.
Die on I forgot to charge my mobile phone.
It's going to die on me soon.
How about How about we go see a movie tonight.
How about How about you be quiet and let me do my job.
How about How about we get married in Cancun instead of Greece.
Busted Busted We were playing baseball in the backyard and I accidentally busted a window.
Busted Mike was in a car accident and busted his rib and arm.
Busted Busted The cat knocked over my mom's favorite vase and it busted into a million pieces.
Take apart Once I'd taken the clock apart I couldn't fit the bits together again.
Take apart When I was a kid I loved taking apart my toys to see how they work.
Take apart This book shows you how to take apart electronic devices and gadgets.