EnglishPod.com Yeah, we're here because we feel this is an injustice.
The financial irresponsibility of big business has to stop.
We're here to show the government that we don't like the way they're spending our tax dollars.
Sir, but what exactly is making everyone so angry?
It's an absolute outrage, Sarah.
The U.S.
government wants to give $25 billion of taxpayers' money to the auto industry.
These are companies that have been mismanaged and are now nearly bankrupt.
I see.
But many supporters of the bailout argue that it could help save the jobs of millions of hardworking Americans.
That may be true, and I for one don't want to see anyone lose their job.
But how can these CEOs ask for a bailout when they're making millions of dollars, and then they have the nerve to fly to Washington in private jets?
This costs hundreds of thousands of dollars.
They're asking for money.
That is just not right.
Good point.
This is Sarah O'Connell reporting live from Washington, D.C.
Back to you, Tom.