The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A female romantic partner.
Girlfriend.
End a romantic relationship.
Break up.
Take responsibility for your actions.
Man up.
An unplight way of saying something is foolish.
Crap.
A grown male still dependent on his mother.
Mama's boy.
Change the place where you live.
Leave a house.
Move out.
Let's try that faster.
A female romantic partner.
Girlfriend.
An unplight way of saying something is foolish.
Crap.
Man up.
End a romantic relationship.
Break up.
A grown male still dependent on his mother.
Mama's boy.
Change the place where you live.
Leave a house.
Move out.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Break up.
I am going to break up with my girlfriend next week.
We decided to break up and date other people.
Break up.
They weren't getting along so they broke up.
Man up.
You need to man up and take responsibility for your actions.
He didn't want to man up to what he did.
Man up.
Man up to him.
Don't let him bully you.
Mama's boy.
I don't like it when people call me a mama's boy.
When are you going to stop being a mama's boy?
Mama's boy.
Just because my mom cleans my room, my friends call me a mama's boy.
Crap.
I need to clean my room and get rid of all this crap.
I forgot my wallet.
Crap.
This car is a piece of crap.
Move out.
My parents told me I need to move out by my 21st birthday.
I am looking for an apartment and will move out next week.
Move out.
My roommate is moving out next month so you can take his room.
Thanks for watching!