EnglishPod.com Why did your girlfriend break up with you?
I don't know.
She said she was tired of me not manning up and being more independent, which I think is all a bunch of crap.
Well, you still live with your parents, so she does have a point.
What do you mean?
A lot of people live with their parents, especially when rent is so expensive and the slump in the economy.
Yeah, but you're almost 40.
Plus, you make good money, so there's really no excuse.
It's just simply because you're a mama's boy.
Whatever, dude.
I have everything I need.
Why would I move out?
I have a great roof over my head, my mom does my laundry and cooks for me.
What else could a guy ask for?
Let's agree to disagree.