The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Make someone scared and uncomfortable.
Creep out.
Very disturbing or frightening.
Chilling.
Unable to be explained by science.
Supernatural.
Strange and a little frightening.
Spooky.
Extremely scary.
Terrifying.
Frightening in appearance.
Scary-looking.
Strange or scary.
Creepy.
A very large house.
Mansion.
A ghost lives or visit a place.
Haunt.
To try and get information about something.
Investigate.
Someone who is too afraid to do what is right.
Coward.
Small bumps on your skin caused by fear, cold, etc.
Goosebumps.
Someone who is always scared of things.
Scaredy-cat.
Let's try that faster.
Strange or scary.
Creepy.
Strange and a little frightening.
Spooky.
Make someone scared and uncomfortable.
Creep out.
A ghost lives or visit a place.
Haunt.
Frightening in appearance.
Scary-looking.
Unable to be explained by science.
Supernatural.
A very large house.
Mansion.
To try and get information about something.
Investigate.
Someone who is always scared of things.
Scaredy-cat.
Someone who is too afraid to do what is right.
Coward.
Very disturbing or frightening.
Chilling.
Small bumps on your skin caused by fear, cold, etc.
Goosebumps.
Extremely scary.
Terrifying.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Scary-looking.
That guy is making me nervous.
He's really creepy-looking.
Scary-looking.
I saw the craziest-looking house today.
It was built upside down.
Scary-looking.
What a nice-looking dog.
Can I pet him?
Spooky.
Whenever I walk by the Main Street graveyard, I get a really spooky feeling that someone is following me.
Why don't you sleep over at my house this weekend?
Your house is kind of spooky at night.
Spooky.
That was so spooky!
The TV turned on while I was out of the room.
Walking alone at night gives me the creeps.
I always feel like someone is going to attack me.
Mr.
Crane gives me the creeps whenever he tries to touch me.
Small, dark spaces always gives my sister the creeps.
Goosebumps.
Can you turn down the air conditioning?
I have the goosebumps.
Goosebumps.
When I think about how the murderer lived near my house, I get goosebumps.
Do you get goosebumps when you watch scary movies?
I swear the ghost of Old Man Fink haunts my dreams every night.
David told me that there is a ghost that haunts the seventh floor of this hotel.
Weird things happen in that house.
I think it must be haunted.