The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Pasta in the shape of long narrow strips.
Fettuccine Pasta dish originally from Italy.
Spaghetti A type of Italian pasta.
Penne The stomach of a horse used as food.
Horse tripe Pasta dish originally from Italy.
Spaghetti Pasta in the shape of long narrow strips.
Fettuccine A waiter or waitress Server The stomach of a horse used as food.
Horse tripe A large shrimp Prawn A type of Italian pasta Penne A suggestion or proposal Recommendation Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Good morning sir, may I take your order?
Thank you.
I placed my order 30 minutes ago.
I want an order of fries.
Recommendation Do you have any recommendations for dinner?
Recommendation I'm sorry, I don't have any recommendations.
Recommendation I'd like to hear your recommendations.
Personally, I like chicken more than beef.
Personally, I don't like this colour.
Personally, I don't think it's a good idea.
I'd like to have some tea instead of coffee.
Can I come at 8 instead of 9?
Instead of going to work, I stayed home.
Thanks for watching!