The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A gambling game in which the players bet on which slot of a rotating disc a small ball will come to rest in.
Roulette To make something legal.
Legalize A machine featuring an electronic game on which to gamble, worked by placing a coin in a slot.
Slot machine Bad or immoral behavior or habits.
Vice A variation of poker, where there are five community cards and each player has two personal cards.
Texas Hold'em Using someone for something unfairly.
Exploitation The probability expressed as a ratio that something will or will not happen.
Odds Only reason Sole purpose A form to gamble via the internet, visiting websites and using a credit card.
Online gambling About money Monetary The practice of risking money in a game or bet.
Gambling A building or room that has games you can bet on.
Casino A person who organizes bets.
Bookie Unable to stop doing something that is harmful.
Addicted Let's try that faster!
A gambling game in which the players bet on which slot of a rotating disc a small ball will come to rest in.
Roulette To make something legal.
Legalize A form to gamble via the internet, visiting websites and using a credit card.
Online gambling A variation of poker where there are five community cards and each player has two personal cards.
Texas Hold'em The practice of risking money in a game or bet.
Gambling About money Monetary A machine featuring an electronic game on which to gamble, worked by placing a coin in a slot.
Slot machine A building or room that has games you can bet on.
Casino Unable to stop doing something that is harmful.
Addicted Only reason Sole purpose The probability expressed as a ratio that something will or will not happen.
Odds Using someone for something unfairly.
Exploitation A person who organizes bets.
Bookie Bad or immoral behavior or habits.
Vice Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Legalize Legalizing The state of California is considering legalizing marijuana for medicinal purposes.
Legalize The president is passing a bill that would legalize gay marriages throughout the country.
Legalize Considering the possible consequences, we think that is not a good idea to legalize dog racing in our state.
Vice Smoking is a dangerous and unhealthy vice that is difficult to quit.
Vice Blasphemy is a vice according to the Catholic Church.
Vice I think that gluttony is a vice that everyone can relate to.
Exploitation Exploitation Canada is considering the exploitation of newly discovered oil fields.
Exploitation He got ahead in this industry through the exploitation of his friends and co-workers.
Exploitation Child labor exploitation is a concern in underdeveloped countries.
Sole purpose The sole purpose of this meeting is to decide on an idea for our new product.
Sole purpose The sole purpose of this new software is to prevent kids from accessing adult content on the internet.
Sole purpose My sole purpose in life is to become a rock legend.
Monetary The central bank is rethinking its monetary policy in order to avoid a recession.
Monetary Monetary I think we should become a non-monetary society and get goods and services through barter.
Monetary The necklace has sentimental value as opposed to monetary value.