EnglishPod.com Um, sorry to bother you.
My name is Rachel.
I'm new here.
Can I ask you for a favor?
Hi Rachel, welcome on board.
I'm afraid I can't help you right now.
I'm getting ready for a very important meeting.
Excuse me, but can I bother you for a second?
You know what?
I'd love to help you, but I'm about to meet an important client.
Do you want to ask Sean instead?
He sits right over there.
Sorry to interrupt you, Sean.
Could you do me a quick favor?
Actually, I'm working on a document that's due in a couple of minutes.
I really can't talk right now.
Sorry about that.
Jeez!
I just want to know where the bathroom is.
What's wrong with you people?
Thanks for watching!