The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Important Urgent To be victim of a robbery, something stolen.
Get robbed To send money electronically Wire Questionable, suspicious Dodgy To gain access illegally or without authorization Hack To swindle someone by means of a trick Scam A swindler who exploits the confidence of his victim Con artist To gain access illegally or without authorization Hack To send money electronically Wire Questionable, suspicious Dodgy To be victim of a robbery, something stolen Get robbed Important Urgent To swindle someone by means of a trick Scam A swindler who exploits the confidence of his victim Con artist Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Get robbed I got robbed last week.
Get robbed If you get robbed you should call the police.
Get robbed This city is very dangerous at night and you may get robbed.
Wire Wire My cousin wired me some money from England.
Wire If you wire the money today, it will be available the next day.
Wire Wire There are many companies that offer money wiring services.
Dodgy This bar looks very dodgy.
Dodgy This is a very dodgy neighborhood so be careful.
Dodgy I don't think you should eat that fruit.
It looks a bit dodgy.
Scam My friend was scammed and lost $1,000.
Scam There are many email scams circulating around the internet.
Scam A guy tried to scam me for some money last week.
Hack Our website was hacked and was down for a week.
Hack Google claims that their servers were hacked.
Hack You should have a long alphanumeric password for your email account to prevent others from hacking it.