The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Without using any chemicals.
Organic.
Healthy to the body.
Green.
Small ring-shaped fried cakes.
Doughnut.
Let's try that faster.
Without using any chemicals.
Organic.
Small ring-shaped fried cakes.
Doughnut.
The way people live.
Lifestyle.
Have healthy food.
Eat right.
Healthy to the body.
Green.
A high calorie food and low in nutritional value.
Junk food.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Eat right.
My mother started eating right and lost pounds.
We need to stop eating at restaurants every night and start eating right.
Eat right.
Eating right is better for one's health.
Lifestyle.
A healthy lifestyle includes eating right and exercising regularly.
She has a very unhealthy lifestyle.
Lifestyle.
He wouldn't be able to live here because he has a very expensive lifestyle.
Junk food.
My favorite junk food is potato chips.
The movie theater in my town only serves junk food.
Junk food.
My high school stopped serving junk food in the cafeteria.
Organic.
The organic section in the grocery store keeps getting bigger.
These apples have been grown organically.
Organic.
This store only sells organic products.
Green.
In America, many people are trying to live green.
Some of my friends are switching to a greener lifestyle.
Green.
The green options for going to work are to walk, bike, or use the metro system.