EnglishPod.com Okay, darling, I got some pizzas, potato chips, hot dogs, and lots of cheese.
Oh, John, I thought we said we'd start eating right.
Remember?
Our new healthy lifestyle?
That's all junk food.
Huh.
Right, so what did you get?
Well, healthy food, of course.
I got some whole wheat bread, skimmed milk, fresh fish, and organic carrots.
Organic?
What's organic?
Do we need organic carrots?
They were grown without using any chemicals that are harmful to our health.
And yes, John, we need organic carrots.
Oh, so organic vegetables are the green option, right?
Yep, better for the environment and better for us.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Donuts?
Are they organic donuts, Kelly?
But I like donuts.
Thanks for watching!