The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Relax Settle down The act of overcharging Rip off Deal with Handle Vomit Throw up Entertainment Amusement Let's try that faster.
Deal with Handle Relax Settle down Entertainment Amusement The act of overcharging Rip off Vomit Throw up Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Settle down I feel I'm too young to settle down.
Settle down Please tell the children to settle down.
Settle down I wish I could settle down in a peaceful place.
Rip off That guy tried to rip us off.
Rip off This place is a total rip off.
There is nothing to do and it cost so much to get here.
Rip off That concert was a rip off.
She sang the same song three times and her voice was horrible.
Handle Do you think you can handle such a big responsibility?
Handle I can't handle this pressure.
I need to go out for a while.
Handle Please handle this box with extreme care.
Throw up Last night I saw a guy throw up so much that I felt sick too.
Throw up Children tend to throw up after eating when they move too much.
Throw up Please be careful not to throw up inside the perimeter.
Amusement I've never been to an amusement park in my life.
Amusement This must be the best amusement park I've ever seen.
Amusement I wish there were more amusement parks like this in my city.