EnglishPod.com I'm so excited!
We're finally here!
Six Flags Magic Mountain!
This is the best amusement park in the world!
Alright, settle down now.
You're gonna give yourself a heart attack.
I can't believe they charge us $35 each.
Seems like such a rip-off, don't you think?
It's not like I'm gonna get on these things.
Whoa!
Viper!
That's the world's highest and fastest roller coaster!
You go at more than 100 miles per hour.
I'm gonna go on that one.
Can I, Mom, please?
Can I?
Chris, I'm not sure you should get on that.
It seems a bit too much for you, and we just had breakfast 30 minutes ago.
I don't think it's a good idea.
Aw, come on, Mom!
I can handle it.
I promise I won't ask for anything else.
Besides, it's not like I'm gonna throw up or anything.
Let him go, Carol.
He'll be fine.
Alright!
Yeah!
This is amazing!
See how high up we go?
Whoa!