The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Baby Infant Shake or tremble when see something Quake at the sight From or to a great distance Afar A person who rescues people from harm or danger Saviour An old-fashioned poetic or religious word for your Thy Let's try that faster.
From or to a great distance Afar An old-fashioned poetic or religious word for your Thy Baby Infant A person who rescues people from harm or danger Saviour Shake or tremble when see something Quake at the sight Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Infant The infants woke up when the dog started barking.
Infant I was only an infant when my parents died.
Infant She held the infant as if he was her own.
Quake at the sight Infant The farmers quaked at the sight of the wolves.
Quake at the sight The villagers quaked at the sight of the advancing army.
Quake at the sight The dogs quaked at the smell of the bear.
Afar The wise men travelled from Afar to find the baby Jesus.
Afar I could see the boat coming in from Afar.
Afar Afar From Afar it seemed like it was only a hill, but up close it was a huge mountain.
Saviour Saviour Jesus Christ claimed to be the Saviour of the world.
Saviour The Hebrew Scriptures made prophecies about the coming Saviour.
Saviour You saved me from drowning.
You're my Saviour.
Thy Thy face is as beautiful as the starlit sky.
Thy Love thy neighbour as thyself.
Thy May thy harvest always be plentiful.