The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To think about Wonder A person who designs buildings Architect To end up like Turn out To ruin or destroy something, like a car Wreck Used to express a realization Now that I think of it A feeling of guilt Remorse To feel sad or sorry about something Regret To think deeply about something Ponder A happy and relaxed life Good life To think fondly about the past Reminisce An alternative scenario Could have been The art and science of designing buildings Architecture A sudden event that is not planned Accident Let's try that faster A person who designs buildings Architect A feeling of guilt Remorse To end up like Turn out A happy and relaxed life Good life To feel sad or sorry about something Regret An alternative scenario Could have been The art and science of designing buildings Architecture To think about Wonder Used to express a realization Now that I think of it To ruin or destroy something, like a car Wreck To think deeply about something Ponder To think fondly about the past Reminisce A sudden event that is not planned Accident Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Wonder I wonder what Mike is doing in his room.
I think he's building a time machine or something.
Wonder I wonder why Debbie kicked her husband out of the house.
Wonder We often wonder and ask ourselves why we continue to spend money on useless things.
Turn out Our house turned out beautifully.
The architect is very talented.
Turn out I'm curious to see how everything will turn out in the next few days.
Turn out It turns out Bob was right.
I really do have a drinking problem.
Now that I think of it Actually, now that I think of it, I do have a lawnmower you could borrow.
Now that I think of it Wait, now that I think of it, you owe me $100.
Now that I think of it Now that I think of it, I should have behaved better at the party.
Regret You can't live your life with regrets.
Stay positive and optimistic.
Regret Do you have any regrets in life?
Regret I regret to inform you that your dog will never walk again.
If I hadn't gone skiing, I wouldn't have broken my leg.
If Ellie had studied harder, she would have passed the exam.
They wouldn't have missed their flight if they had left home earlier.