EnglishPod.com This is the good life.
We have it good, don't you think?
Yeah, of course.
Although, don't you ever wonder what could have been?
What do you mean?
Well, sometimes I think of how things could have turned out if I had done things a little differently.
For example?
Like, for example, if I hadn't studied architecture, I would have become an artist like I wanted to.
I see.
Yeah, now that I think of it, I wouldn't have gotten married if I hadn't moved to this town and met Sally.
You see, everything happens for a reason.
We wouldn't even have met if I hadn't been in that car accident ten years ago.
Well, I have no regrets.
I'll drink to that.