Welcome back racing fans, my name is Rick Fields and as always I'm joined by my partner in crime, Bob Copeland.
We're in the last stretch of this very exciting race and Kimi Raikonen is leading the pack with only four laps to go.
They're heading to turn three and Lewis Hamilton tries to pass Raikonen.
It's a close one and oh no, Hamilton hits the wall.
He came in too fast, jammed on the brakes and spun out.
We have yellow flag and the pace car is making its way into the track.
The clean up crew is towing the heavily damaged car and the green flag drops.
Raikonen is still in the lead with only two laps to go.
Smoke is coming out of his car.
He seems to be having engine trouble, he makes his way under the pit and Fernando Alonso takes the lead.
How unlucky for Raikonen and this race is over ladies and gentlemen.
Alonso takes the checkered flag.