The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A person you always do things together with.
Partner in crime.
The final time period.
Stretch.
Left to complete.
To go.
Hit or step on the brakes quickly and forcefully.
Jam on the brakes.
A car slides and makes a turn rapidly in an uncontrolled way.
Spin out.
The car used when accidents happen which leads other cars but is not a competitor in the race.
Pace car.
The sign used in an F1 race to show that there is an accident on some part of the track.
Yellow flag.
The group of people who clean up the track.
Clean up crew.
The sign used in an F1 race to show that the race is now back to the normal state.
Green flag.
To be the first in position.
Take the lead.
A flag with black and white squares showing someone has won.
Checkered flag.
Cause an engine to run very quickly.
Rev.
The status of winning a championship in a sport.
Title.
The quality of moving easily through the air.
Aerodynamic.
A person who loves cars and racing.
American English.
Motorhead.
The race that determines who will be able to participate in the main race.
Qualifying round.
The front position in a car race.
Pole position.
Let's try that faster.
Cause an engine to run very quickly.
Rev.
The sign used in an F1 race to show that there is an accident on some part of the track.
Yellow flag.
Left to complete.
To go.
The race that determines who will be able to participate in the main race.
Qualifying round.
A person who loves cars and racing.
American English.
To be the first in position.
Take the lead.
The status of winning a championship in a sport.
Title.
The quality of moving easily through the air.
Aerodynamic.
The group of people who clean up the track.
Clean up crew.
The car used when accidents happen which leads other cars but is not a competitor in the race.
Pace car.
A flag with black and white squares showing someone has won.
Checkered flag.
The front position in a car race.
Pole position.
Hit or step on the brakes quickly and forcefully.
Jam on the brakes.
The sign used in an F1 race to show that the race is now back to the normal state.
Green flag.
A car slides and makes a turn rapidly in an uncontrolled way.
Spin out.
A person you always do things together with.
Partnering crime.
The final time period.
Stretch.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Jam on the brakes.
You shouldn't jam on the brakes suddenly while driving.
You can lose control of your car.
Jam on the brakes.
He was really angry and jammed on the brakes and ordered me to get out of the car.
There was an accident right in front of me.
Luckily I jammed on the brakes and was able to avoid it.
That was a close one.
The teacher almost caught me cheating.
It's a close one.
We are tied and the game is almost over.
My girlfriend almost found the presents I hid under the bed.
It was a close one.
To go.
Only three days to go and then we are going on vacation.
I have another 15 minutes to go before I can go home.
To go.
I'm so excited.
Only one month to go until my new baby is born.
I managed to make my way through the crowd and go into the concert.
There was a lot of security at the concert but I managed to make my way onto the stage.
She was able to make her way onto the train.
You can't park here or your car will be towed by the police.
My car broke down last night so I had to call someone to come and tow my car.
I can't believe they towed my car away.
I was parked there for only a few minutes.