The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
On a diagonal, forward and to the left or right.
Diagonally A game in which each player moves sixteen pieces across a board and tries to capture the opponent's king.
Chess The final and most important piece in chess.
King Make ready for use.
Set up A very powerful piece in chess.
Queen Very useful or helpful.
Valuable A useful piece in chess.
Knight To take Capture A piece in chess that can only move diagonally.
Bishop The weakest piece in chess.
A person or group without much power.
Pawn Not interesting Boring A piece in chess that can only move along straight lines.
Rook Describe situation in which king cannot move.
Checkmate Let's try that faster.
Not interesting Boring A useful piece in chess.
Knight The final and most important piece in chess.
King Describe situation in which king cannot move.
Checkmate A game in which each player moves sixteen pieces across a board and tries to capture the opponent's king.
Chess A very powerful piece in chess.
Queen To take Capture Make ready for use.
Set up The weakest piece in chess.
A person or group without much power.
Pawn A piece in chess that can only move diagonally.
Bishop On a diagonal.
Forward and to the left or right.
Diagonally Very useful or helpful.
Valuable A piece in chess that can only move along straight lines.
Rook Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Diagonally Susan lives diagonally across the street from us.
Diagonally Bishop The bishop is a piece that can move diagonally as many spaces as it wants.
Diagonally Diane sits diagonally from me at work.
Set up Help me set up my new home theater system.
Set up We can't work today because the workers are setting up the network.
Set up We are setting everything up for the party tonight.
It's gonna be fun!
Valuable Valuable His house was furnished with valuable antique furniture.
Valuable The witness provided valuable information, which led to the apprehension of the murderer.
Valuable All my valuables were stolen from my home last night.
Capture Capture Oh no!
You captured my queen!
Capture I've captured almost all your pieces.
You will lose.
Capture I can't believe the police finally captured that murderer.
Pawn Germania was an underdeveloped nation that was a pawn in international politics.
Pawn The pawn is the least valuable piece on the chessboard, but it is a very important piece.
Pawn Pawn He used Sherry as a pawn in his evil game.