The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Store that bakes and sells bread and pastries.
Bakery Any shaped or molded mass of food.
Loaf Cut into thin slices.
Slice The grain of some grasses, used in making flour or pasta.
Wheat A kind of food made of flour.
Bread A small cake.
Muffin The edible, usually bluish berry of various shrubs.
Blueberry A wildly cultivated cereal grass.
Rye Complete amount Total A type of cake.
Cheesecake A baked dessert.
Cake Let's try that faster.
A small cake.
Muffin A baked dessert.
Cake A kind of food made of flour.
Bread A wildly cultivated cereal grass.
Rye Any shaped or molded mass of food.
Loaf A type of cake.
Cheesecake The grain of some grasses, used in making flour or pasta.
Wheat Complete amount Total Cut into thin slices.
Slice The edible, usually bluish berry of various shrubs.
Blueberry Store that bakes and sells bread and pastries.
Bakery Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Total Can you please tell me what the total amount will be?
Total You are sick for a total of 40 days.
Total In total your bill comes to $100.
Wheat I prefer wheat over white as it is more healthy.
Wheat Do you have any wheat bread left?
Wheat I'm going on an all wheat diet to lose some weight.
Bakery Can you please go to the bakery and buy some bread?
Bakery Next time you are at the bakery don't forget to buy a cake.
Bakery Damn, the bakery is all out of muffins.
Slice Could you please slice the meat for me?
Slice I like to slice the bread into triangles.
Slice Be careful not to slice your fingers with that sharp knife.
Blueberry I love to eat blueberry muffins.
Blueberry I always have my toast with blueberry sauce.
Blueberry Blueberries are too sweet for my liking.