EnglishPod.com I've never heard of Amlion College.
Could you?
Of course, sir.
Let me give you a brief overview.
Amlion College is located in the center of New York City.
The school covers a wide range of academic subjects and eighty percent of the courses are transferable to other state universities.
And last year Amlion College was ranked number one in terms of graduate employment.
Interesting.
And what about the tuition fees then?
You'll be looking at somewhere around fifteen thousand US dollars per semester.
Okay, well...
And did I mention our on-campus housing?
Students can stay in our newly renovated dorms for as little as three thousand dollars per month.
Sounds good!
Well, I'll just grab one of your flyers.
Sir, you got the wrong flyer!
Sir!