The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Indicates something someone does very often.
All she ever does.
The mother of someone's wife.
Mother-in-law.
Someone or something that makes you very proud.
Pride and joy.
To run away with a lover, especially with the intention of getting married.
Elope.
To want or desire something or someone very much.
Pine.
A marriage arranged by someone other than the person's getting married.
Arranged marriage.
To do something that you have thought or talked about.
Go through with.
Money or property brought by a bride to her husband at marriage.
Dowry.
Not able to be corrected or changed.
Encourageable.
A marriage partner, a husband or wife.
Spouse.
Let's try that faster.
A marriage arranged by someone other than the person's getting married.
Arranged marriage.
The mother of someone's wife.
Mother-in-law.
Money or property brought by a bride to her husband at marriage.
Dowry.
To do something that you have thought or talked about.
Go through with.
To run away with a lover, especially with the intention of getting married.
Elope.
Indicates something someone does very often.
All she ever does.
To want or desire something or someone very much.
Pine.
Not able to be corrected or changed.
Encourageable.
Someone or something that makes you very proud.
Pride and joy.
A marriage partner, a husband or wife.
Spouse.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
All she ever does.
All Mary ever does is talk about her boyfriend and how great he is and so on.
It makes me sick.
All she ever does.
What do you mean you're tired?
All you ever do is sit here and watch TV.
All she ever does.
I don't understand you.
All you ever do is complain.
You are never happy.
Pride and joy.
Jack's new car is his pride and joy.
He washes it every weekend.
Pride and joy.
My brother is very happy with his newly born child.
It's his pride and joy.
Pride and joy.
And here's a picture of my pride and joy.
My six month old daughter.
Pine.
Victoria has been pining over her boyfriend since he left for France.
It's so hard to quit smoking.
I've been pining for a cigarette all day.
Pine.
I read that pining for lost love can turn into a physically addictive pleasure.
Can you believe that?
Go through with.
I don't know if I can go through with this deal.
I'm having doubts.
Go through with.
Molly was supposed to get married last weekend but she couldn't go through with it so the wedding was cancelled.
I committed to this project and now I have to go through with it.
Encouragable.
That criminal is incorrigible.
He was released from prison and committed another crime that same day.
Encouragable.
We live in an incorrigible country that will continue to make the same mistakes over and over again.
We have to find a new home for our dog since he is simply incorrigible.
Today he chewed and destroyed all of my shoes.