The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A silly or stupid person.
Airhead.
Information.
411.
Nerd, loser.
Dweeb.
Relax.
Chill out.
Take a chill pill.
Very good.
Wicked.
A male who plays a lot of sports.
Jock.
To be romantic with.
To get with.
Leave a place quickly.
Jet.
Rich.
Loaded.
Leave me alone.
Go away.
I don't care.
Bite me.
A car.
Ride.
Very ugly.
Butt.
Man.
Dude.
Knew, cool.
Fresh.
Completely cool.
Bad to the bones.
Just kidding, I was joking.
Psych.
Get angry.
Have a cow.
Let's try that faster.
Leave a place quickly.
Jet.
Very ugly.
Butt.
Very good.
Wicked.
Knew, cool.
Fresh.
A silly or stupid person.
Airhead.
A male who plays a lot of sports.
Jock.
Completely cool.
Bad to the bones.
Nerd, loser.
Dweeb.
A car.
Ride.
Just kidding, I was joking.
Psych.
Man.
Dude.
To be romantic with.
To get with.
Leave me alone.
Go away.
I don't care.
Bite me.
Rich.
Loaded.
Relax.
Chill out.
Take a chill pill.
Information.
4-1-1.
Get angry.
Have a cow.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Airhead.
I did a girl in college and she was a real airhead.
She thought Europe was a country.
Airhead.
Bob is a real airhead.
All I can talk about is girls, parties, and drinking.
Airhead.
Can you believe that Nick called me an airhead?
He's such a jerk.
Wicked.
My brother is an amazing hockey player.
He has a wicked slap shot.
Wicked.
I just saw the new Terminator movie and it's wicked.
There is a comedian that does a wicked imitation of the president.
It's so funny.
Dweeb.
My classmates in high school thought I was a dweeb because I liked math.
Stop being a dweeb.
Let's go out tonight.
You can study tomorrow.
Dweeb.
Catherine has a new boyfriend and from what I hear, he's a real dweeb.
Loaded.
I wish I were like Bill Gates.
That guy is loaded.
Loaded.
Jason's father owns stock in most Fortune 500 companies.
That guy is loaded.
Loaded.
You want to buy a Ferrari?
Dude, you need to be loaded to even think about doing that.
To get with.
Tom has been dreaming of getting with Sarah, but she already has a boyfriend.
If you want to get with Lucy, you have to be nice and sweet.
To get with.
I heard you got with Daniel last night.
Is that true?