EnglishPod.com Jim, what's up, man?
Charlie, is that your ride?
It's butt ugly, dude.
Don't be an airhead.
This is a 1969 Chevy Impala.
I just need to fix it up a bit.
In a couple of months, this baby is gonna be wicked.
Not even.
Check it out.
Now that's a fresh ride.
Too bad the driver's a major dweeb.
Anyone can have a car like that if their daddy's loaded like his.
He's coming this way.
Be cool.
Hey, guys.
What do you think of my automobile?
Isn't it bad to the bone?
Word.
The ladies are gonna be lining up to get with you when they see you driving around in that car.
You really think so?
For sure.
Awesome.
Psych.
You totally fell for it.
You're a real scumbag, Charlie.
When I do the nasty with the prom queen, we'll see who has the last laugh.
Dude, don't have a cow.