EnglishPod.com Okay, that's fine.
Bye.
What happened?
That's it.
My lease is up.
I have to move.
What?
Why?
Can't you renew it?
The owner apparently is selling this place to make way for the construction of a parking lot.
Well, I can help you pack.
We should start looking for a new place for you ASAP.
I think I might move in with my parents for a couple of months until I can find something.
You know how hard it is to find a decent place around here.
I'm going to have to put most of my stuff in storage for a while.
Well, let me know if there's anything I can do to help out.
Actually, would you mind looking after my pet tarantula and snake for a couple of weeks?
Sure.