The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A contract granting use of property.
Lease To cause something to continue to be effective.
Renew Wrap up Pack To put articles in a case or container for moving.
Pack A building or an area.
Place A space for storing goods.
Storage Take care of Look after To create space for something else.
Make way for As soon as possible.
ASAP Good Decent Take care of Look after Let's try that faster.
Wrap up Pack Good Decent As soon as possible.
ASAP A contract granting use of property.
Lease Take care of Look after To put articles in a case or container for moving.
Pack To create space for something else.
Make way for Take care of Look after To cause something to continue to be effective.
Renew A building or an area.
Place A space for storing goods.
Storage Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Lease We are only leasing the apartment for one year.
Lease I didn't buy the car.
It's a lease vehicle.
Lease According to your lease, you'll have to pay a fine for destruction of property.
Make way for Make way for the king.
Make way for We'd better make way for that ambulance.
Make way for The company reduced its stock to make way for the new products.
ASAP I want you to clean up this mess ASAP.
ASAP Get back to me ASAP about the details of the deal.
ASAP ASAP If we don't finish this project ASAP, we could be fired.
Decent The city government was full of decent hard working people.
Decent The car is decent enough.
It gets me from point A to point B.
Decent This is a matter of common decency.
You should really apologize for your behavior.
Look after Look after We're looking after my friend's dog this week.
Look after Can you look after my daughter while I'm away?
Look after Look after I put Mary in charge of looking after the Jones account.