EnglishPod.com Good afternoon.
Did you call for a plumber?
Yes, yes I did.
Please come in.
I'm so glad you came.
This old house is falling apart.
Come into the bathroom.
See, here, there's water leaking everywhere.
I see.
Let me have a look.
It seems that your toilet is clogged and that's why it won't flush.
Let me just get my plunger.
No, that's not working either.
I suspect that there's some sort of foreign object in the pipe that's causing a blockage.
That's what's making your toilet overflow.
Oh, that must be because of my four-year-old daughter.
She is always flushing things down the toilet.
You know how kids are.
Yeah, I have a little one myself.
Anyway, these water pipes are really rusty, so they also should be changed.
That could be causing water to not drain completely.
That might lead to more problems in the future.
I would suggest fixing this faucet that isn't shutting off properly.
I could have it all finished by today if it's urgent.
That would be great.
Is it expensive?
Let's see.
I would say about $800.
What?
That's more than I make in a day and I'm a heart surgeon.