The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Break apart suddenly.
Burst.
A machine that moves liquid from one place to another.
Pump.
The part of the sink that water comes out of.
Tap.
An electric machine with a special purpose.
Appliance.
Water coming into a place where it shouldn't.
Flood.
Slowly forming a block in something.
Clog.
Something that stops another thing from passing through.
Blockage.
To cause a machine to stop operating.
Shut off.
Slowly break.
Falling apart.
Liquid or gas escaping from its container.
Leak.
Plumber.
To cause water to clean a toilet.
Flush.
A tool for unclogging toilets.
Plunger.
Have an idea about the reason for something.
Suspect.
Something that doesn't belong.
Foreign.
To flow over the edge of something.
Overflow.
Covered with a reddish-brown color.
Rusty.
To remove liquid from something by letting it flow.
Drain.
A device that controls the flow that comes out of.
Faucet.
To cause a machine to stop operating.
Shutting off.
Let's try that faster.
To cause water to clean a toilet.
Flush.
Break apart suddenly.
Burst.
Something that doesn't belong.
Foreign.
To flow over the edge of something.
Overflow.
Have an idea about the reason for something.
Suspect.
To cause a machine to stop operating.
Shut off.
Slowly break.
Falling apart.
Liquid or gas escaping from its container.
Leak.
Plumber.
Covered with a reddish-brown color.
Rusty.
A device that controls the flow that comes out of.
Faucet.
A tool for unclogging toilets.
Plunger.
An electric machine with a special purpose.
Appliance.
Water coming into a place where it shouldn't.
Flood.
Something that stops another thing from passing through.
Blockage.
Slowly forming a block in something.
Clog.
To cause a machine to stop operating.
Shutting off.
The part of the sink that water comes out of.
Tap.
A machine that moves liquid from one place to another.
Pump.
To remove liquid from something by letting it flow.
Drain.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Clog.
Heavy traffic clogged the freeways this morning.
It isn't a good idea to flush toilet paper down the toilet since it can clog it.
Clog.
All the water pipes are clogged with mud.
We won't have water for a week until the plumber unclogs them.
Blockage.
We had to wash the toilet paper down the toilet.
We had to call a plumber to clear out the blockage in the drain pipe.
Blockage.
Your arteries have serious blockage due to your unhealthy diet.
We must operate.
Blockage.
Judy couldn't come to work today due to some intestinal blockage, also known as constipation.
Leak.
This water bottle is leaking.
Bring me a cup quickly.
Leak.
You need to seal the toilet with silicon to prevent it from leaking when you flush.
Yesterday, a damaged nuclear reactor leaked radioactivity into the atmosphere.
Falling apart.
This house was built 100 years ago.
I guess that's why it's falling apart.
Falling apart.
I hate my car.
It's falling apart little by little and I only got it a year ago.
Falling apart.
I've been getting sick a lot lately.
My body is falling apart from old age.
Shutting off.
Be sure to shut off the gas when you leave for a vacation.
I can't shut off this valve.
It's stuck.
Shutting off.
During summer you should shut the hot water valve off to save energy.