EnglishPod.com Hi there.
I am looking for a new car.
I have this old Ford Pinto that I would like to trade in.
I see.
You are in luck this month because all of our 2010 models are on sale.
It is a perfect time to buy a new car since it's the end of the year.
Perfect.
I like this one.
That is the Ford Focus.
A very light but powerful vehicle.
It comes with dual side airbags, power steering and power windows.
Tinted windows and your choice of either automatic or manual transmission.
Sounds like a good car.
How many miles to the gallon?
It is a very fuel efficient vehicle giving you about 34 miles in the city and 40 on the highway.
That is really convenient.
Especially now the fuel prices are so high.
What's under the hood?
A very powerful 2.5 liter turbocharged engine.
Trust me, this car is fast.
Now for the most difficult question.
What is the price tag for this lovely vehicle?
Very affordable ma'am.
You can take it out of this lot today with zero down payment and no interest for the first year.
You can test drive it now and we can sign the papers when we get back.
Great.
Let's do it.