The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something that you sell as part of a payment for new.
Trade in Unit measuring distance Miles Something that can be turned into energy Fuel First payment that you pay when you buy something.
Down payment Money paid by a borrower for the borrowed money.
Interest Let's try that faster.
First payment that you pay when you buy something.
Down payment Something that you sell as part of a payment for new.
Trade in Money paid by a borrower for the borrowed money.
Interest Something that can be turned into energy.
Fuel Unit measuring distance Miles Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Trade in He traded his old car for a new one.
Trade in You can trade in your used home appliances and get new ones.
Trade in I am thinking about trading in my car.
Miles How many miles to the gallon does your car get?
Miles A Hummer only gets about 10 miles to the gallon.
Miles In the future we will have cars that can get 1000 miles to the gallon.
Fuel The Toyota Prius is one of the most fuel efficient vehicles on the market.
Fuel It is important to have a fuel efficient car in order to protect the environment.
Fuel Sports cars are usually the least fuel efficient cars on the market.
Down payment You need to give a 10% down payment on the house in order to lease it.
Down payment In order to reserve the property, you need to give us a 5% down payment.
Down payment We don't require you to pay a down payment at this time for this vehicle.
Interest The annual rate is 12%.
Interest You can buy this car at 0% interest for the first year.
Interest My credit card company charges me too much interest on my purchases.