EnglishPod.com Oh, I feel terrible.
I keep sneezing and my eyes are all watery.
What's wrong with me?
Wow, you're not dying, are you?
Looks like you have a cold.
You should take some medicine.
I don't think it's a cold.
I feel fine if I move a few feet away from my desk.
Maybe we should put you into quarantine.
Jokes aside, I think you might have an allergy.
An allergy?
I never thought about that.
I don't think I'm allergic to pollen, though, and I'm desensitized to bee stings after being stung so many times.
Hmm.
Ow!
Why did you chuck that peanut at me?
Just checking if you're allergic to peanuts.
I guess not.
Not funny.
I could have gone into anaphylactic shock.
Okay, my bad.
How about dust?
This office is full of it.
Yes, the whole office is dusty, yet I only feel affected near our desks.
You brought your cat into the office?
Yeah, it's Mr.
Snuffle's birthday today.
I didn't want him to be alone on his special day.
Ah, put it away!
I guess we found the problem.
You're allergic to cats.