The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The fertilizing element of flowering plants consisting of fine powdery yellowish greens or spores.
Pollen To lessen the sensitiveness of.
Desensitize.
Have allergy towards something.
Allergic.
To act on, produce an effect or change in.
Effect.
Dry, fine powdery material such as particles of dirt, earth or pollen.
Dust.
Severe and sometimes fatal allergic reaction to a foreign substance such as bee venom.
Anaphylactic shock.
A strict isolation imposed to prevent the spread of disease.
Quarantine.
Let's try that faster.
The fertilizing element of flowering plants consisting of fine powdery yellowish greens or spores.
Pollen.
A strict isolation imposed to prevent the spread of disease.
Quarantine.
Severe and sometimes fatal allergic reaction to a foreign substance such as bee venom.
Anaphylactic shock.
To act on, produce an effect or change in.
Effect.
To lessen the sensitiveness of.
Desensitize.
Have allergy towards something.
Allergic.
Dry, fine powdery material such as particles of dirt, earth or pollen.
Dust.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Allergic.
I'm not allergic to anything, lucky me.
My friend is allergic to certain flowers.
Allergic.
If I have an allergic reaction to peanuts, I may die.
Quarantine.
When we moved to Australia, we had to put our cat into quarantine.
I feel really sick, I hope I don't have to go into quarantine haha.
Quarantine.
I have to wait 6 months before I can collect my plant from quarantine.
Dust.
My house has so much dust in it, I really need to clean it.
I hate dust, it always makes me want to sneeze.
Dust.
This television is so dusty, I can't even watch it.
Desensitize.
After watching so many horror movies, I've become desensitized to violence.
I will desensitize my son's allergy to nuts by slowly entering them into his daily diet.
Desensitize.
I desensitize the spiciness of chillies by covering them in yoghurt.
Effect.
These horror movies never seem to affect me, I'm not scared at all.
I was deeply affected after the death of my brother.
Effect.
She seemed to affect her brother with her constant winching.