So, Michelle, let me introduce you to Maria.
She's my colleague from Brazil.
Maria, this is Michelle.
Hi, Michelle.
So what do you do here in Shanghai?
I mean, what work do you do?
I work in advertising right now.
How about you?
I'm actually in the wine business.
Oh, that sounds really great.
I love wine myself.
Is this your first time to Shanghai, Maria?
No, actually, I often visit.
I usually come to China for business at least once a year.
Also, I love the restaurants in Shanghai, so that's a good reason to come.
Me too.
Actually, there's a great Brazilian restaurant I recommend.
I mean, the food is delicious, but the service isn't so good.
I often like to get together with friends and have a great barbecue there.
We should go there together sometime.
Wonderful idea.
I'd love that.
Thank you.