The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Say something deserves to be chosen.
Recommend An act of help or assistance Service The person who works with you together Colleague A framework, as a grill or a spit, or a fireplace for cooking meat or vegetables over an open fire Barbecue To present, to another, so as to make acquainted Introduce Let's try that faster!
To present, to another, so as to make acquainted Introduce An act of help or assistance Service The person who works with you together Colleague Say something deserves to be chosen Recommend A framework, as a grill or a spit, or a fireplace for cooking meat or vegetables over an open fire Barbecue Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Introduce Let me introduce you to my parents.
I'm sure they will love you.
Introduce I should introduce you to my boss.
Maybe he will give you a job.
Introduce After being introduced by my friend, we started dating.
Now we are married.
The service at the restaurant was terrible, so we decided to leave.
Service Service The service provided to us by the local bank was terrific.
Service He decided to ask for the manager as he felt the service being provided was not good enough.
Barbecue I am having a barbecue later tonight and you're all invited.
Barbecue I like the bonding that happens between people at a barbecue.
Barbecue I think sausages, beer and friends are the best things for a barbecue.
Recommend I recommend you order the fish as it is a local delicacy.
Recommend I recommend you don't jump off the bridge.
Recommend It is recommended that women do not drink alcohol when they are pregnant.
Colleague My colleague is always stressed out from work.
Colleague I have a few colleagues that will be swimming in today's race.
Colleague Office The office is empty as all my colleagues are away on holiday.