EnglishPod.com Alright class, now that we're all dressed up, let's see what professions you chose.
Ah, I see a fireman, a police officer, a medic, and a lifeguard.
Can anyone tell me what these people have in common?
They save people from bad things?
That's right!
Now class, if something bad happened and you had to get help, do you know what phone number you would call?
9-1-1 Yes!
You would pick up the phone and dial 9-1-1.
What are some emergency situations in which you would need to dial 9-1-1?
If my grandpa had a heart attack.
If there was an accident.
If a robber broke into the house.
If the fire alarm went off.
I wouldn't call 9-1-1 if the fire alarm went off in my house.
The only time that ever happens is when we're having spaghetti for supper and my mom burns the garlic bread as usual.
Thanks for watching!