The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To put on fancy dress or a disguise.
Dress up.
An occupation requiring special training.
Profession.
Person who puts out fires and rescues people.
Fireman.
Policeman or policewoman.
Police officer.
Person who protects people from drowning.
Lifeguard.
To press the buttons to make a telephone call.
Dial.
To enter a house illegally, especially by force.
Break into.
To ring or sound loudly.
Go off.
Person who robs or steals.
Robber.
Painful condition where the heart stops beating.
Heart attack.
Take up by hand.
Pick up.
Let's try that faster.
Painful condition where the heart stops beating.
Heart attack.
To enter a house illegally, especially by force.
Break into.
Person who puts out fires and rescues people.
Fireman.
To ring or sound loudly.
Go off.
An occupation requiring special training.
Profession.
Take up by hand.
Pick up.
Policeman or policewoman.
Police officer.
Person who protects people from drowning.
Lifeguard.
To put on fancy dress or a disguise.
Dress up.
To press the buttons to make a telephone call.
Dial.
Person who robs or steals.
Robber.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Dress up.
I dressed up as a policeman for Halloween.
There was an event this weekend where all the guests had to dress up as angels.
Dress up.
I think it's cute when children dress up for Halloween.
Pick up.
If you have an emergency, pick up the phone and call the police.
Pick up these toys from the ground.
Pick up.
I dropped my pencil.
Can you bend over and pick it up for me, please?
Dial.
Pick up the phone and dial this number.
I wanted to dial but I couldn't remember the number.
Dial.
It's hard for me to dial a number on this phone.
The buttons are too small.
Break into.
We had a break-in last weekend.
The thief broke in the apartment and stole the TV.
Break into.
I had to break into my own car last night because I forgot the keys inside.
Go off.
My car alarm goes off whenever someone gets near my car.
The fire alarm went off in our school today.
Go off.
My alarm clock goes off every morning at six.