The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Move something, usually heavy.
Drag.
To attach someone or something with a rope or string.
Tie up.
Believe a lie.
Fall for it.
Easily believing something that is not true.
Easily fooled.
Gullible.
The truth is revealed.
The cat's out of the bag.
The male form of a witch.
Man that practices magic.
Wizard.
Tell the truth when you don't really want to.
Tell someone everything.
Spill the beans.
A state of not knowing where you are.
Confused.
Disoriented.
Person that can't tell the truth lies about anything.
Compulsive liar.
Used to say that someone is speaking or writing in a very direct and honest way.
Frank.
Let's try that faster.
A state of not knowing where you are.
Confused.
Disoriented.
Person that can't tell the truth lies about anything.
Compulsive liar.
Believe a lie.
Fall for it.
The truth is revealed.
The cat's out of the bag.
Easily believing something that is not true.
Easily fooled.
Gullible.
The male form of a witch.
Man that practices magic.
Wizard.
To attach someone or something with a rope or string.
Tie up.
Tell the truth when you don't really want to.
Tell someone everything.
Spill the beans.
Used to say that someone is speaking or writing in a very direct and honest way.
Frank.
Move something, usually heavy.
Drag.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Fall for it.
He might seem like a nice guy, but don't fall for it.
He's a jerk.
Fall for it.
I can't believe I fell for your lie.
I told my mom I was going to the library and she fell for it.
Pretend that you're my boyfriend and he'll go away.
I can't believe Lucy pretended to be sick.
You forgot my birthday.
Don't pretend that everything is okay.
Drag.
Help me drag my suitcase out of the way.
Stop dragging that chair.
You're making marks on the floor.
Drag.
Can you drag that table over here?
The cat's out of the bag.
I know you're a secret.
I'm sorry I let the cat out of the bag about your surprise party.
Drag.
John let the cat out of the bag so we know all about the surprise trip to Hawaii.
Gullible.
Sarah is so gullible.
She'll believe anything you say.
Gullible.
I'm not that gullible.
You can't fool me.
Gullible.
You believed that robber when he told you he was a police officer?
How can you be so gullible?