The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A document showing the identity of someone when outside his country.
Passport Register bags with the airline and give them to be put on the plane.
Check Piece of luggage, one bag Piece The bags that one can carry on to the plane.
Carry on luggage Between continents Intercontinental Get on the plane Board Very cheap, inexpensive Next to nothing Phrase used to indicate that something is very expensive.
An arm and a leg A device that senses the presence of metal.
Metal detector A pass that authorizes passengers to get on an airplane.
Boarding pass An instrument or machine for weighing.
Scale A short stop or break in a journey usually imposed by scheduling requirements.
Layover A trip from one place to another and back usually over the same route.
Round trip The bags that one can carry on to the plane.
Carry on luggage A document showing the identity of someone when outside his country.
Passport Register bags with the airline and give them to be put on the plane.
Check Between continents Intercontinental An instrument or machine for weighing Scale A device that senses the presence of metal.
Metal detector Piece of luggage, one bag.
Piece A short stop or break in a journey usually imposed by scheduling requirements.
Layover A pass that authorizes passengers to get on an airplane.
Boarding pass Very cheap, inexpensive.
Next to nothing A trip from one place to another and back, usually over the same route.
Round trip Phrase used to indicate that something is very expensive.
An arm and a leg Get on the plane.
Bored Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
It's absurd to think that the world will end in 2012.
He made one of the most absurd comments I have ever heard.
That's absurd.
I never cheated on my wife.
Next to nothing Do you like my new house?
It was so cheap.
It cost next to nothing.
Next to nothing Let's go to Thailand.
Tickets cost next to nothing right now.
Next to nothing The real estate agent charged me next to nothing for his commission.
So I got a really good deal.
An arm and a leg Be careful with the new carpet.
It cost me an arm and a leg.
An arm and a leg Can you believe how expensive homes are in New York?
It'll cost you an arm and a leg to buy a small house.
An arm and a leg We paid an arm and a leg for our new home theater and then it got stolen.
Check Frank was at the airport three hours before his flight because he had to check a lot of luggage.
Check Excuse me, is this the counter where I can check oversized luggage?
Check Most airlines only allow one piece of luggage to be checked.
How am I supposed to fit the dog in the car?
There are ten people in there already.
How am I supposed to get to work if her car is in the shop?
How are we supposed to know the answer to that?
It's impossible.