Next please.
Hello sir, may I see your passport please?
Yes, here you go.
Will you be checking any bags today?
Yes, I'd like to check three pieces.
I'm sorry sir, airline policy only allows two pieces of check luggage at 20 kilograms each plus one piece of carry-on luggage.
I will have to charge you extra for the additional suitcase.
What?
Why?
I'm taking an intercontinental flight.
I'm flying 16,000 kilometers.
How am I supposed to take only two 20 kilo bags?
That's absurd.
I'm sorry sir, there's nothing I can do.
You cannot board the flight with that large bag either.
Carry-on bags must fit in the overhead compartment or under your seat.
That bag is clearly too big.
Now I see.
You charge next to nothing for an international ticket.
When it comes to charging for any other small thing, you charge an arm and a leg.
So tell me miss, how much will I have to pay for all of this?
Let's see, 625 US dollars.
That's more than my round trip ticket!