EnglishPod.com and a mushroom soup for you.
Waiter!
I heard a cream of mushroom soup with asparagus.
This soup is obviously too runny and it's over seasoned.
It's completely inedible.
Okay, I do apologize for that.
Can I bring you another soup or would you like to order something else?
Take this foie gras back as well.
It's rubbery and completely overcooked.
And look at the portion size!
How can you charge $25 for a sliver of duck liver?
Right away, sir.
Honey, come on.
The foie gras was fine.
Why are you making such a big deal?
Are you trying to get our meal comped again?
What do you mean?
We are paying for this and I'm shelling out my hard-earned bucks!
I expect value from money!
Here you are, sir.
I hope it is alright now.
The chef has prepared it especially for you.
Yes, fine.
Honey, are you alright?
Oh, God!