The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A bad second taste.
A bad aftertaste.
A strong unpleasant taste that is opposite of sweet.
Bitter.
A strong unpleasant smell.
Rank.
A rotten taste or smell.
Rancid.
Not appealing, not attractive or tasty.
Unappealing.
Little dish people have before meal.
Appetizer.
Place of business like a restaurant or hotel.
Establishment.
Work done by someone to serve customers.
Service.
The list containing your choices of dishes.
Order.
A food made from the livers of geese.
Foie gras.
More liquid than expected.
Runny.
Too salty.
Over-seasoned.
Cannot be eaten.
Inedible.
Difficult to chew.
Rubbery.
Be cooked over time.
Overcooked.
The amount of food that is served to a person.
Portion size.
A small thin piece.
Sliver.
Get very upset about something small.
Make a big deal.
Be given to customers for free.
Comp.
To spend money.
Shell out.
Money you work hard for.
Hard earned.
Let's try that faster.
Work done by someone to serve customers.
Service.
Place of business like a restaurant or hotel.
Establishment.
More liquid than expected.
Runny.
The amount of food that is served to a person.
Portion size.
A strong unpleasant smell.
Rank.
Difficult to chew.
Rubbery.
Too salty.
Over-seasoned.
Not appealing, not attractive or tasty.
Unappealing.
Be given to customers for free.
Comp.
Get very upset about something small.
Make a big deal.
A strong unpleasant taste that is opposite of sweet.
Bitter.
A bad second taste.
A bad aftertaste.
A food made from the livers of geese.
Foie gras.
The list containing your choices of dishes.
Order.
Be cooked over time.
Overcooked.
Cannot be eaten.
Inedible.
To spend money.
Shell out.
Money you work hard for.
Hard earned.
A rotten taste or smell.
Rancid.
A small thin piece.
Sliver.
Little dish people have before meal.
Appetizer.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Inedible.
This fish tastes terrible.
It's completely inedible.
Inedible.
If you leave meat out of the refrigerator for too long, it will be inedible.
Are you sure you can eat that?
Aren't the flower decorations on cakes inedible?
Rubbery.
This steak is so rubbery I can barely chew it.
If the meat is so rubbery, why don't you send it back?
Rubbery.
The foie gras is so rubbery.
I bet it would bounce on the floor if I dropped it.
Sliver.
No, John's on a diet.
He'll just have a sliver of cake and no ice cream.
Sliver.
I'm really full, but it looks so delicious.
Can you just cut me a sliver?
Sliver.
You call this sliver of beef on my plate a meal?
There's almost nothing here.
Hard earned.
Doesn't it feel good when you use your hard earned bucks to buy something you've always wanted?
I refuse to spend my hard earned bucks on someone who won't appreciate it.
Hard earned.
Richard is such a great guy.
Every year he would donate his hard earned bucks to a different charity.
I can't believe I got a parking ticket yesterday.
Now I'm going to have to shell out $75 bucks.
It's me and my girlfriend's 5 year anniversary on Saturday.
So I'm going to shell out for a nice dinner and a pair of nice earrings.
Tommy loved to party.
Last night he shelled out $300 buying people drinks.