EnglishPod.com Take the theory of the Big Bang.
How is it possible that all of the stuff in the universe comes from an explosion?
That's no better than Atlas carrying the globe on his back, or African myths about turtles and stuff.
Turtles?
Whatever.
Look, all that's required for the creation of matter is an imbalance of particles and antiparticles.
At least, that's what the math says.
Math shmath!
What's the evidence?
There is evidence.
You know Edwin Hubble, the guy who in the early 20th century was the first scientist to measure the drift of matter in the universe, thus advancing notions of an expanding universe.
What would it be expanding from?
Well, the Big Bang, duh.
Anyway, it's just a theory.
Why do people go around touting theories?
Where's the rigor in that?
Dude, don't equivocate.
A theory only becomes a theory after withstanding, rigorous testing.
You slept through class, didn't you?
You're making my head hurt again.
Quit with the questions.