The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
What is happening?
An informal greeting.
What's up?
Something that is extremely difficult to deal with or withstand.
Killer A set of statements or principles devised to explain a group of facts or phenomena.
Theory The theory that a cosmic explosion caused the origin of the universe.
Big Bang The substance of which something is made.
Material.
Matter The situation where there is an unequal amount of different things.
Imbalance Any one tiny part of matter.
Particle A particle that has the same mass as another particle but has opposite values for its other properties.
Antiparticle Ideas or concepts Notion A state of something being very exact.
Rigor Use vague language so as to deceive someone.
Equivocate Surviving a difficult experience or trouble.
Withstand The scientific study of matter in outer space, especially the positions, dimensions, distribution, motion, composition, energy and evolution of celestial bodies and phenomenon.
Astronomy A region of space resulting from the collapse of a star with extremely high gravitational field.
Black hole A small, faint, very dense star.
White dwarf The tendency of all matter and energy in the universe to evolve toward a state of inert uniformity.
Entropy A point of infinite density and infinitesimal volume at which space and time become infinitely distorted according to the theory of general relativity.
Singularity A seemingly contradictory statement that may nonetheless be true.
Paradox Let's try that faster.
The substance of which something is made.
Material Matter Surviving a difficult experience or trouble.
Withstand Use vague language so as to deceive someone.
Equivocate A particle that has the same mass as another particle but has opposite values for its other properties.
Antiparticle Any one tiny part of matter.
Particle The situation where there is an unequal amount of different things.
Imbalance A set of statements or principles devised to explain a group of facts or phenomena.
Theory The scientific study of matter in outer space, especially the positions, dimensions, distribution, motion, composition, energy and evolution of celestial bodies and phenomenon.
Astronomy A point of infinite density and infinitesimal volume at which space and time become infinitely distorted according to the theory of general relativity.
Singularity A small, faint, very dense star.
White dwarf The theory that a cosmic explosion caused the origin of the universe.
Big Bang A seemingly contradictory statement that may, nonetheless, be true.
Paradox What is happening?
An informal greeting.
What's up?
Ideas or concepts.
Notion The tendency of all matter and energy in the universe to evolve toward a state of inert uniformity.
Entropy Something that is extremely difficult to deal with or withstand.
Killer A state of something being very exact.
Rigor A region of space resulting from the collapse of a star with extremely high gravitational field.
Black hole Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
So you can see that we've studied the fossil record and thus we can conclude that evolution is a fact.
He broke severe company policies, thus we had to fire him.
I did not receive the documents on time, thus I was unable to send them to you.
But we examined the data rigorously.
How can there be an error?
It's simply not possible.
Don't worry, the nuclear reactor went through rigorous testing so we can be sure that it is safe.
She is a professor who is known for her scientific rigor.
The dieting experts are touting the benefits of the latest weight loss program, but I think it's just a fad.
This drug is being touted as a miracle cure.
The release of the much touted web browser will revolutionize the way you use the internet.
Equivocate When asked about his plan for cutting taxes, the presidential candidate did not equivocate.
Equivocate In the interview, when I asked him about why he left his last job, he started to equivocate.
Equivocate Stop equivocating.
Tell me clearly what you mean.
Notion Where did you get this notion that the sun travels around the earth?
Notion Notion Scientists are advancing the notion that socialization plays a role in language learning.
Notion That's an absurd notion.
It's absolutely not true.