EnglishPod.com Welcome to Adventure Tours.
How may I help you?
I want to book a tour with Adventure Sports.
Excellent!
Our company has more than 10 years of experience in the Adventure Tourism and Sports field.
Let me show you some options.
This is our most popular choice.
Our river guides will take you on a white water rafting trip followed by a ride in a hot air balloon.
I don't really think I'm ready to throw myself down a river full of jagged rocks and a rubber boat.
Or go up in the air in a wicker basket held up by an oversized balloon.
What else do you have?
Well, in that case we can take you hang gliding with one of our experienced instructors.
It's the closest you can get to flying.
What?
You mean strap myself to a flimsy kite?
No thank you.
Next?
Okay, well why don't you tell me a little bit more about what you would like.
We have everything from mountain biking to rock climbing to street luge.
I'm thinking something exciting but safer.
I have the perfect option.
This package will take you on a hiking trip through the Himalayas for three days and afterwards there's a dog sledding journey.
That's more like it!