The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A huge balloon risen up by hot air.
Hot air balloon.
In an area of work study.
In the field.
Having a sharp surface.
Jagged.
Larger than what is listed.
Oversized.
If something said earlier is true.
In that case.
Gliding in a hang glider.
Hang gliding.
The easiest way, the most likely thing.
The closest thing you can get to.
Ride a bicycle designed for riding in mountainous.
Mountain biking.
The sport of scaling rock masses on mountainsides.
Rock climbing.
The sport of descending a steep road.
Street luge.
The sport of rafting down fast flowing rivers.
White water rafting.
Let's try that faster.
The sport of scaling rock masses on mountainsides.
Rock climbing.
If something said earlier is true.
In that case.
Gliding in a hang glider.
Hang gliding.
The sport of rafting down fast flowing rivers.
White water rafting.
Having a sharp surface.
Jagged.
Ride a bicycle designed for riding in mountainous.
Mountain biking.
The easiest way, the most likely thing.
The closest thing you can get to.
In an area of work study.
In the field.
A huge balloon risen up by hot air.
Hot air balloon.
The sport of descending a steep road.
Street luge.
Larger than what is listed.
Oversize.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
In the field.
I've been working in the medical field for 20 years now.
I know it inside and out.
In the field.
He's only worked in the field for less than a year.
So I have no idea why they hired him as the new supervisor.
In the field.
They tested the new theory for two years in the field before publishing their findings.
White water rafting.
I clung to the sides of the raft as we headed for the rapids and silently wished I had never signed up for white water rafting.
She has white water rafted many many times before so you should trust her to get through the journey safely.
White water rafting.
The summer camp I'll be attending is offering a white water rafting excursion.
Jagged.
I clung to the bridge as I looked down at the jagged rocks hundreds of feet beneath me.
As I picked up the broken glass the jagged edges cut into my hand.
Jagged.
The tailor began to cut off the jagged edges of the piece of fabric.
Oversized.
The oversized coat engulfed me.
I began to fall asleep in the oversized armchair.
Oversized.
In the oil fields in Alberta, oversized trucks three stories tall transport oil sands from the field to the refinery.
The closest thing you can get to.
Eating McDonald's is the closest thing you can get to eating Western food in China.
Descending a steep incline on a roller coaster is the closest you can get to experiencing zero gravity without having to get on a jet plane.
The closest thing you can get to.
Driving this car is the closest I can get to riding in luxury for under 30 grand.