The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Not yet completed.
Need more time.
Still working on.
Suggest.
Would recommend.
Free.
Complementary.
To choose.
Pick.
Go with.
To get quickly.
Grab.
Let's try that faster.
Not yet completed.
Need more time.
Still working on.
To get quickly.
Grab.
Suggest.
Would recommend.
To get quickly.
Grab.
To choose.
Pick.
Go with.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Still working on.
Have you decided what to do tonight?
I'm still working on it.
Complementary.
Would you like a complementary dessert?
Go with.
I'll go with the red dress instead of the blue one.
Grab.
Let's grab some beers after work.
Go with.
I'll go with the red dress instead of the blue one.
Grab.
Let's grab some beers after work.