The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A real or specific solution to a problem.
Concrete solutions.
Increase sales.
Drive sales.
In the industry.
In the market.
Be as good as or better than other companies in the same industry.
To match the competitors.
Will not work, will not be approved.
Will never fly.
Something done to make people aware of a product.
Promotion.
Will arrive very soon.
Be here any minute.
Thinking about.
To consider.
Excellent.
Brilliant.
As good as or better than others of the same type.
Competitive.
Make sales successfully.
Win sales.
Plans for a company's sales activities.
Sales strategy.
The process a customer goes through when deciding to buy a product.
Sales cycle.
To sell more than others.
To outsell.
When a customer buys the same brand over and over.
Customer loyalty.
Let's try that faster.
Excellent.
Brilliant.
Will arrive very soon.
Be here any minute.
To sell more than others.
To outsell.
Will not work, will not be approved.
Will never fly.
The process a customer goes through when deciding to buy a product.
Sales cycle.
Something done to make people aware of a product.
Promotion.
In the industry.
In the market.
Increase sales.
Drive sales.
Be as good as or better than other companies in the same industry.
To match the competitors.
As good as or better than others of the same type.
Competitive.
Make sales successfully.
Win sales.
Plans for a company's sales activities.
Sales strategy.
When a customer buys the same brand over and over.
Customer loyalty.
Thinking about.
To consider.
A real or specific solution to a problem.
Concrete solutions.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Drive sales.
If we want to drive sales, I think we need to spend more time training our salespeople.
The most important thing for us right now is to focus on driving sales.
Drive sales.
I think if we increase our marketing budget, it will help us to drive sales in the fourth quarter.
I expect each of you to come to the meeting tomorrow with concrete solutions for our recruitment problem.
Dale, have you come up with any concrete solutions?
I'm sorry, but I just can't offer any concrete solutions right now.
Promotion.
We can't have a sales promotion right now because our costs are too high.
The department store is offering a promotion.
Everything is 50% off.
Let's go shopping.
Promotion.
A two-for-one promotion might be a way to attract new customers.
We guarantee that we can match the competitors' lowest price.
It's impossible for us to match the competitors.
Our costs are just too high.
Do you think we can match the competitors' quality and still keep our price low?
In the market.
EnglishPod is the best podcast in the market.
iPods are the most popular MP3 players in the market.
In the market.
Our product is the cheapest in the market.
We'll never fly.
This marketing plan will never fly.
We just don't have enough money for it.
We'll never fly.
I like that idea, but it'll never fly with management.
Brad told me his idea for a film script, but the story will never fly.
It's not interesting enough.
Be here any minute.
Hurry up!
The bus will be here any minute.
Be here any minute.
Nick just called.
He said he should be here any minute.
Be here any minute.
Is everything prepared for the meeting?
The CEO will be here any minute.
To consider.
We're considering a sales promotion.
I think we need to consider a new sales strategy.
To consider.
Have you considered reducing the price?
Brilliant.
That's a brilliant idea.
This is a brilliant marketing plan.
Brilliant.
What a brilliant suggestion.
Thanks Roger.