EnglishPod.com Alright people, we're holding this meeting today because we've got to do something about our sales and we need to do it now.
I want concrete solutions.
How do you plan to drive sales?
Well, in fact, we're the most expensive in the market, so maybe we need to lower our prices to match the competitors?
Lower our prices.
Not very creative.
It'll never fly with Swan.
What kind of thinking is that?
Anyone have a better plan?
Natalie?
Perhaps a promotion.
Maybe a two-for-one offer or something like that.
Wow, that's the same thing.
Bad idea.
Really bad idea.
Damn it, people, come on!
Think!
The CEO will be here any minute.
Hello, Mr.
Swan.
Oh, Mr.
Hello, Mr.
Swan.
Do we have any ideas yet?
Yes, Mr.
Swan.
We were kind of considering a two-for-one offer to get more competitive.
A two-for-one promotion.
Hmm.
I kind of like the sound of that.
It sounds like something we should consider.
Yeah, exactly!
That's just what I was thinking.
In fact, it's a brilliant idea.
I'm glad we thought of that.
Very creative.