The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To educate kids at home by a parent or tutor.
Home school Firstly First of all To do research or instruct yourself on a topic.
Read up To set apart from others, place alone.
Isolate Meeting, talking, doing activities with people.
Social interaction A meeting or class between two people.
One-on-one A quality that makes someone effective or useful.
Strengths The quality or state of being weak.
Weakness To mention or open for discussion.
Bring something up.
Let's try that faster.
To set apart from others, place alone.
Isolate To mention or open for discussion.
Bring something up.
A quality that makes someone effective or useful.
Strengths Meeting, talking, doing activities with people.
Social interaction A meeting or class between two people.
One-on-one To do research or instruct yourself on a topic.
Read up To educate kids at home by a parent or tutor.
Home school The quality or state of being weak.
Weakness Firstly First of all Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Home school I have many good friends that were homeschooled.
Home school Bill and Diane are homeschooling their children.
Home school Many people decide to homeschool their children because of religious reasons.
Read up I have been reading up on the Big Bang Theory.
Read up I need to read up on this subject for my class tomorrow.
Read up I was reading up on Roman history and I found it to be very interesting.
Isolate Isolate I feel isolated living in this small town.
Isolate That tiger is isolated from the rest because he was attacking them.
Isolate Isolate They isolated the political prisoners from the other inmates.
One-on-one We will have a one-on-one meeting this afternoon.
One-on-one Let's play a game of one-on-one basketball.
One-on-one I have a tutor that teaches me Chinese one-on-one every afternoon.
Bring something up Please don't bring up our personal problems with your parents.
Bring something up I hate to bring up the topic, but I really need you to pay me.
Bring something up I will bring up your doubts with the president at a later time.
Thank you for watching.