EnglishPod.com I think we should homeschool our children when we decide to have kids.
What?
Why?
Well, our public schools here are not very good and private schools are just too expensive.
I have been reading up on some homeschooling and it has a lot of advantages.
Like what?
I think that by doing something like that we would be isolating our children from social interaction.
Well, first of all, I would be able to teach them everything they learn in school in a more relaxed and fun way.
I also think that having a 101 class is much better since you can focus more on his or her strengths or weaknesses.
I think neither your parents or mine would agree to such an idea.
I'll bring it up over Sunday brunch.
Good luck with that.