The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To turn out to be.
Amount to.
In a sudden and extreme way.
Dramatically.
Represent.
Stand.
To get something as a result of something.
Reap.
Situation in which people compete in an unpleasant way.
Cutthroat.
Let's try that faster.
To turn out to be.
Amount to.
Situation in which people compete in an unpleasant way.
Cutthroat.
Represent.
Stand.
In a sudden and extreme way.
Dramatically.
To get something as a result of something.
Reap.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Amount to.
When we add in the figures from Q4, our annual sales revenue amounts to 1,757,000 RMB.
The grand total amounts to 345,000.
Amount to.
My father always said if I didn't study hard enough I'd never amount to anything.
Dramatically.
The number of employees rose dramatically last spring.
I'm sorry to report that the number of safety incidents has risen dramatically these past two months.
Dramatically.
We hope this marketing campaign will push sales to rise dramatically.
Stand.
The current unemployment rate stands at about 4.5%.
We can see that in July, membership rates stood at about 6,200.
Stand.
The price of oil is expected to stand at $93 per barrel in November.
Cutthroat.
I had no idea the music industry was so cutthroat.
This is a highly competitive cutthroat market.
Cutthroat.
He eventually lost his job because of his cutthroat business tactics.
Reap.
It just goes to show you, you reap what you sow.
That's so unfair.
George did all the work, but Emily is reaping all the rewards.
Reap.
Our company is really reaping the benefits of the current housing situation.