EnglishPod.com.
As all of you are well aware, competition in the laptop computer sector is intense.
We continue to fight with our competitors for market share, and this is the case both in the developed markets in the West as well as more developing markets in Asia and Africa.
You may ask yourself, why is this market so cutthroat?
Well, the answer is simple.
There is a huge untapped potential market out there, with a huge untapped potential for profit.
If I bring up the first graph here, it shows the increase in terms of number of computer owners across the globe.
As you can see, in the 1980s, computer ownership amounted to around 0.5% of the total world population.
Since the 1990s, computer ownership has risen dramatically.
In the new millennium, we saw an even larger explosion in computer owners, with figures rising to around 4-5%, an increase of 1,000% compared with the 1980s.
If we move on to discuss the figures for China specifically, we can see in chart B that the overall figure for computer ownership stands at around 60 million, which represents a huge increase in a very short time period.
Now of course, 60 million is just a drop in the ocean if you compare the total population of China.
And this is a key reason why the personal computer market is such a hot market.
For us at Alpha, and of course for all of our competitors as well, we have millions of potential customers who are looking to join the internet generation.
If we do this right, we really can reap huge rewards in a very short time frame.
I'd now like to move on to discuss the X420 brand itself and compare and contrast with some of our key competitors.