EnglishPod.com Excuse me, sir.
This is the express checkout lane for people who have 15 items or fewer.
It looks like you have more than 15 items there.
Oh, come on.
I have 16 items.
Cut me some slack, will ya?
Fine.
Please place your items on the belt and push your shopping cart through.
Do you prefer paper or plastic?
Plastic.
I also have a couple of coupons.
No problem.
I'll take those.
Sir, these coupons expired yesterday.
Darn.
Oh well.
I guess it's just not my day.
Thanks anyway.
Do you have a club card or will it be cash?
Yeah, I got a club card.
Here you go.
Will this be debit or credit?
Debit, please.
Also, could I get cash back?
$50 would be great.
Yeah, sure.
Your total is $78.33.
Here's your receipt.
Have a nice day.