The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The place you line up to pay for the things you want.
Checkout lane.
To supply a shop with merchandise.
Stock.
Don't be so strict.
Bend the rules.
Cut me some slack.
A place where goods are stored prior to their sale or distribution.
Warehouse.
To no longer be valid after a period of time.
Expire.
Domestic birds such as chickens, turkeys, ducks, or geese Raised for meat or eggs.
Poultry.
A person, usually a teenager, that works at a supermarket and places groceries that a person buys in plastic or paper bags.
Bag boy.
Charging more money to your card in order to receive cash back.
Cash back.
An arrangement of numbers and parallel lines on a package which can be electronically scanned at a checkout to give the price of the goods.
Barcode.
A lot of bad things happened to me today.
It is just not my day.
Let's try that faster.
A place where goods are stored prior to their sale or distribution.
Warehouse.
A lot of bad things happened to me today.
It is just not my day.
The place you line up to pay for the things you want.
Checkout lane.
Don't be so strict.
Bend the rules.
Cut me some slack.
Charging more money to your card in order to receive cash back.
Cash back.
An arrangement of numbers and parallel lines on a package which can be electronically scanned at a checkout to give the price of the goods.
Barcode.
To no longer be valid after a period of time.
Expire.
Domestic birds such as chickens, turkeys, ducks, or geese raised for meat or eggs.
Poultry.
A person, usually a teenager, that works at a supermarket and places groceries that a person buys in plastic or paper bags.
Bag boy.
To supply a shop with merchandise.
Stock.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Checkout lane.
Excuse me, can you tell me where the checkout lane is?
There are so many people waiting in line at the checkout lane.
Checkout lane.
I hate coming to this grocery store because they don't have enough checkout lanes.
Cut me some slack.
Cut me some slack, I'm only two minutes late.
My wife just had a baby and I'm so tired.
Cut me some slack, I'll send you the report tomorrow.
Cut me some slack.
Emily had a really bad week, I think you should cut her some slack.
Expire.
I'm sorry sir, this credit card expired five years ago, you can't use it anymore.
My driver's license expires in a month, so I have to get it renewed.
Expire.
Don't drink that, the milk has expired.
Cash back.
I wanted to get cash back at the grocery store, but the cashier said they had a policy against it.
Can I get cash back if I pay with my credit card?
Cash back.
Cash back is the most convenient way to get cash in case of an emergency without paying additional fees.
It is just not my day.
I spilled coffee in the morning and got a flat tire on my way home.
It's just not my day today.
It is just not my day.
Today was just not my day.
I have too many things to do and so little time.
It is just not my day.
I need a massage.
Today was just not my day.
We had a lot of problems with our new client.