EnglishPod.com And, well, I think we need to start seeing other people.
What?
Why?
I mean, we've had our ups and downs, and we have the occasional disagreement, but we're happy together, aren't we?
That's just it.
I'm not happy anymore, Tim.
It's not you, it's me.
I know that I can be hard to deal with, and you're a great guy.
You're the type of guy that any woman would kill for.
So, what are you saying?
You're breaking up with me because I'm perfect?
Tim, you are too good for me.
You deserve someone who can make you smile and make you happy the way that you made me happy.
I could say that I'll be all you need, but that'd be a lie.
I know I'd only hurt you.
I know I'd only make you cry.
Baby, come on, don't do this to me.
Whatever it is, we can work it out.
Just give me another chance.
I know that we can get through this, but we gotta stick together.
Don't leave me.
I can't, Tim.
I hope someday you can find some way to understand I'm only doing this for you.
I don't really want to go, but deep in my heart, I know this is the kindest thing to do.
Laura.
Here are your keys.
I'll send my sister to pick up the rest of my things next week.
I'm sorry, Tim.
I wish you all the best, and I hope that one day we can meet again.
I'll always love you.
Goodbye.
Make you cry.
I'm not the one you need.
I love you.
Goodbye.