EnglishPod.com What do you want based on the genre, title, or if you know the author, I can point you towards the right direction.
I'm looking for a book that has nursery rhymes.
That would be in our children's section, that bookshelf there on the right.
Okay, I would like to check out these books.
Do you have a library card?
No, how do I get one?
I just need to see a driver's license or a utility bill to prove that you are a resident of this state.
Here you go.
So, you're all set.
You can have these books for two weeks.
If you need to have them longer, you can bring them here to renew them.
If you don't, you get charged ten cents a day for each book.
Okay, thanks.