The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Chinese medical practice or procedure that treats illness or provides local anesthesia by the insertion of needles at specified sites of the body.
acupuncture A point on the skin that is extremely sensitive to pressure because of the presence of pressure-sensing organs.
pressure point An act or manner of treating.
treatment A small slender rod-like instrument, usually of polished steel, with a sharp point at one end.
needle The process of drawing blood from the body and the application of a cupping glass.
cupping The soft substance of a human or other animal body, consisting of muscle and fat.
flesh A drug, treatment or anything else that relieves pain.
painkiller Let's try that faster.
A small slender rod-like instrument, usually of polished steel, with a sharp point at one end.
needle The soft substance of a human or other animal body, consisting of muscle and fat.
flesh Chinese medical practice or procedure that treats illness or provides local anesthesia by the insertion of needles at specified sites of the body.
A point on the skin that is extremely sensitive to pressure because of the presence of pressure-sensing organs.
pressure point A drug, treatment or anything else that relieves pain.
painkiller The process of drawing blood from the body and the application of a cupping glass.
cupping treatment Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
treatment Don't worry, my father's treatment will make you feel better in no time.
treatment This seems like a really weird treatment.
treatment I'm skeptical of any treatments that are not of western origin.
painkiller I have such a bad headache, I need some painkillers.
painkiller This works really well as a painkiller.
painkiller You shouldn't rely on painkillers all the time as you may develop an unhealthy addiction.
pressure point My brother would not be quiet so I grabbed him by a pressure point to make him.
pressure point Massaging the pressure points is a great way to relieve stress.
pressure point You have to be careful with pressure points as it could really hurt someone.
acupuncture acupuncture I'm scared to go get acupuncture.
I don't like needles.
acupuncture Since I got acupuncture last week, I no longer have any pain in my back.
acupuncture acupuncture I attempted acupuncture on my dad but I accidentally put a needle in his eye.
cupping I'm being accused of beating my husband because he is all bruised from cupping.
cupping cupping Cupping is a great method to improve energy flow.
cupping I'm going to get cupping done today to help cure my cold.