EnglishPod.com What's wrong?
I have a headache.
These past few days I've been living off painkillers.
Man, I feel like my head is going to explode.
You should get acupuncture treatment.
My mom was always having headache issues and it was acupuncture that cured her.
The results are too slow.
On top of that, just the thought of smoking needles poking into my flesh frightens me.
They don't just randomly stick you.
They find your pressure points.
The heat allows the body to immediately respond to the treatment, restoring the body's chi.
But I get scared the moment I see a needle.
How could I stand having needles in my body for hours on end?
The needles are very thin and as long as the doctor's technique is good and the patient himself is relaxed, it won't hurt.
On the contrary, it will actually alleviate pain.
Now there are high tech needles that are micro-thin.
They don't hurt at all.
However, if you are really scared of acupuncture, scraping or cupping are also options.
Scraping is too terrifying.
When they finish scraping, your body is all red as if you were just tortured.
Cupping is the same.
Your body ends up with red circles all over it.
It looks like someone beat you up.
This only signifies that the toxins have left the body.
Actually, there's only discomfort during the treatment process.
Once it's over, you'll feel very comfortable.
Chinese medicine is strange.
The patients are already ill and then the doctor makes them suffer more.
This is the only way to get at the problem.
Anyway, if you want to relieve the pain, you are just going to have to be tough and do it.
Forget it.
I don't want to inflict any more pain on myself.
In a little while, I'll go and buy some more painkillers and take a nap.