The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word Charge.
Make someone pay.
Costing.
Being informed of something.
Please note that.
A statement of the price of an item or service.
Quotation.
Go with the safest option.
Play it safe.
Introduction.
I am writing to.
Let's try that faster.
Go with the safest option.
Play it safe.
A statement of the price of an item or service.
Quotation.
Being informed of something.
Please note that.
Charge.
Make someone pay.
Costing.
Introduction.
I am writing to.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Please note that.
Please note that the deadline for this project is next Monday.
Please note that we require full payment before the magazine goes to print.
Please note that.
Please note that the meeting has been changed to Monday at 3pm.
Quotation.
The quotation seems very high.
Why is it so expensive?
Quotation.
I'll send you a quote for the project next week.
The other company gave us a much lower quote.
Play it safe.
Let's play it safe and finish this project before the deadline.
This is a really important account so we need to play it safe.
Play it safe.
The clients want a really interesting and cool design so let's not play it too safe.
I am writing to.
I am writing to follow up on our meeting last week.
I am writing to confirm the details for the full page ad you requested.
I am writing to.
I am writing to request some changes to the layout for the ad.
Costing.
Can you please include the final costing in the proposal?
The costing of the project will be finished next week.
Costing.
I have a few questions about the costing for this advertisement.