EnglishPod.com Let's go out tomorrow night.
We can go to a bar and try to find you a girlfriend.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'm just not good with approaching someone and starting up a conversation.
Maybe you just need a few pick-up lines, you know, to break the ice.
Pick-up lines don't work.
Come on, you can just walk up to a girl and say, If you were a booger, I'd pick you first.
What?
Come on, that's just lame.
No girl would fall for that.
Fine, then you can say, So there you are.
I've been looking all over for you, the woman of my dreams.
That's a good one.
I think that's pretty funny.
Yeah, so you make her laugh, you make a fool of yourself a little bit, and then you buy her a drink.
Okay, how does this sound?
I was so enchanted by your beauty that I ran into that wall over there.
So I'm going to need your name and number for insurance purposes.
Nice.
Let's go.