The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Meet for a game or battle.
Encounter In the future.
Ahead of someone.
A highly energetic, strong team.
Powerhouse To reach the latter stages of a selection or process by competing successfully in earlier rounds.
Qualify In their best condition.
In top shape.
Hit the ball to start the game.
Serve To pass a volleyball by redirecting it with the forearms.
Bump The action of putting the ball in the air so it can be driven to the opponent's court.
Set Strongly hit the ball to the opponent's court using the palm of the hand.
Spike To foresee and act in advance of.
Anticipate A serve with the ball firstly thrown overhead and then the player jumping to hit it.
Jump serve The ball touches the net in a serve but still crosses into the opponent's court.
Let serve A pause during the game.
Time out When the team that served the ball loses the rally causing the other team to serve the next point.
Side out A mishit when a player attempts to hit or spike the ball with an open hand and nearly misses the ball.
With The ability to prevent the ball from touching one's court after a spike or attack particularly a ball that is nearly touching the ground.
Dig It is the practice of throwing a coin in the air to resolve a dispute between two parties.
Coin toss A contest or game ending in a tie.
Draw Let's try that faster.
A highly energetic strong team.
Powerhouse To foresee and act in advance of.
Anticipate To reach the latter stages of a selection or process by competing successfully in earlier rounds.
Qualify In their best condition.
In top shape The ability to prevent the ball from touching one's court after a spike or attack particularly a ball that is nearly touching the ground.
Dig It is the practice of throwing a coin in the air to resolve a dispute between two parties.
Coin toss To pass a volleyball by redirecting it with the forearms.
Bump In the future Ahead of someone A pause during the game.
Time out A serve with the ball firstly thrown overhead and then the player jumping to hit it.
Jump serve Hit the ball to start the game.
Serve When the team that served the ball loses the rally causing the other team to serve the next point.
Side out A contest or game ending in a tie.
Draw A miss hit when a player attempts to hit or spike the ball with an open hand and nearly misses the ball.
With Meet for a game or battle.
Encounter Strongly hit the ball to the opponent's court using the palm of the hand.
Spike The ball touches the net in a serve but still crosses into the opponent's court.
Let serve The action of putting the ball in the air so it can be driven to the opponent's court.
Set Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Powerhouse Powerhouse Our company is considered to be a powerhouse in the manufacturing industry.
Powerhouse How did Austria become a powerhouse of soccer in the 1920s?
Powerhouse China has grown into an economic powerhouse in the past decade.
In top shape Sarah ran a marathon this weekend and won.
She is really in top shape.
In top shape Mount Everest You have to be in top shape to climb Mount Everest.
In top shape Our company had great sales this quarter so we are in top shape.
Anticipate We thought we could see all the animals in the zoo but we didn't anticipate there would be so many people.
Anticipate I anticipated it would rain today so I brought my umbrella.
Anticipate Set A businessman must try to anticipate what his customers will want.
Set The setter must set the ball precisely so the other player can hit it.
Set Set You are setting the ball too low.
I can't hit it.
Set That was a great set.
The player jumped and hit the ball perfectly.
I was almost late to the sales meeting but managed to make it on time.
Sarah was sick but she managed to make it to work today.
I am sorry.
I can't make it to your party tonight.
I already have plans.