The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Live in a place permanently.
Reside.
Free from disease or injury in good condition.
Sound.
By means of or as a result of this.
Hereby.
A paper made to settle property after one's death.
Last will and testament.
The body of a dead person.
Remains.
The highest point, top.
Summit.
Everything you own, all your assets.
Estate.
Choose someone to do a particular job.
Appoint.
Add or append.
Affix.
To sign at the end of the will or contract.
Subscribe.
A person's partner in marriage.
Spouse.
Cancel.
Revoke.
The body of a dead person.
Remains.
Cancel.
Choose someone to do a particular job.
Appoint.
Spouse.
To sign at the end of the will or contract.
Subscribe.
Add or append.
Affix.
A paper made to settle property after one's death.
Last will and testament.
Free from disease or injury in good condition.
Sound.
The highest point, top.
Summit.
By means of or as a result of this.
Hereby.
Live in a place permanently.
Reside.
Everything you own, all your assets.
Estate.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Revoke.
His driving license was revoked by the police.
My parents revoked my phone privileges.
Revoke.
The court decided to revoke the terrorist citizenship.
Remains.
The remains were transferred to the morgue.
A cemetery has the remains of many people.
Remains.
The police covered the remains with a white sheet.
Estate.
Bill Gates' estate is valued at over one billion dollars.
A person's estate is comprised of all assets which are held in the descendant's name alone.
Estate.
The family divided the estate equally among everyone.
Hereby.
I hereby declare you husband and wife.
I hereby resign as President of the United States.
Hereby.
We hereby commit to obeying the laws of this country.
Appoint.
The President appointed me as the Vice President.
My teacher appointed me as the classroom monitor.
Appoint.
He was appointed as the child's legal guardian.