EnglishPod.com Okay class, so today we're going to continue with our anatomy class.
Today we will review everything we have learned.
Can anyone tell me what the first major organ is?
The brain!
That's right, the brain.
It serves as a control center for the body, handling the processes of the central nervous system as well as cognition.
Then what major organ is in our chest?
The heart!
Very good.
It pumps blood throughout the body using the circulatory system such as blood vessels and veins.
Now let's not forget that our lungs provide oxygen to our heart and body to keep us alive.
Now what about the organs that help us digest food?
The stomach and intestines.
Very good.
Let's not forget that the stomach is the one that breaks down our food and our intestines process the food and then expel the waste.
Are we forgetting anything?
Yeah, our kidneys, liver and bladder.
Oh yes, you are right.
Very important organs indeed.
So what do these organs do, teacher?
Well, um, they...
Time for a break!
We can talk about it when you get back.