The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The trunk of the body from the neck to the abdomen.
Anatomy A grouping of tissues into a distinct structure, for example the heart.
Organ An organ enclosed in the skull that controls and coordinates the body.
Brain The ability to direct the actions of something.
Control A planned series of steps or actions that leads to something.
Process The front of the body from neck to the waist.
Chest An organ in the chest that pumps blood.
Heart To supply, to circulate.
Pump The fluid that circulates in the body.
Blood Body part that inflates with air and allows breathing.
Lung A guess that we breathe in order to live.
Oxygen To swallow and to solve something.
Digest The organ people use to digest food.
Stomach To release something.
Expel The organ used to produce blood.
Liver Let's try that faster.
An organ enclosed in the skull that controls and coordinates the body.
Brain A grouping of tissues into a distinct structure, for example the heart.
Organ To supply, to circulate.
Pump The front of the body from neck to the waist.
Chest A guess that we breathe in order to live.
Oxygen The ability to direct the actions of something.
Control An organ in the chest that pumps blood.
Heart Body part that inflates with air and allows breathing.
Lung To swallow and to solve something.
Digest The organ people use to digest food.
Stomach To release something.
Expel The fluid that circulates in the body.
Blood A planned series of steps or actions that leads to something.
Process The organ used to produce blood.
Liver The trunk of the body from the neck to the abdomen.
Anatomy Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Digest Do you think this medicine is safe to digest?
Digest It's hard for your body to digest junk food.
You should eat natural foods.
Digest Babies should eat easily digested foods such as banana when they are small.
Stomach My stomach keeps grumbling.
I think it's hungry.
Stomach Whenever I eat spicy food my stomach really hurts.
Stomach Stomach Wow, her stomach is really big.
Is she pregnant?
Heart I had a heart attack last year.
I need to be careful.
Heart Heart My doctor told me I need to lay off bacon as it's damaging my heart.
Heart I'm going to donate my heart when I die.
It's not like I will need it.
Oxygen This room smells so bad.
I need to get some oxygen.
Oxygen The man died when he ran out of oxygen diving in the ocean.
Oxygen I python kills it's prey by crushing it.
Without the oxygen the prey dies.
Chest My chest is really big after that workout at the gym.
Chest Chest I want to wax my chest.
It's too hairy.
Chest I think I have a disease.
My chest is all swollen and black.