The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Slammer Short for intelligence, information or instructions.
Intel Person who watches and warns if there is danger.
Lookout Permission to do something.
Go ahead A meeting planned at a certain time and place.
Rendezvous Mistake, an unforeseen obstacle.
Hitch A phrase used to express frustration.
For Pete's sake.
Let's try that faster.
Pry into the private affairs of others.
Snoop A meeting planned at a certain time and place.
Rendezvous A phrase used to express frustration.
For Pete's sake.
Run through Person who watches and warns if there is danger.
Lookout Permission to do something.
Go ahead Slammer An unforeseen obstacle.
Hitch Short for intelligence, information or instructions.
Intel Out of Out of Run through Let's run through the English lesson one more time.
Run through He must run through his lines for the play again.
Run through The computer must run through all the codes before processing information.
Slammer After he was caught robbing the store, he was thrown into the slammer.
Slammer The slammer is not for the weak hearted.
Slammer She visits her husband in the slammer every weekend.
Intel The intel suggests he is a very dangerous man.
Intel His intel was wrong.
She is not at home.
Intel The boss's intel is always detailed and correct.
Rendezvous The rendezvous point is at the north end of the beach.
Rendezvous Every year they rendezvous in Paris, France.
Rendezvous We must change the rendezvous.
The cops are on to our plans.
For Pete's sake Oh for Pete's sake Stop changing the channel so much.
For Pete's sake My phone fell into the toilet.
Oh for Pete's sake For Pete's sake Oh for Pete's sake.
Must you take so long to get ready?