EnglishPod.com Alright, let's run through this one more time from the top.
I will be positioned here, across from the bank on this park bench.
Now, according to the intel we got from Jimmy...
Oh, who's Jimmy?
Jeez, Ralph, pay attention, will ya?
Jimmy's our mole, you know?
The guy on the inside?
He's been snooping and passing on the info to us so we can pull this heist off.
Yeah, Ralph, clean the mothballs out of your ears and listen up.
This here's important!
We don't want to end up back in the slammer, do ya?
Your role is pretty important here, we're dependent on you, man.
Okay, okay, I'm listening...
Mothballs.
Alrighty then, where was I?
Oh yeah, okay.
So I'll be on the lookout, sitting here on the bench across from the bank.
Nobody moves until I give the go-ahead, alright?
And what's the go-ahead, Ralph?
You, um...
you, uh...
Oh yeah, you'll take off your hat and scratch your head.
Right.
When I take my hat off and scratch my head, you do what?
I get in the box.
Right, you get in the box.
I'll make sure it's all sealed and then posing as the delivery guy, I'll drop off a special package for the manager.
Now, according to Jimmy, the bank manager's leaving early on Tuesday because it's his wedding anniversary.
He and the wife are having a romantic rendezvous in the country, so any packages delivered will be left unopened in his office until he gets back late on Wednesday.
Which gives us access to his office for at least 12 hours.
Okay, Ralph, this is where you come in.
Where are you?
I'm standing right next to you, Sammy.
Oh, sorry, Sam.
I'm in the box, right here, in that box.
And what do you do once I deliver you to the manager's office?
I stay in the box until the bank is closed.
And then I get out of the box.
And then?
What next, Ralph?
Oh, for Pete's sake, this is never going to work.
Hey, give me a chance here, fellas.
I crack the safe and then...
then I take the money.
And then I...
well, I get back in the box.
Atta boy, Ralph.
In the morning, I come back to the bank, say there's been a mix-up with the delivery I made, and take the special package back here.
All right, let's get some sleep.
It's a big day tomorrow, fellas.
A perfect plan, Sammy.
It went off without a hitch.
Let's open this up and get Ralph out of here so we can start counting the money.
Phew, I sure am glad to see you guys.
I was sure getting lonely with no one to talk.
That's nice.
Okay, how much?
Uh, really?
Really, really, really glad.
Money, Ralph.
Money!
Oh, man.
I knew I forgot something.
Dammit.