The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Casual tennis shoes Sneakers Having stripes or bands of color Striped A pattern with alternating squares Checkered A fabric pattern with many circles Polka dot A type of footwear with open toes Sandal A type of fabric used to make jeans Denim The shape and style of a piece of clothing Cut Used to describe something that is no longer popular Out of fashion The line formed by the lower edge of clothing Hemline A person who makes clothes adjusts the fit Tailor An event where you eat at a friend's house Dinner party A ribbed cotton clothing material Corduroy An idea for what clothing looks good Fashion sense Let's try that faster!
A type of fabric used to make jeans Denim A type of footwear with open toes Sandal A ribbed cotton clothing material Corduroy A person who makes clothes adjusts the fit Tailor Used to describe something that is no longer popular Out of fashion Having stripes or bands of color Striped An idea for what clothing looks good Fashion sense The line formed by the lower edge of clothing Hemline The shape and style of a piece of clothing Cut A pattern with alternating squares Checkered An event where you eat at a friend's house Dinner party A fabric pattern with many circles Polka dot Casual tennis shoes Sneakers Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Striped The zebra has strong black and white striping for confusing predators Striped It is never a good idea to wear a striped shirt with checkered pants Striped Uncle Joe took me down to the pond to fish for striped bass Checkered A black and white Checkered flag is often used to signal the end of a race Checkered Chess is always played on a checkered board Checkered We were all unaware of the man's checkered past.
Nobody knew he just got out of jail.
Cut The cut of men's suits has changed considerably over the years.
Cut She was not pleased with the cut of her wedding dress so now it must be redone.
Cut Michael is such a dependable employee.
They really like the cut of his jib.
Dinner party Another dinner party?
Why can't we ever eat at home with our own family?
Dinner party It is always a good idea to bring a bottle of wine or a dessert when attending a dinner party Dinner party James made a fool of himself at the dinner party when he tried to show off his new magic tricks Fashion sense You have no fashion sense whatsoever Just look at what you are wearing Fashion sense Fashion sense Fashion sense is not something you can learn by imitating others.