The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Be not.
A children's Halloween practice of asking for treats.
Trick or treat.
Attire in clothes suited to a particular role.
Dress up.
To seize and detain or carry away by unlawful force.
Kidnapper.
To go all over the place.
To move quickly from one place to another.
Run around.
Let's try that faster.
A children's Halloween practice of asking for treats.
Trick or treat.
Attire in clothes suited to a particular role.
Dress up.
Be not.
To seize and detain or carry away by unlawful force.
Kidnapper.
To go all over the place.
To move quickly from one place to another.
Run around.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Trick or treat.
It is common for young kids to go trick or treating on Halloween.
Last year when I went trick or treating, I got enough candy to last for a whole year.
Trick or treat.
Many parents don't allow their children to go trick or treating because they think it's dangerous.
Dress up.
When I was eight years old, I dressed up as Superman for Halloween.
Many people don't like to dress up on Halloween.
Dress up.
It's cute to see all the children dressed up in their costumes.
Be not.
The teacher gave out the exams.
Our company gave out Christmas bonuses this year.
Be not.
I hate Halloween.
Why do I have to give out candies for free?
Run around.
There are so many kids running around that they are driving me crazy.
I saw your dog running around the front lawn this morning.
Run around.
Pete's cat is running around here somewhere, so make sure to close the door.
Be not.
Aren't you a little too big to be playing with those kids?
Aren't those pants a little too small for you?
Be not.
Isn't that shirt a little too old to be wearing it to a dinner party?