The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A list of drugs written by a doctor.
Prescription A unit for measuring weight.
Milligram Drug contained in a plastic container.
Capsule Drug formed in round hard shape.
Take more drugs than suggested.
Overdose Liquid used to drop into eyes to treat eye diseases.
Eyedrop Hold on Hang on Type in the number of something to check its price.
Get a price check A device made of a hollow tube and a needle that is used to force fluids into or take fluids out of the body.
Syringe A usually sweet liquid that contains medicine used to stop coughing called also cough medicine.
Cough syrup A covering such as a strip of cloth that protects or supports part of the body that has been hurt.
Bandage A liquid that is used to make things lighter in color or to kill bacteria.
Hydrogen peroxide A smooth substance that is rubbed on the skin to help heal a wound or to reduce pain or discomfort.
Ointment Let's try that faster!
Drug contained in a plastic container.
Capsule Drug formed in round hard shape.
Take more drugs than suggested.
Overdose Liquid used to drop into eyes to treat eye diseases.
Eyedrop A device made of a hollow tube and a needle that is used to force fluids into or take fluids out of the body.
Syringe A liquid that is used to make things lighter in color or to kill bacteria.
Hydrogen peroxide A covering such as a strip of cloth that protects or supports part of the body that has been hurt.
Bandage Type in the number of something to check its price.
Get a price check A list of drugs written by a doctor.
Prescription A unit for measuring weight.
Milligram A usually sweet liquid that contains medicine used to stop coughing, called also cough medicine.
Cough syrup A smooth substance that is rubbed on the skin to help heal a wound or to reduce pain or discomfort.
Ointment Hold on Hang on Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Prescription In order to buy medicine in the US, you need to bring your doctor's prescription.
Prescription I lost my prescription and I don't remember what medicine I had to buy.
Prescription Valium is medicine that you can only buy with a prescription.
Tablet Tablet Children should only take half a tablet of cold medicine.
Tablet I find it hard to swallow tablets.
They are just too big.
Tablet Tablet I had a box full of medicine tablets, but I don't know where I left it.
Overdose My dog accidentally swallowed some aspirins and almost overdosed.
Overdose A lot of famous movie stars have accidentally overdosed on drugs and died.
Overdose You must follow your doctor's instructions when taking medicine, otherwise you might overdose.
Eye drop Your eyes are really red.
You should get some eye drops.
Eye drop When I wear contact lens, I have to use these eye drops or else my eyes get irritated.
Eye drop Susan got pink eye, so her doctor prescribed some eye drops and told her not to touch her eyes.
Some new merchandise arrived today, so we need to run a price check on each item.
This item doesn't have a price on it.
Can you run a price check to make sure we sell it here?
That store always has to run a price check on new items since they don't have a modern pricing system.
Thanks for watching!