EnglishPod.com Hey, Michelle.
This is my friend, James.
He's visiting Shanghai from New York.
Oh, hi, James.
Nice to meet you.
So, are you visiting for business or pleasure?
Well, actually a little of both.
I'm meeting some business contacts, but I'm also taking some Mandarin classes, too.
Oh, that's cool.
How's it going?
Well, I'm finding the classes pretty tough, actually.
But I'm having a great time in Shanghai.
It's really an amazing city.
It sure is.
Are you staying for long?
Only two weeks, unfortunately.
I wish I could stay longer, but...
Well, listen, if you need someone to show you the sights, then just call me.
I'm having a little get-together at my new apartment next week, so if you want to drop by then...
That sounds great.
I'd love to.
Let me take down your number, Michelle.