The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Prepare the table so as to sit down and eat.
To set the table, anything specific, anything in particular, eating utensils, fork, spoon, knife, silverware, to bake uncovered, especially in an oven, to roast, a dish used for serving food, serving dish, anything specific, anything in particular, eating utensils, fork, spoon, knife, silverware, prepare the table so as to sit down and eat.
To set the table, to bake uncovered, especially in an oven, to roast, a dish used for serving food, serving dish, now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
To set the table, everyone knows that the proper way to set a table is to turn the knife towards the dish and not away from it.
To set the table, kids, supper is almost ready so please set the table and call your dad.
To set the table, I think I will set the table with our crystal glasses for our guests tonight.
Anything in particular, I'm not looking for anything in particular, just browsing.
Anything in particular, did you want anything in particular for your birthday?
Anything in particular, is there anything in particular I can do to help you clean up?
Silverware, she brought out her good silverware for the dinner party.
Silverware, the only drawback of having silverware made of real silver is that it tarnishes easily.
Silverware, he polished the silverware before every use.
To roast, he roasted the beef until it was tender.
To roast, she tossed some vegetables in a pan then put them in the oven to roast.
To roast, the turkey took most of the day to roast but it was well worth the wait.
Serving dish, the guests admired the creative arrangement of cheese and crackers on the serving dish.
Serving dish, can you put the stir fry into a serving dish and then place it on the table for me?
Serving dish, my aunt and uncle gave me a beautiful clay serving dish as a wedding gift.