EnglishPod.com Honey, can you set the table?
Um, sure.
What are we having for dinner?
Do I need to put anything out in particular?
Well, make sure to put out the pepper and salt shakers.
I don't know if your brother is coming tonight, so set an extra placemat just in case.
Okay, should I use the fancy silverware?
Yeah, go ahead.
Forks, spoons, and knives.
I roasted some meat, so be sure to put out some steak knives as well.
I'll also set some cups and saucers for some coffee after dinner.
Honey, have you seen our soup bowls?
They're in the cupboard where you keep the gravy boat and serving dishes.
Just be careful because the wine glasses are also there.
Oops.