The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
So extreme a degree.
Such a.
To deceive by trickery.
Cheat.
My opportunity to do something.
My turn.
Place where prisoners are kept.
Jail.
Used to ask for permissions.
Can I.
The player in charge of the bank and gambling games.
Banker.
Used to ask for permission.
Can I.
So extreme a degree.
Such a.
My opportunity to do something.
My turn.
Place where prisoners are kept.
Jail.
Such a.
Mike is such a loser.
He has no ambitions or goals in life.
Such a.
Amanda is such a phony.
You can never really believe her.
Such a.
He is such a playboy.
He has many girlfriends.
Cheat.
My classmate was cheating on the exam.
Carol always cheats when we play games together.
Cheat.
My parents taught me never to cheat people.
Can I.
Can I have your ice cream.
Can I have a taste of your soup.
Can I.
Can I have some money please.
My turn.
It's your turn to wash the dishes.
It's his turn to clean the room.
My turn.
It's my turn to get on the ride.