EnglishPod.com Hey Mal, are you up for some tennis today?
Sorry, I can't.
I have to go to work, pick up Jake and Maddie from school, and make them an afternoon snack, then take Jake to soccer practice and Maddie to dance class.
Mmm, you sound exhausted.
Maybe you should hire a nanny to help you out.
She can pick the kids up and take them to their after school activities.
She can also help you do some household chores and run some errands.
Oh, I don't know.
It's hard to find the right nanny.
You have to consider her previous work experience, the responsibilities you give her, and how she interacts with the kids.
I would love to have someone to help me out, though.
I think you should definitely consider it.
This way you won't have to juggle such a busy schedule, and you'll still get to spend time with the kids in the evenings.
I can refer you to this great nanny, Amy.
She used to work for my neighbors before they moved away.
She's very responsible, a good cook, and great with kids.
Oh, that's great.
Thanks, Grace.
Can you give me her number?
I'll talk it over with Julie and give her a call tomorrow.
Maybe this way I won't be so tired every day, and Julie and I might even get to go on a date once in a while.