The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Very tired Exhausted To give work Hire A woman who is paid to care for a young child Nanny A small job that is done regularly Chore Short journey that you take to do or get something Errand To do several things at the same time Juggle To send someone to a person or place for treatment Refer Let's try that faster A woman who is paid to care for a young child Nanny A small job that is done regularly Chore To send someone to a person or place for treatment Refer Very tired Exhausted To give work Hire Short journey that you take to do or get something Errand To do several things at the same time Juggle Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Are you up for some fun today?
We're going to an amusement park.
I don't feel so well.
I don't think I'm up for basketball this afternoon.
What do you want to do?
I'm up for anything.
I can't go out until I finish my chores.
My mom left me with a list of chores to do around the house.
Very few children enjoy doing household chores.
When you are applying for a new job, your interviewer will ask for a recommendation from your previous employer.
My parents are much nicer to Alex than they were to my previous boyfriend, Jared.
This house is smaller than our previous house, but it's in a better neighborhood.
This job comes with a lot of responsibility.
Are you sure you can handle it?
It's my responsibility to take care of the family dog.
Mark has a lot of responsibilities as president, but he does his job well.
From the way they interact, it seems like they are good friends.
My schedule is so busy, I don't have much time to interact with my friends anymore.
You can learn a lot from interacting with people of different backgrounds.
Cindy has the job of work, school, and taking care of her son, Daniel.
Even though Manuel is very busy, he does a good job of juggling all his responsibilities.
Every day at work, Laura juggles many different tasks.