The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Hi, you, informal.
Heya.
Really good.
Swell.
Dance is held usually in high school gym or cafeteria.
Sock hop.
A very fun time.
A blast.
An informal dance, usually in high school, where girls invite boys.
Sadie Hawkins dance.
Focus your attention on something you want.
Have one's eye on someone.
Stop putting pressure on someone.
Ease off.
A punch.
Knuckle sandwich.
Relax, take it easy.
Cool it.
Someone who is not important.
Pipsqueak.
Get really angry and explode.
Go ape.
Be really happy.
Be on cloud nine.
A very cool person.
Cool cat.
Movie or film.
Flick.
A person who is not fun.
Party pooper.
It's no problem.
No sweat.
Let's try that faster.
Dance is held usually in high school gym or cafeteria.
Sock hop.
Be really happy.
Be on cloud nine.
Someone who is not important.
Pipsqueak.
Stop putting pressure on someone.
Ease off.
An informal dance, usually in high school, where girls invite boys.
Sadie Hawkins dance.
A very fun time.
A blast.
Get really angry and explode.
Go ape.
Hi, you.
Informal.
Heya.
A punch.
Knuckle sandwich.
Really good.
Swell.
Focus your attention on something you want.
Have one's eye on someone.
A person who is not fun.
Party pooper.
A very cool person.
Cool cat.
Relax.
Take it easy.
Cool it.
It's no problem.
No sweat.
Movie or film.
Flick.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Swell.
We had a swell time at the party last night.
I don't know why you don't like Tim.
I think he's swell.
Swell.
Bowling tonight sounds like a swell idea.
A blast.
Roger and I went to the park and played soccer.
We had a blast.
A blast.
Every time Josh and Carl get together, they have a blast.
Come on, let's go to the carnival.
It will be a blast.
A blast.
I've had my eye on that car for a long time and now I'm going to buy it.
I've had my eye on that new TV.
I'm going to buy it when it goes on sale.
Wendy had her eye on that boy since high school but never asked him out.
Ease off.
You need to ease off the junk food.
Matt is putting so much pressure on me these days.
I wish he would ease off.
Ease off.
You're pushing Susie too much.
You should ease off a bit.
Cool it.
Just cool it.
Now is not the right time to get angry.
Cool it.
You need to cool it and stop yelling at me.
Don't cry Pam.
Just cool it.
It will be okay.