EnglishPod.com So, so I said, let's take a break.
And since that night, I've been waiting for him to call but I still haven't heard from him.
You don't think he's seeing someone else, do you?
Come on, don't be so dramatic.
I'm sure everything is going to work out just fine.
You think so?
Oh no, how could he do this to me?
I'm sure he's cheating on me.
Why else wouldn't he call?
But you two are on a break.
Theoretically, he can do whatever he likes.
He's the love of my life.
I really messed this up.
Come on hun, pull yourself together.
It's going to be alright.
But I still love him and it's all my fault.
I can't believe how immature and selfish I was being.
I mean, he is a firefighter.
It's not like he can just leave someone in a burning building and meet me for dinner.
I've totally messed this up.
You know what Veronica?
I think you should make the first step.
I'm sure he'll forgive you.
No.
This is not going to happen.
I've ruined everything.
Hey, do you hear something?
Guess what?
It's your lovely firefighter.
I'll be right back.