The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Dating or going out with someone.
Seeing someone.
Having a romantic relationship with someone else, not your husband or wife or boyfriend or girlfriend.
Cheat on someone.
A relationship that is temporarily on hold.
On a break.
Calm down, relax, organize your thoughts.
Pull yourself together.
Acting in a childish way.
Immature.
Having or showing concern only for yourself and not the needs or feelings of other people.
Selfish.
Damage, destroy something.
Ruin.
End a relationship.
Break up.
End a relationship when the other person does not want to.
Dump someone.
Serious, long-term boyfriend or girlfriend.
Partner.
Former boyfriend, girlfriend, husband or wife.
Ex.
Romantic social life.
Love life.
Don't worry, it's not so serious.
It's not the end of the world.
Let's try that faster.
Having a romantic relationship with someone else, not your husband or wife or boyfriend or girlfriend.
Cheat on someone.
Calm down, relax, organize your thoughts.
Pull yourself together.
Romantic social life.
Love life.
Damage, destroy something.
Ruin.
Former boyfriend, girlfriend, husband or wife.
Ex.
Don't worry, it's not so serious.
It's not the end of the world.
Acting in a childish way.
Immature.
A relationship that is temporarily on hold.
On a break.
End a relationship.
Break up.
Dating or going out with someone.
Seeing someone.
End a relationship when the other person does not want to.
Dump someone.
Serious long-term boyfriend or girlfriend.
Partner.
Having or showing concern only for yourself and not the needs or feelings of other people.
Selfish.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Seeing someone.
I think that Carl is seeing someone from the office.
Peter asked me to be his girlfriend but I'm seeing someone so I had to say no.
Seeing someone.
If you are not seeing anyone, I would like to ask you out to dinner.
Cheat on someone.
They got a divorce because Mary cheated on her husband.
My friend went to the cinema yesterday and found his girlfriend there cheating on him with another guy.
Cheat on someone.
I cheated on my girlfriend one time but she never found out about it.
Pull yourself together.
This is no time to panic.
You have to pull yourself together and solve your problem.
Pull yourself together.
Calm down.
Get out there and score a goal.
It's not like I can just leave my office whenever I want.
My boss will fire me.
It's not like you can just insult me and then expect me to not feel bad.
It's not like we can just use all our savings on this trip.
We have to think about the future.
Ruin.
You spilled red wine on my shirt.
You've ruined it.
Ruin.
We were having such a nice day at the park and then you ruined it by arguing with me.
I accidentally ruined the turkey by leaving it in the oven too long.