The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A meal laid out on a table or sideboard so that guests may serve themselves.
Buffet An arrangement to secure accommodations at a restaurant or hotel.
Reservation The quality of being at hand when needed.
Availability Confirm details at front desk.
Check-in Better than others.
Superior A connected series of rooms to be used together.
Suite To keep back or safe for future use.
Reserve Let's try that faster.
A connected series of rooms to be used together.
Suite A meal laid out on a table or sideboard so that guests may serve themselves.
Buffet Confirm details at front desk.
Check-in To keep back or safe for future use.
Reserve An arrangement to secure accommodations at a restaurant or hotel.
Reservation The quality of being at hand when needed.
Availability Better than others Superior Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Reservation Hello sir, do you have a reservation?
Reservation Reservation If we want a room we will need to make a reservation.
Reservation Sorry, there are no seats available.
Please make a reservation.
Buffet Buffets Buffets are great.
I get to eat whatever I like.
Buffet I'm so hungry I can't wait to eat this huge buffet.
Buffet There is a wide variety of food available at the buffet.
Suite This vacation I'm going to get the best suite available.
Suite I wanted the deluxe suite but they were all taken.
Suite I don't want the junior suite.
It's too small for a large family.
Reserve Hello, I would like to reserve a table for two please.
Reserve Reserve My friend always reserves the same table at the same restaurant every Valentine's Day.
Reserve I was too late and now I cannot reserve a suite at the hotel.
Check in Please check in at a later time.
The room is not ready yet.
Check in I can't wait to check in to my suite and get out of this weather.
Check in I forgot to bring my identification.
How will I check in?