EnglishPod.com housewarming gift but Armand started acting really weird and then he practically kicked me out.
I tried to sort of peek into his house but everything was so dark inside that I couldn't really get a good look.
The whole thing really creeped me out.
Well you'll never guess what I saw this morning.
A delivery truck pulled into his driveway and it dropped off a long rectangular box.
It almost looked like a coffin.
You see?
Why would he...
Armand!
You scared the heck out of me.
This is my friend Doris.
Pleasure to meet you.
If you're not doing anything tonight I'd like to have you both for dinner.
I mean I'd like to have you both over for dinner.