The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of information.
I don't know if you heard.
Tell me about it.
Fill me in.
A sense or feeling that something bad is going to happen.
A bad feeling.
Strange, unusual.
Weird.
Make or force someone to leave when they don't want to.
Kick out.
Make me feel uncomfortable and a bit scared.
Creep me out.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of news.
You'll never guess.
Cause someone to feel a lot of fear.
Scare the heck out of me.
Strange or unusual.
Bizarre.
Strange or scary, causing people to feel nervous and afraid.
Creepy.
A dead person who drinks the blood of living people.
Vampire.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of gossip.
Have you heard?
Phrase used to introduce an interesting or surprising piece of information.
Guess what?
Let's try that faster.
A dead person who drinks the blood of living people.
Vampire.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of news.
You'll never guess.
Tell me about it.
Fill me in.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of gossip.
Have you heard?
Strange or scary, causing people to feel nervous and afraid.
Creepy.
Phrase used to introduce an interesting or surprising piece of information.
Guess what?
Strange, unusual.
Weird.
Make me feel uncomfortable and a bit scared.
Creep me out.
Cause someone to feel a lot of fear.
Scare the heck out of me.
Make or force someone to leave when they don't want to.
Kick out.
A sense or feeling that something bad is going to happen.
A bad feeling.
Strange or unusual.
Bizarre.
Phrase used to introduce a piece of information.
I don't know if you heard.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Weird.
Last night I kept hearing a really weird sound.
I don't know what it was.
Weird.
Our teacher seems a bit weird, don't you think?
The weirdest thing happened to me yesterday.
A pack of monkeys stole my car keys.
A bad feeling.
I've got a bad feeling about Kelly's new boyfriend.
I don't think he's a good guy.
A bad feeling.
I have a bad feeling about this sales strategy.
I think it's going to fail.
A bad feeling.
I've got a bad feeling about this trip.
I think we should stay home.
Kick out.
If you don't be quiet, I'm going to kick you out of this meeting.
We got kicked out of the restaurant at midnight because they were closing.
Kick out.
That's it.
I'm kicking you out of class.
Go stand in the hall.
Creep me out.
This old house is so scary.
It's really creeping me out.
Creep me out.
I watched The Exorcist last night.
That movie really creeps me out.
Creep me out.
The last time I walked home alone at night, I really got creeped out.
I almost got in a car accident yesterday.
That scared the heck out of me.
Don't wear that vampire mask.
You're scaring the heck out of the baby.
I'm terrified of clowns.
They scare the heck out of me.
I don't know if you've heard, but Susan and John are breaking up.
I don't know if you've heard, but the new marketing manager is single.
I don't know if you've heard, but Maurice quit his job yesterday.
Fill me in.
I can't go to today's meeting, but can you fill me in on the important details?
How was your date?
You have to fill me in.
Fill me in.
Sarah missed her class yesterday, but I filled her in on the homework assignment.
You'll never guess what I heard.
Peter and Anna are getting married.
You'll never guess who I saw yesterday.
Bill, my boyfriend from high school.
You'll never guess what Sandra told me.
She's moving to Alaska.