The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A ticket that allows you only to go to a certain place.
One-way ticket To leave, start a voyage.
Depart A flat elevated portion of ground.
Platform On time, precisely at a certain time.
On the dot Planned at a specific time to leave.
Scheduled departure time.
Let's try that faster.
To leave, start a voyage.
Depart Planned at a specific time to leave.
Scheduled departure time.
A flat elevated portion of ground.
Platform A ticket that allows you only to go to a certain place.
One-way ticket On time, precisely at a certain time.
On the dot Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
One-way ticket One-way ticket I have a one-way ticket to Paris and have no plans on ever coming back to North America.
One-way ticket My friend bought a one-way ticket to the middle of China and then managed to travel around for a month on the generosity of the people he met.
One-way ticket I only need to buy a one-way plane ticket because I plan on taking the train back.
Depart The train will depart at half past six.
Depart We will depart as soon as we have de-iced the plane.
Depart The bus will be departing again in ten minutes so use the washroom quickly.
Platform Platform We waited in the waiting room at the train station for half an hour before they finally let us onto the platform.
Platform I only had three minutes until the train would leave so I ran down the platform as fast as I could.
Platform The Hogwarts Express leaves from platform nine and three quarters.
On the dot They left at ten p.m.
on the dot.
On the dot She arrived at five past seven on the dot.
On the dot I think that the artist's representation of Shanghai in this painting is right on the dot.
Scheduled departure time The scheduled departure time for your plane is one forty five.
Scheduled departure time The plane has been delayed one hour from the scheduled departure time.
Scheduled departure time I received an email saying that our scheduled departure time has been moved ahead by half an hour.