Welcome to Perfect Getaway Tours.
How can I help you?
I would like to plan a surprise getaway for me and my wife.
Very well.
We have a couple of different options such as beaches, the wilderness, the countryside, or even going to a spa for the weekend.
I think something in the countryside would be nice.
Perfect.
This package includes round trip flights to New Hampshire.
A free airport pickup is included.
Our VIP limousine will pick you up and provide you with complimentary champagne and finger foods to soften this 30 minute ride to the countryside.
Sounds good.
What is the hotel that we'll be staying at like?
That is the best part.
Your hotel is actually an old country villa that has been restored and refurbished to accommodate a maximum of 10 guests.
You will enjoy an intimate and private time in this very spacious and warm hotel.
Included in the price is three meals a day, excluding beverages.
You can choose to eat at the fabulous restaurant that offers a stunning view of the lush green gardens or if you prefer, your own private butler can arrange your meal to be served in your room or outside on our terrace.
Wow.
This sounds like something my wife would really enjoy.
Are there any outdoor activities we can take part in?
Of course.
The hotel has a stable with beautiful stallions for a very romantic horseback ride along the country trail.
You can also go fishing at the nearby lake or visit the local vineyard.
I'm sold.
I want to book this trip and I don't care what it costs.
Money is no object.