The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
End a relationship with someone.
Dump someone.
Hurt someone's feelings very badly.
Hurt someone emotionally.
Break someone's heart.
Honest emotional talk.
A heart to heart.
Former boyfriend, girlfriend, husband, or wife.
Ex.
A person who you are in a long-term relationship with.
Partner.
Phrase used if one must talk about serious things.
Can we talk?
What stage this relationship is in.
Where this relationship is going.
Feel strong romantic affection for someone.
In love with.
Amazing, great.
Awesome.
We have experienced our happy days.
We have had our laughs.
Don't like.
Don't appreciate.
Have strong affection to someone.
Love.
Perhaps it is time for us to do something.
Maybe it is time that we.
Let's try that faster.
End a relationship with someone.
Dump someone.
We have experienced our happy days.
We have had our laughs.
Former boyfriend, girlfriend, husband, or wife.
Ex.
Phrase used if one must talk about serious things.
Can we talk?
Have strong affection to someone.
Love.
Amazing, great.
Awesome.
Feel strong romantic affection for someone.
In love with.
What stage this relationship is in.
Where this relationship is going.
A person who you are in a long term relationship with.
Partner.
Honest emotional talk.
A heart to heart.
Don't like.
Don't appreciate.
Perhaps it is time for us to do something.
Maybe it is time that we.
Hurt someone's feelings very badly.
Hurt someone emotionally.
Break someone's heart.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Can we talk?
I've got something really important to tell you.
I think I'm in love with someone else.
Can we talk?
I need your help with something.
Where this relationship is going.
We fight every day.
I don't know where this relationship is going.
Where this relationship is going.
Where is this movie going?
I don't understand what's happening.
Where this relationship is going.
You want to do what?
Where are you going with this conversation?
We have had our laughs.
College was so much fun.
We definitely had our laughs.
We have had our laughs.
She has her moments.
But for the most part, she's a really nice girl.
We have had our laughs.
You had your fun.
Now it's time to go to sleep.
Maybe it is time that we.
It's two o'clock in the afternoon.
Maybe it's time we have some lunch.
Maybe it is time that we.
If you're not happy at your job, maybe it's just time for you to quit.
Maybe it's about time you clean your room.
It's so dirty.
Baby, I love you so much.
Where would you like to eat, sweetheart?
Darling, you look absolutely beautiful.