The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something that holds a person.
Support A shoe with the bottom part having straps.
Strappy sandals A low cut, low heeled shoe.
Edgy pump The shoe with the toes exposed.
Open toed shoe.
The length of the heel is 2 inches.
2 inch heel.
The shoe having a narrow top.
Pointed shoe.
Squeeze between the thumb and a finger.
Pinch The inner sole of a shoe.
Insole Tight and hurts the body with a sharp thing.
Cut into The inner sole of a shoe.
The length of the heel is 2 inches.
Tight and hurts the body with a sharp thing.
Cut into The inner sole of a shoe.
Insole Something that holds a person.
Support A shoe with the bottom part having straps.
Strappy sandals The shoe having a narrow top.
Pointed shoe Squeeze between the thumb and a finger.
Pinch The shoe with the toes exposed.
Open toed shoe.
A low cut, low heeled shoe.
Edgy pump Support It is important that your shoe support the arches of your feet so that your ankles don't roll in.
Support Apparently my shoes are the cause of my back pain so I need to get custom made insoles that provide extra support.
Support I find that it is so much easier to walk in a shoe that has arch support.
Cut into My new shoes are cutting into the back of my heel.
Cut into The straps on these sandals are cutting into my feet.
Cut into I think my feet are too wide for this shoe because the shoe is starting to cut into the sides of my feet.
2 inch heel I can't stand high heels so if I have to wear them I only ever wear shoes with a 1 inch heel.
2 inch heel I don't know how models can stand, let alone walk in 4 inch heels.
2 inch heel Pinch I love any kind of high heel shoes but pumps with 3 inch heels are my favorite by far.
Pinch When I bought these shoes they fit perfectly but now I find that they are pinching my baby toe.
Pinch Does the size down fit better or are they pinching your feet?
Pinch I haven't yet been able to buy shoes in China because the shoe sizes are smaller so my toes are always pinched.
I always put insoles in my shoes so I don't need to worry about how comfortable a shoe is before I buy it.
The doctor suggested that my mother get special insoles made for her shoes.
I always wear good quality shoes so I never needed to buy insoles.