EnglishPod.com Hi, excuse me, sir.
I'm looking for a dress shoe.
My usual pair that I've had for years have finally been stretched out of shape.
They don't provide any support anymore.
Sure, what kind of shoe are you looking for?
We've got strappy sandals, sleek high heels, edgy pumps.
If you're looking for something a little more practical, we've got Mary Janes, ballerinas.
Show me some classic high heels, please.
Okay, right this way.
What color did you have in mind?
Black, classic.
Of course, we've got this style here that is very popular.
Because it's an open toe shoe, you can wear it any time of the year.
They look great on everyone.
Um, too shiny.
And I wear pantyhose with my shoes, so let's look for a closed toe shoe.
Okay, these are a very nice pair of leather shoes with a two inch heel, so they are very comfortable.
I don't like the pointed toes.
Let me take a look at what else you have.
Too high.
That one looks like the back would cut into my heel.
I have a high instep, so I doubt that one would fit properly.
I don't want bows.
I find slingbacks very uncomfortable.
Those might as well be stilettos.
Too modern.
Ah, finally, this is what I'm looking for.
What size?
Seven and a half.
Here we are.
How does it fit?
Mmm, not good.
They're too tight.
The length is right, but the shoe is too narrow and it's pinching my toes.
And there'd be no room for my insoles.
You know what?
I don't think I have the patience for this today.
They just don't make shoes like they used to.
I'll come back another time.
Have a nice day, ma'am.