The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
mid-priced restaurant bistro To make an arrangement to hold something for later.
Make a reservation.
All sold out or full of reservations.
Fully booked If something said earlier is true.
In that case go to attend Something that is kept back or withheld.
Reservation Let's try that faster.
Something that is kept back or withheld.
Reservation mid-priced restaurant bistro All sold out or full of reservations.
Fully booked go to attend To make an arrangement to hold something for later.
Make a reservation If something said earlier is true.
In that case Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Make a reservation I made a reservation for us already.
Make a reservation I need to make a hotel reservation.
Make a reservation How could you forget to make our hotel reservation?
Fully booked Our hotel is fully booked throughout the holidays.
Fully booked Fully booked I'm sorry sir, but the flight you requested is fully booked.
Fully booked That new restaurant on 5th street is fully booked for the next 3 months.
In that case In that case, I would like to cancel my reservation.
In that case In that case, I think it's best if we stay home.
In that case In that case, I'd rather go to Hong Kong instead of Taiwan.
Reservation We have a reservation under the name Mark.
Reservation The hotel says they lost our reservation.
Reservation I'm sorry sir, if you don't have a reservation, I'm afraid we can't seat you.
Bistro I heard they opened up a very nice French bistro down the block.
Bistro I know of a bistro that has very good food.
Bistro They have a great wine selection at this bistro.