The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To arrange An agreement to meet someone at a particular time.
Appointment Not busy.
Willing to talk to someone.
Available Check again Double check Having no available place or time.
Booked solid Be okay Work for you Planned at a specific time Scheduled Not okay No good Let's try that faster To arrange Be okay Work for you Not okay No good Be okay Work for you To arrange Be okay Work for you Check again Double check Be okay Work for you Check again Double check An agreement to meet someone at a particular time.
Appointment Check again Double check To arrange Be okay Work for you Check again Double check Planned at a specific time Scheduled Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Appointment Can you make an appointment for me to see the doctor?
Booked solid I can't get a hotel room.
They're booked solid until after the new year.
Double check I thought that I sent that email already, but let me double check.
Available I'm available at 3.
Let's meet then.
Work for you I'm free at 10.
Does that work for you?
No good Tuesday's no good.
I have meetings all day.
Appointment Can you make an appointment for me to see the doctor?
Booked solid I can't get a hotel room.
They're booked solid until after the new year.
Double check I thought that I sent that email already, but let me double check.
No good Tuesday's no good.
I have meetings all day.