The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something you really want to do.
Dream Place where a person lives.
Home Located or residing in a suburb.
Suburban A house which is built on one level.
Bungalow The years from 1960 to 1969.
The 60s The smallest possible amount or size.
Minimal A view across an area of land.
Landscaping An area of the garden with a hard surface.
Patio Unusual or old fashioned.
Quaint A place where you park your car.
Carport A kind of dry colour in sticks.
Pastel Material attached to the outside of a building.
Siding The triangular upper part of a wall.
Gable The top of a building.
Roof Covers unfold in front of a window.
Shutter The shelf above a fireplace.
Mantle Sheets of wood fit into a frame to form a wall.
Panelling A bluish green precious stone.
Turquoise Firm plastic which can be bent.
Vinyl Used as a term of endearment.
Sweetums Fashion Fad Having a feeling of home, comfortable.
Homie Used as a term of endearment.
Sweetie pie Not harmful to the environment.
Eco-friendly Installed in the floor.
In-floor A system for keeping rooms warm.
Heating To keep or keep possession.
Retain Relating to the sun, using its light.
Solar A flat section of a wall, door.
Panel Representative of the best and most typical.
Vintage Used as terms of endearment.
Dearest A chemical substance used to kill insects.
Pesticide A creature living in water.
Fish A small body of water.
Pond A plant with small yellow flowers.
Buttercup Based on scientific and industrial progress.
Technological Improvement or development Advancements A fence consisting of pickets.
Picket fence A form or style of room.
Open concept Have all knowledge or information of something.
All up on Let's try that faster A bluish-green precious stone.
Turquoise Unusual or old-fashioned.
Quaint Place where a person lives.
Home The triangular upper part of a wall.
Gable An area of the garden with a hard surface.
Patio Based on scientific and industrial progress.
Technological The top of a building.
Roof Material attached to the outside of a building.
Siding Used as a term of endearment.
Sweetums Used as terms of endearment.
Dearest Firm plastic which can be bent.
Vinyl Something you really want to do.
Dream The years from 1960 to 1969.
The 60s Representative of the best and most typical.
Vintage Improvement or development Advancements A system for keeping rooms warm.
Heating A chemical substance used to kill insects.
Pesticide A view across an area of land.
Landscaping A house which is built on one level.
Bungalow Installed in the floor.
In floor Having a feeling of home, comfortable.
Homey Located or residing in a suburb.
Suburban To keep or keep possession.
Retain Fashion Fad A place where you park your car.
Carport A fence consisting of pickets.
Picket fence A form or style of room.
Open concept A small body of water.
Pond Relating to the sun, using its light.
Solar A creature living in water.
Fish Covers unfold in front of a window.
Shutter Not harmful to the environment.
Eco-friendly The shelf above a fireplace.
Mantle A plant with small yellow flowers.
Buttercup Sheets of wood fit into a frame to form a wall.
Panelling The smallest possible amount or size.
Minimal Used as a term of endearment.
Sweetie pie Have all knowledge or information of something.
All up on A flat section of a wall, door.
Panel A kind of dry colour in sticks.
Pastel Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Picket fence The only thing holding in the cattle is the old wooden picket fence, so it's no wonder that the bull so easily charged through it and escaped.
Picket fence In her daydreams, she always imagined herself newly married and living in a house with a white picket fence in a picturesque countryside.
Picket fence My mother grew up in a neighbourhood where everyone's yard was enclosed by a picket fence.
Nowadays, some of those fences are still standing, but most of them have been replaced by chain link fences.
Vinyl When my family renovated our kitchen, we took up the old vinyl flooring and put down a hardwood floor.
Vinyl I love the vinyl floor in the bathroom because though it is made to look like tile, it is warmer and softer on bare feet.
Vinyl My friend is a vinyl fanatic.
He has vinyl records, vinyl floors, vinyl clothing, a vinyl couch, and even the siding on his house is vinyl.
Open concept A popular trend in architecture right now is designing open concept buildings.
Open concept Open concept homes are spacious and bright, but the effect is only truly achieved when the decor is consistent between the adjoining rooms.
Open concept The open concept and soothing colours of the hotel lobby took my breath away as I walked through the revolving door.
Eco-friendly Eco-friendly Carrying your groceries in a reusable cloth bag is more eco-friendly than using a new plastic one.
Eco-friendly My neighbours told me that they spray their lawn with an eco-friendly fertiliser.
Eco-friendly Eco-friendly It seems that more and more businesses are becoming concerned about protecting the environment and are using their eco-friendly practices and values as a key point in their advertisements.
All up on A friend of mine is all up on the latest trends in fashion.
When I was in high school, I was all up on finding a cure for cancer, but then I went to university and discovered that my real passion was composing music.
All up on My brother is an advocate for environmental awareness, so he's all up on crazy facts like how long it takes for a piece of plastic to disintegrate and how many fish die per year from ingesting garbage floating around in the ocean.