The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An electronic system enabling the recording and storage of voice messages.
Voicemail Set down in writing or voice or the like.
Record Essentially, fundamentally, basically.
The supplying or a supply of something required by the public.
Service Prepare Set up Let's try that faster.
An electronic system enabling the recording and storage of voice messages.
Voicemail Prepare Set up Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Basically Basically, what you're saying is, I have to buy a monkey?
Basically He basically just told me to get lost.
Basically So basically, if we had a million dollars we could buy the zoo?
Voicemail I've tried calling his mobile phone a few times now, I'll leave a voicemail.
Voicemail I hate receiving voicemails, they take up all my phone memory.
Voicemail Some creepy guy just sent me a random voicemail.
Set up For an extra fee, I can set up your television.
Set up This looks very complicated to set up.
Set up I don't know how to set things like this up, that's why I hire professionals.
Record Can you please record a message for the answering machine for when we are not here?
Record I think we should record an album together and become pop stars.
Record Record I'm going to record the basketball match so I can watch it later.
Service We provide a security service to local schools in the neighbourhood.
Service Service I don't think your idea of a car washing service will work as nobody has any cars.
Service The idea of a service to provide people with maids is great.
Thanks for watching!