Can you help me set up my voicemail message?
I just got the service and I'm not really sure what I'm supposed to say.
Sure.
You just basically got to let the caller know who they called and ask them for their contact information so you can call them back.
Okay, so I can say, this is Abby's voicemail.
I will call you later, so leave me your name and number.
That's more or less the idea, but try something that sounds more friendly.
Okay, so how about this?
This is Abby, and I'm really happy you called.
I promise I will give you a ring as soon as I can, so please leave me your name and number.
Talk to you soon!
Uh, a little too friendly, Abby.
Just say this.
Hi, you've reached Abby.
I'm unable to answer your call right now, but if you leave me your name and phone number, I will get back to you as soon as possible.
Thanks.
That's perfect.
Can you say that again and record it for me?