The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Hand covering, separating thumb from fingers.
Mitten Stop Wait Hold on A long, narrow piece of cloth worn around the neck.
Scarf A warm, tubular covering for the ears.
Earmuff Name you call someone you love.
Honey Head covering Hat Let's try that faster.
Hand covering, separating thumb from fingers.
Mitten Name you call someone you love.
Honey A long, narrow piece of cloth worn around the neck.
Scarf Head covering Hat Stop Wait Hold on A warm, tubular covering for the ears.
Earmuff Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Mitten For Christmas, his grandmother gave him a pair of mittens that she made herself.
Mitten I like mittens more than gloves because my fingers can keep each other warm.
Mitten My friend has a pair of mittens with snowflake designs on top.
Hold on Can you hold on a second while I tie my shoelaces?
Hold on Are those cookie crumbs I see on your sweater?
Hold on Just hold on a minute.
I just need to check my emails.
Scarf His scarf was so long that he could wrap it around his neck three times.
Scarf Some people wear scarves in the summer or indoors as a fashion accessory.
Scarf My mom wears silk scarves when she gets dressed up and wool scarves when she needs to go out in the cold.
Earmuff When I was a child, I used to wear earmuffs all the time, but now that I'm a teenager, I don't wear them because they're not cool.
Earmuff I was in a store the other day, and they were selling rainbow earmuffs and leopard print earmuffs, and all kinds of other neat designs.
Earmuff My best friend has a pair of earmuffs that he wears all the time.
He has a pair of earmuffs that he wears all the time, and he has a pair of earmuffs that he wears all the time, and he has a pair of earmuffs that he wears all the time.