The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Made especially for the needs of one person.
Custom made To ascertain the dimensions, quantity Measure Be sure Make sure Be more likely Tend An artistic or decorative design that repeats.
Pattern design Let's try that faster.
An artistic or decorative design that repeats.
Pattern design Be sure Make sure Be more likely Tend Made especially for the needs of one person.
Custom made To ascertain the dimensions, quantity Measure Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Custom made Brad got a custom made motorcycle.
It looks amazing.
Custom made Custom made I want to get a custom made sports car.
Custom made Her dress was custom made in Italy.
Measure I need to measure the length of this street.
Measure Help me measure the width of this box.
Measure Measure Many people try to measure the diameter of the earth.
Make sure Make sure you make some extra food just in case.
Make sure Please make sure you leave the door unlocked.
Make sure Can you make sure those reports are done by the end of this week?
Tend Don't buy cheap things.
They tend to break easily.
Tend I always tend to forget my keys in my car.
Tend People tend to forget what happened in the past.
Pattern design This flower pattern for my dress looks really nice.
Pattern design I bought wallpaper that has a black and red circle pattern.
Pattern design I want a simple and elegant dress pattern.
Thank you for watching.