EnglishPod.com Welcome to Bill's Fabric World.
What can I do for you today?
I was wondering if you guys also tailor clothes.
Sure we do.
We have the best tailors in the country.
What is it that you need exactly?
Well, I'm looking to get a custom-made suit.
Excellent.
We have the finest cash mirrors at affordable prices.
How about we get you measured?
Let's start off by measuring the width of your shoulders.
Now let's measure the length of your arms and this bit around your neck here.
Can you make sure you leave a little extra space in the collar?
My neck gets easily irritated.
No problem.
Now for your pants.
Let me just measure your waist and the inseam.
You might also want to leave a little extra room in the waist area.
I tend to gain a few pounds over the holidays.
Okay.
Now you can pick your fabric and pattern design.
Please follow me.