The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Go, or run somewhere, very quickly.
To dash.
Over.
Or.
A hollow device that can ring when struck.
Bell.
Cheer someone up.
Make one's spirit bright.
Make a gentle ringing noise.
Jingle.
Let's try that faster.
Go, or run somewhere, very quickly.
To dash.
A hollow device that can ring when struck.
Bell.
Make a gentle ringing noise.
Jingle.
Cheer someone up.
Make one's spirit bright.
Over.
Or.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
To dash.
He dashed to the finish line.
She dashed to the shopping mall to do her last minute Christmas shopping.
To dash.
Dashing through the wind and rain.
He finally reached the doctor's house.
Or.
Or the field and through the woods.
To grandmother's house we go.
Or.
There's a hospital in the village.
Just or that hill.
Or.
There is a storm brewing.
Or the plains.
Bell.
The church bells ring every day for mass.
Christmas bells always sound so cheerful.
Bell.
One of my favorite things at Christmas time is listening to a bell choir playing carol of the bells.
Make one's spirit bright.
The children's spirits brightened when Santa Claus walked into the room.
He made my spirit bright whenever he made a joke.
Make one's spirit bright.
Their spirits were bright when they learned that their grandparents were coming for Christmas.
Jingle.
The bells jingled every time a customer walked through the door of the small shop.
The coins jingled in her pocket.
Jingle.
The keys on his keychain jingled as he opened the door.