The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Informal of saying cigarette.
Stogie A receptacle for tobacco ashes and cigarettes and cigars.
Ashtray The end of the cigarette, which contains the filter and is placed into the mouth to smoke.
Butt Reduce the amount taken or used.
Cut down A solid, sticky substance that remains when tobacco is burned.
It accumulates in the lungs of smokers and is considered carcinogenic.
Tear Immediate, complete withdrawal from something.
Cold turkey A mechanical device for lighting a cigarette, cigar or pipe.
Lighter A patch that slowly releases nicotine into the body.
Nicotine patch A thin strip of wood or cardboard tipped with a chemical that ignites when scraped against a rough or specially treated surface.
Match Gum that slowly releases nicotine into the body.
Nicotine chewing gum Smoking a cigarette once, a puff, share a cigarette with someone.
Drag To act more forcefully, to regulate or repress.
Crack down To start smoking a cigarette.
Light up The strength of mind to carry out a decision.
Willpower A strong impulse, inner drive or yearning.
Urge A box of cigarettes.
Pack of smokes Let's try that faster!
A receptacle for tobacco ashes and cigarettes and cigars.
Ashtray Informal of saying cigarette.
Stogie To start smoking a cigarette.
Light up A strong impulse, inner drive or yearning.
Urge A box of cigarettes.
Pack of smokes A solid, sticky substance that remains when tobacco is burned.
It accumulates in the lungs of smokers and is considered carcinogenic.
Tar The strength of mind to carry out a decision.
Willpower The end of the cigarette which contains the filter and is placed into the mouth to smoke.
Butt Immediate, complete withdrawal from something.
Cold turkey A patch that slowly releases nicotine into the body.
Nicotine patch Reduce the amount taken or used.
Cut down Smoking a cigarette once.
A puff.
Share a cigarette with someone.
Drag A thin strip of wood or cardboard tipped with a chemical that ignites when scraped against a rough or specially treated surface.
Match A mechanical device for lighting a cigarette, cigar or pipe.
Lighter To act more forcefully, to regulate or repress.
Crack down Gum that slowly releases nicotine into the body.
Nicotine chewing gum Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Crack down The police is cracking down on drunk driving in our city.
Crack down The president has passed a law that will crack down on possession of illegal substances.
Crack down Our school has really started to crack down on tardiness.
Cut down You should really cut down on the amount of salt you eat.
It's not good for you.
Cut down Cut down Our company has decided to cut down our workload, so from now on we leave at 3pm every Friday.
Cut down My doctor told me I need to cut down on fatty foods because of my heart condition.
Light up Honey, you can't light up here.
We are in a non-smoking area.
Light up John is addicted to smoking.
Anytime and anywhere he has a chance, he lights up immediately.
Light up Light up The government is making it more difficult to light up with all these anti-smoking laws.
Willpower I don't have the willpower to stick to my diet.
It's so hard.
Willpower Kathy is a workaholic.
She needs to gather more willpower and refuse to work extra hours.
Willpower Willpower and discipline are essential to any person that wants to succeed in life.
Urge Willpower I was so angry at him that I felt a sudden urge to hit him.
Urge Last night my wife got an uncontrollable urge to smoke every hour.
It was weird.
Urge Willpower When Carol was pregnant, she once had an urge to eat a bacon and tuna sandwich.
It was disgusting.