The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something that is spread all over an area.
Scattered Small balls of ice that fall from the sky.
Hail Small drops of water that float in the air.
Fog A very strong snowstorm.
Blizzard Light rain Drizzle To enter or arrive from somewhere.
Come in from A statement of what will happen in the future.
Forecast Describes when air is not clear because of fog or smog.
Hazy Stay near a certain level or place.
Hover around A collection of different kinds of things.
Mixed bag The amount of sky that is covered with clouds.
Saying that some type of weather will happen.
Call for Rainfall in a short time.
Shower Leading edge of a cooler and drier mass of air.
Cold front Very cold Chilly Limited to one area.
Isolated Strong sudden rainstorm Downpour Strong sudden increase in wind speed.
Gust A mix of rain and snow.
Sleet Having some clouds and some sun.
Partly cloudy skies Let's try that faster.
Strong sudden rainstorm Downpour Something that is spread all over an area.
Scattered Leading edge of a cooler and drier mass of air.
Cold front Stay near a certain level or place.
Hover around A mix of rain and snow.
Sleet Very cold Chilly The amount of sky that is covered with clouds.
Light rain Drizzle A very strong snowstorm.
Blizzard Rainfall in a short time.
Shower A collection of different kinds of things.
Mixed bag A statement of what will happen in the future.
Forecast Strong sudden increase in wind speed.
Gust Small balls of ice that fall from the sky.
Hail To enter or arrive from somewhere.
Come in from Having some clouds and some sun.
Partly cloudy skies Small drops of water that floats in the air.
Fog Describes when air is not clear because of fog or smog.
Hazy Limited to one area.
Isolated Saying that some type of weather will happen.
Call for Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Scattered The children scattered in all directions when the teacher approached.
Scattered Your room is a mess.
There is trash scattered everywhere.
Scattered I accidentally knocked over the plant and scattered dirt all over the floor.
Downpour I forgot my umbrella at home today.
And a downpour just hit.
Downpour The weather here is terrible.
You have downpours almost every day.
Downpour Come in from A massive downpour hit us Monday night.
With 150 millimeters of rain falling in less than three hours.
Come in from I have a friend that is coming in from Brazil this weekend.
Come in from England has many migrant workers coming in from all over the world.
Come in from Mike is coming in tonight from his trip to Finland.
Forecast The president's forecast of the economy is very optimistic.
Forecast Based on our forecast of inflation, we made a small price increase to our products.
Forecast Weatherman's forecast The weatherman's forecast is always wrong.
Hover around The temperature will hover around zero degrees all week.
Hover around Hover around I wish he would stop hovering around me and just go away.
Hover around The company's margin this year is hovering around the 40% mark.