EnglishPod.com And now, let's go to Kenny Williams for today's weather forecast.
Thank you, Bill, and good morning Salt Lake City.
What's the weather looking like today, Kenny?
Well, it's a bit of a mixed bag in Utah today.
We've got heavy cloud cover here in northern Utah, and we're calling for scattered showers throughout the day with a daytime high of 45 degrees.
Now, if we move down to the south of the state, we can see that a cold front is moving in.
We can expect clear skies, but it will be quite cold with temperatures hovering around the 30-degree mark.
It's a chilly day, folks, so don't forget your coats.
What about tomorrow, Kenny?
Do you have good news for us?
Well, it'll be a rainy day for northern Utah.
We can expect some isolated downpours in the morning.
Winds will be coming in from the northeast, with gust reaching 23 miles per hour.
Salt Lake City can expect the rain to turn to sleet in the evening.
Things are looking a bit better for the south.
We'll see cloudy skies with a chance of showers.
Later in the day, we can expect partly cloudy skies with a forecast high of 38 degrees.
You heard it, folks.
It's going to be a cold one.
That's right, Bill.
We'll have more later on today on the 6 o'clock news.
That's the weather forecast for this morning.