The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To officially begin something Kick A step in a process Stage Something only appropriate for girls or women Sissy Game Match One who provides services, etc.
as for a convention Host Let's try that faster A step in a process Stage Something only appropriate for girls or women Sissy To officially begin something Kick Game Match One who provides services, etc.
as for a convention Host Now, say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Stage There are several stages a team must go through in order to make the finals.
Stage This morning, I finally moved on to the next If we start her on these medications, we can cure her because she is still only in the first stages of the illness.
Kick Today, we are kicking off a new line of cosmetics.
Kick At the opening ceremony, we will kick off the beginning of the weekend conference.
Kick The fundraiser's kickoff will be tomorrow at 5 p.m.
Match It's Spain versus Brazil in the final match Match I can't make it to the match today, but let me know how it goes.
Match This soccer match is going to be nerve-wracking because it is my school against our rival school across town.
Host The host country put on quite an elaborate show at the opening ceremonies.
Host The host school went wild when the home team won the championship.
Host I hardly got any time to speak to the host of the party because she was constantly running around and talking to the other guests.
Match Sissy I think soccer is a sissy sport Host Sissy That kid is such a sissy when his mom is around, but he's fine when she's gone.
Sissy The whole camping trip she was being such a sissy about having to sleep on the ground and not being able to shower.