EnglishPod.com What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Don't you know what day it is?
Umm...no.
It's only the day when the world's biggest sporting event is kicking off.
What?
The World Cup!
The first match is today.
It's Mexico versus South Africa.
It's going to be a really good match.
Both teams have a very strong offense and have skilled players.
I think that South Africa will probably dominate the first half since they are the host country and all.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
The only sporting event we watch at home is the Super Bowl.
This is bigger than the Super Bowl, man!
Teams from thirty two countries compete against each other every four years and fight to win that trophy.
They first start in a group stage with eight groups.
Each group having four teams.
The top two teams pass on to an elimination stage before going on to the semi-finals and the quarter-finals.
Sounds interesting, but soccer doesn't really appeal to me.
Are you kidding?
Over seven hundred million people watch the final match of the 2006 World Cup.
It's a very exciting and nerve-wracking sport.
Each nation is cheering on their team, hoping they will become the next champion.
So far, Brazil is the team with the most titles under their belt.
They're really good.
All I know about soccer is that you can't use your hands and that players are always falling down trying to get a free kick or penalty kick.
It seems like a sissy sport to me.
Whatever.
I'm going to go watch the opening match.