The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Popular dance music, especially of the late 1970s.
Disco House Crib A performance, especially by a band.
Gig Used to say that something makes sense.
Ride on An authority figure, like the boss or government.
The man A negative situation.
Bummer How's it going?
How are you?
How's it hanging?
Cool, excellent, enjoyable.
Groovy An enclosed place for roller skating.
Roller rink The latest, cool.
Far out Sexy, attractive.
Foxy Part of a neighborhood surrounded by four streets.
Block Talk informally to a person you're attracted to.
Chat someone up.
Relax Mellow out Money, informal and old-fashioned.
Bread All right, cool.
Gravy A person who is unreliable or irresponsible.
Jive turkey Ask someone for money.
Hit someone up for.
Leave quickly.
Book Food, informal.
Grub Let's try that faster.
A person who is unreliable or irresponsible.
Jive turkey Used to say that something makes sense.
Ride on Food, informal.
Grub Popular dance music, especially of the late 1970s.
Disco Part of a neighborhood surrounded by four streets.
Block An authority figure, like the boss or government.
The man A negative situation.
Bummer Leave quickly.
Book Money, informal and old-fashioned.
Bread A performance especially by a band.
Gig An enclosed place for roller skating.
Roller rink The latest, cool.
Far out Sexy, attractive.
Foxy House Crib Talk informally to a person you're attracted to.
Chat someone up.
Ask someone for money.
Hit someone up for.
Cool, excellent, enjoyable.
Groovy Relax Mellow out Alright, cool.
Gravy How's it going?
How are you?
How is it hanging?
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Groovy Where did you buy that groovy shirt?
I really like it.
Groovy The party at Paul's house last night was groovy.
Groovy James has a groovy new motorcycle and he said he would let me ride it.
Far out I went to the cinema and saw the new Star Trek movie.
It was far out.
Far out You got a job at Morgan Stanley?
That's far out, man.
Congratulations.
Far out Did you see how fast that car went?
That was far out.
Mellow out I don't feel like going out tonight.
I think I would just mellow out here at home.
Mellow out Chopin really mellows me out when I'm feeling tense.
Mellow out After final exams, let's go down to the beach and mellow out.
Ride on Ride on.
You got a high score.
That's amazing.
Ride on You got the job?
Ride on Ride on Jenny was right on when she told me she thought Rick was no good for me.
I should have listened to her.
Book Book This party is really boring.
Let's book and go to another bar.
Book The police arrived and started arresting people, so my friend and I booked as fast as we could.
Book Book Dan saw his ex-girlfriend at the restaurant and started to get nervous and ended up booking.