The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Mixed vegetables served cold.
Salad.
Deep fried strips of potato.
French fries.
A type of sandwich with the beef patty.
Hamburger.
Food that is not healthy.
Junk food.
To block or get in the way of something.
Clog.
A fatty substance found in animal tissue.
Cholesterol.
What do you think?
How about...
Bread with tomato sauce and cheese on top.
Pizza.
Chicken pieces cooked in hot oil.
Fried chicken.
A food with bread and sausage in the middle.
Hot dog.
A useless or hopeless situation.
Lost cause.
Let's try that faster.
Bread with tomato sauce and cheese on top.
Pizza.
Chicken pieces cooked in hot oil.
Fried chicken.
A useless or hopeless situation.
Lost cause.
What do you think?
How about...
A food with bread and sausage in the middle.
Hot dog.
Mixed vegetables served cold.
Salad.
Deep fried strips of potato.
French fries.
A type of sandwich with the beef patty.
Hamburger.
Food that is not healthy.
Junk food.
A fatty substance found in animal tissue.
Cholesterol.
To block or get in the way of something.
Clog.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Junk food.
I have junk food once or twice a week.
If you want to lose weight, you should try having less junk food.
Junk food.
The good thing about junk food is that it's fast and cheap.
Clog.
The water pipes in my house are clogged.
Your toilet is clogged.
You should call a plumber.
Clog.
I am worried that eating all these fatty foods will clog up my heart.
Cholesterol.
Eggs are high in cholesterol.
I have to watch what I eat because I have high cholesterol.
Cholesterol.
It is dangerous to have high cholesterol levels because it can lead to health complications.
How about How about we go to the movies instead?
How about How about I cook and you clean the house?
How about How about we go on vacation this year?
Lost cause.
This company is a lost cause.
He doesn't want to be helped.
He is a lost cause.
Lost cause.
Continue fighting the disease.
It's not a lost cause.