Do you want to go catch a movie tonight?
I can't.
I have to go to the gym.
Come on.
You can go tomorrow.
Just skip it today.
It's not as if you're going to get in trouble.
Actually, I will.
I'm working out with a personal trainer that gets on my case if I don't go.
I like it because it makes me feel more obligated to go and get healthy.
That's cool.
Does your personal trainer basically teach you how to work out?
Yeah.
He makes a workout plan depending on the areas I want to work on or the muscles I want to build.
Like, for example, in order to get better muscle tone in my abs, pecs, and biceps, he makes me work out with free weights.
Then for my quads, calves, and hamstrings, I do leg lifts or squats.
Sounds like you're really getting into shape.