EnglishPod.com Hey honey, how was your day?
It was alright.
I ran into Bill and we got to talking for a while.
He's in a bit of a jam.
Why?
What happened?
Well, his son had an accident.
Bill doesn't have health insurance.
This really got me thinking, and I wondered if we shouldn't look into a couple of different HMOs.
Yeah, you're right.
We aren't getting any younger and our kids are getting older.
Exactly.
I searched on the web and found a couple of HMOs with low co-pays and good coverage.
The deductibles are low too.
Sounds good.
Although, do you think we can qualify for insurance?
Those insurance companies are real pirates when it comes to money.
Well, we don't have any pre-existing illnesses or conditions, so we should be fine.
I wish our company or country provided us with health care.
Not in a million years.