EnglishPod.com It's Christmas Eve and I have all these presents to deliver.
Where's your Christmas spirit?
What'll happen when all the children wake up tomorrow and don't find any gifts in their stockings?
Sorry buddy, you were parked in a no-parking zone.
You were speeding AND you have no ID.
Besides that, even if we let you go now, your sleigh's been impounded and those reindeer were taken to the city zoo.
What?
This is unbelievable.
What's this world coming to?
Christmas is ruined!
What's that up ahead?
It looks like...
Elves!
Whoa!
They're shooting candy canes!
Mayday!
We're under heavy attack!
We need backup!
Thanks for watching!