The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Take someone who is arrested to a place where other criminals are kept.
Take someone to jail.
Arrest.
Book.
Say something is true when some people say it may not be true.
Claim.
Large sock.
Traditionally, Christmas gifts are put inside on the Christmas Eve.
Stocking.
Drive faster than legal speed limit.
Speed.
Held by the police.
Impound.
Damaged or destroyed.
Ruined.
Large deer that lives in the north part of the globe.
Reindeer.
Small creatures in stories that have pointed ears and magic powers.
Elf.
A stick-shaped candy with red and white curves on the top.
Candy cane.
Being attacked or hurt.
Under heavy.
Help.
Back up.
Charge.
Make a moving car move to the side of the road.
Pull someone over.
A sudden attack.
Ambush.
Small gifts that are put in the Christmas stocking.
Stocking stuffer.
Christmas ornament.
Let's try that faster.
Say something is true when some people say it may not be true.
Claim.
Arrest.
Book.
Held by the police.
Impound.
A stick-shaped candy with red and white curves on the top.
Candy cane.
Charge.
Take someone who is arrested to a place where other criminals are kept.
Take someone to jail.
Damaged or destroyed.
Ruined.
Christmas ornament.
Small gifts that are put in the Christmas stocking.
Stocking stuffer.
Large deer that lives in the north part of the globe.
Reindeer.
A sudden attack.
Ambush.
Large sock.
Traditionally, Christmas gifts are put inside on the Christmas Eve.
Stocking.
Help.
Back up.
Small creatures in stories that have pointed ears and magic powers.
Elf.
Make a moving car move to the side of the road.
Pull someone over.
Drive faster than legal speed limit.
Speed.
Being attacked or hurt.
Under heavy.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Take someone to jail.
Sir, I'm sorry to inform you that your son was taken to jail.
Her husband was arrested for stealing and he was taken to jail yesterday.
Take someone to jail.
You will be taken to jail if you hit me.
Book.
We just booked this guy for murder.
Book, this guy officer.
He was trying to break into my car.
Book.
Watch out for that guy.
He was booked for fighting in the street.
Claim.
Daniel claimed to be the son of a government minister, but later we found out he was lying.
The criminals claim to have a gun.
Claim.
This man here is claiming to know your father.
Speed.
Slow down.
I don't want to get caught speeding.
Speed.
I got caught speeding and now I must pay a fine.
I was speeding, but luckily the police officer didn't see me.
Impound.
My father's car was impounded because it was parked in a no parking zone.
The police impounded this ship as it was carrying illegal drugs.
Impound.
What should I do if my car gets impounded?
Ruined.
It's been raining for five days.
Our vacation is ruined.
Ruined.
Look at this hole.
You've ruined my favorite pair of jeans.
Ruined.
Sam, you've been caught stealing from the company.
Your chances for a promotion are ruined.
Under heavy.
We're under heavy attack.
We're under heavy fire.
Under heavy.
The prime minister is under heavy security.
Back up.
This looks like a difficult situation.
I think we're going to need backup.
Back up.
The police called for backup because the criminal had a gun.
I'll be your backup in case something goes wrong.