The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A small round piece of money usually made from metal.
Coin A small container used to store coins.
Piggy bank Form of money that is made from paper.
Bill A coin worth one fourth of a dollar.
Quarter A coin worth one tenth of a dollar.
Dime A coin worth one twentieth of a dollar.
Nickel A coin that is worth one cent or one one hundredth of a dollar.
Penny Let's try that faster.
A small round piece of money usually made from metal.
Coin A small container used to store coins.
Piggy bank Form of money that is made from paper.
Bill A coin worth one fourth of a dollar.
Quarter A coin worth one tenth of a dollar.
Dime A coin that is worth one cent or one one hundredth of a dollar.
Penny A coin worth one twentieth of a dollar.
Nickel A small container used to store coins.
Piggy bank Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Coin I don't like having coins in my pocket.
Coin Some rare or old coins are worth more than their face value now.
Coin I used to collect stamps and coins when I was younger.
Piggy bank I used to save a lot of money in my piggy bank.
Piggy bank I bought my son a piggy bank so he could learn how to save.
Piggy bank I don't want to break my piggy bank unless I have a very good reason to spend that money.
Penny Penny I remember when gumballs used to cost a penny.
Penny The face of Abraham Lincoln is on the penny.
Penny Nowadays there is nothing that costs a penny in the United States anymore.
Bill The $100 bill is the highest denomination in the American currency.
Bill Can you change this $50 bill for me?
Bill This machine only accepts one and five dollar bills.
Bob is counting his dimes and nickels.
Nickel Gas prices Gas prices will go up a nickel per liter tomorrow.
Nickel Do you have a nickel I could borrow?