EnglishPod.com Okay class, settle down.
I have the results of your individual personality tests.
I am going to hand them out, and if you'd like, you can read them out loud to the rest of the class.
I'll read mine!
Okay, go ahead.
It says here that I am adventurous, outgoing, and easygoing.
It says that I'm a little superstitious and occasionally naive.
That's not true.
Well, the test isn't 100% accurate.
Is that all it says?
No.
It also says that I'm open-minded with great ambition, but that I can also be reckless and clumsy.
This is stupid.
Okay, anyone else wants to read theirs?
I'll go.
It says that I'm an extroverted, well-balanced person.
It says I am generous, outspoken, and very diligent.
This is so true.
It also says that I am a magnanimous, eloquent, and daring.
This is totally me.
Whatever.
These tests are baloney.