Did you read this?
It says that the number one New Year resolution people make is to spend more time with friends and family.
Why would that be funny?
Well, think about it.
We are a society that is always on the go, not because we have to, but because we want to.
Why?
We work hard and spend less time at home because we are trying to provide for our family with goods and services that are usually unnecessary.
I don't agree, but anyways, I think you should start thinking of a New Year's resolution yourself.
What's the point?
We always make New Year's resolutions, and by February we will have forgotten about them.
It's pointless.
Well, maybe then you should resolve to stick into your goals and objectives.
What about you?
Your gym bag is gathering dust and you still have brand new running shoes that are yet to be jogged in.
Well, I would go if you kept your promise of going to the gym with me every day.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.