The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
New Year's decision or plan New Year's resolution Very busy and active On the go Idea you try to make people understand Point Bring to an end Resolve Completely new Brand new Let's try that faster.
Completely new Brand new Very busy and active On the go Bring to an end Resolve Idea you try to make people understand Point New Year's decision or plan New Year's resolution Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
New Year's resolution My family always made separate New Year's resolutions, but this year we decided to make one resolution for the entire family.
New Year's resolution His New Year's resolution is to finish a marathon.
New Year's resolution A popular New Year's resolution is to go to the gym and eat well.
On the go Our family is always on the go with our kids' extracurricular activities.
On the go He is always on the go with his job.
On the go She prefers being on the go to sitting around and doing nothing.
Point What's the point of giving her another second chance?
She will only break your heart again.
Point It's pointless to go now.
We will be an hour late.
Point There's no point in telling me twice.
I learned my lesson.
Resolve He resolved to devote his entire life to finding a cure for cancer.
Resolve Resolve In order to become the best pianist, you should resolve to practice every day.
Resolve Resolve The warrior resolved to show no mercy to the enemy when he saw the destruction they had caused.
Brand new Have you seen my brand new bike?
It's pink with yellow ribbons.
Brand new He drove around town, showing off his brand new sports car.
Brand new She enjoyed showing off her brand new baby to her friends and family.