The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Absurd, not logical.
Ridiculous.
To admit a fault or crime.
Confess.
Informal way of saying pregnant.
Bun in the oven.
State of being affected deeply in mind or emotion.
Overwhelmed.
A feeling of being supplanted.
Apprehensive of losing affection or position.
Jealousy.
Very crazy.
Insane.
Destroy.
Ruin.
A cruel or unkind person.
Bastard.
To have a sexual relationship with someone who is not your husband, wife, boyfriend, or girlfriend.
Unfaithful.
A person who is not who they seem.
A person who lies.
A fraud.
A person who has a relationship with a married man or a married woman.
A homewrecker.
Dishonest behavior.
Deceit.
And a relationship with.
Split up with.
Listen to another person's conversation.
Ease drop.
Let's try that faster.
A feeling of being supplanted.
Apprehensive of losing affection or position.
Jealousy.
Listen to another person's conversation.
Ease drop.
And a relationship with.
Split up with.
Informal way of saying pregnant.
But in the oven.
A cruel or unkind person.
Bastard.
Destroy.
Ruin.
To have a sexual relationship with someone who is not your husband, wife, boyfriend, or girlfriend.
Unfaithful.
A person who has a relationship with a married man or a married woman.
A homewrecker.
Absurd, not logical.
Ridiculous.
To admit a fault or crime.
Confess.
Very crazy.
Insane.
Dishonest behavior.
Deceit.
A state of being affected deeply in mind or emotion.
Overwhelmed.
A person who is not who they seem.
A person who lies.
A fraud.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Confess.
Barbara confessed to me that she stole the wallet.
I have to confess something.
I'm in love with you.
Confess.
I'm innocent.
I'll never confess to this crime.
Overwhelmed.
I was overwhelmed with joy when I discovered my wife is pregnant.
She is overwhelmed with sadness since her dog died.
Overwhelmed.
Don't be overwhelmed by all the work you have to do.
Take your time.
I don't want to talk to you anymore.
You are a jerk.
My sister had a boyfriend who was a real jerk.
I don't mean to be a jerk, but can you leave my house?
I couldn't help myself.
When I saw that car, I had to buy it.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't help myself.
I just started laughing.
She couldn't help herself, and so she ate the cake by herself.
I had a happy life until my mother-in-law came into the picture.
Our company grew so much after the new CEO came into the picture.
My life feels complete now that you came into the picture.
Thank you for watching.