EnglishPod.com This is ridiculous.
I can't believe you've been sleeping with someone else.
How could you do this?
You know what?
I'm out of here.
Wait!
Doctor, how is this possible?
I haven't cheated on my boyfriend.
I have something to confess.
I'm sorry, Veronica.
I lied.
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
I lied.
You aren't even pregnant.
There's no body in the oven.
I was just so overwhelmed with jealousy that I couldn't help myself.
Veronica, I love you!
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
It's me, Daniel.
Don't you remember me from high school?
I sat behind you in science class.
I used to go to every football game and watch you in the cheerleading squad.
You're insane.
We never even spoke.
Why did you lie like that to my boyfriend?
Because, Veronica, it's not fair.
I love you.
I have since the first day we met.
Everything was going fine until that jerk came into the picture and ruined everything.
I went to med school and became a doctor for you.
You always said how you wanted to marry a doctor.
You will be mine now, one way or another.
I heard everything, you lying bastard.
Get your hands off of her.