The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Let's try that faster.
A fold, ridge, or crease in the skin.
Wrinkle.
A plastic surgery on breasts to make them bigger.
Breast implant.
Plastic surgery.
Cosmetic surgery.
A medical protein injected into facial muscles.
Botox.
Too proud of good looks.
Vein.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I wish my girlfriend was less vain than she is now.
Vein.
Why am I surrounded by so many vain people?
Vain.
Stop being so vain and give the guy a shot.
Wrinkle.
These wrinkles are the result of so many bitter years.
Why is my skin getting so wrinkled?
Wrinkle.
Excessive use of makeup makes skin get premature wrinkles.
Botox.
I really don't like girls who have Botox.
I saw an actress with Botox and I think it ruined her looks.
Botox.
I wonder how much it costs to get Botox.
Cosmetic surgery.
I've heard that in Korea it's really cheap to get cosmetic surgery.
I wouldn't have cosmetic surgery unless someone was paying for it.
Cosmetic surgery.
Cosmetic surgery has become so popular in the last few years.
Breast implants.
Breast implants look so fake.
There are many men who like women with breast implants.
Breast implants.
I think breast implants can be dangerous.
Thanks for watching.