EnglishPod.com What are you doing?
Look at me, I look so old.
I look as if I were 30.
Come on, stop being so vain.
You look great.
You are beautiful.
Yes I am, but I think it's time for some plastic surgery.
I'm tired of these wrinkles and sagging skin.
See?
I don't see any wrinkles or sagging skin.
You're 25.
Stop being ridiculous.
Besides, I think that people who get Botox, have facelifts or tummy tucks look weird.
It doesn't look natural.
Whatever, I think I'm going to get liposuction and a nose job and some breast implants as well.
I think you need to get brain surgery.
I honestly don't think you need cosmetic surgery.
You look amazing.
I thought you were my friend and would support me on this.
I just want to feel better about myself and feel more attractive.
You don't need plastic surgery to do that.
You're fine the way you are and you have guys drooling all over you.
Plus, plastic surgery hurts.
Really?
Yeah, when I got my nose job I was black and blue for a week.