The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Phrase used to express that you haven't seen someone in a very long time.
Long time no see.
A class where instructions are given at the first day of school.
Orientation.
To become accustomed to one's new surroundings.
Settle into.
Fraternity house.
Place where members of a fraternity live and socialize.
Frat house.
A term used to call people that are of a fraternity.
Frat boy.
To quit or not continue a class.
Drop.
Academic mark.
Credit.
The specific focus of your undergraduate program.
Major.
Let's try that faster.
Fraternity house.
Place where members of a fraternity live and socialize.
Frat house.
Phrase used to express that you haven't seen someone in a very long time.
Long time no see.
To quit or not continue a class.
Drop.
To become accustomed to one's new surroundings.
Settle into.
Academic mark.
Credit.
A term used to call people that are of a fraternity.
Frat boy.
The specific focus of your undergraduate program.
Major.
A class where instructions are given at the first day of school.
Orientation.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Orientation starts in an hour and then we have lunch.
Orientation.
We have orientation this week and start classes next week.
Orientation is really good since it shows you how college life works.
Settle into.
It took me a couple weeks to settle into my new apartment.
I find it hard to settle into this city.
Settle into.
My parents are helping me settle into my new dorm.
Credit.
I need five more credits to graduate.
This class is worth ten credits.
Credit.
My tuition each year is based on the number of credits I take.
Major.
I haven't picked a major yet.
I will major in political science.
Major.
I have a major in business and a minor in Chinese.
Long time no see.
Carl, where have you been?
Hey Bob, long time no see.
Long time no see.
Hey guys, long time no see.
How have you been?