EnglishPod.com Hey Jordan is that you?
Long time no see.
Oh hey, no kidding.
I haven't seen you since orientation three months ago.
So how you been?
Settling into college life okay?
Yeah, I think so.
I pledged Phi Iota Alpha, so I'm living at the frat house now.
Oh, so you're a frat boy now, huh?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It's got a lot of support and good suggestions from the guys.
What about you?
What have you been up to?
Well, not much.
I'm still living at home and commuting to school.
I ended up dropping that metalworking class I was so excited about.
It just wasn't as interesting as I'd hoped.
The guidance counselor suggested that I focus on my prerequisite courses so that I can make sure the credits count.
That sounds smart but kinda boring.
Yeah, it is a little bit.
I joined the great outdoors club though, which has been a lot of fun.
We've gone on two camping trips already and I've made some good friends.
That's cool.
Hey, so have you decided on your major yet?
Definitely pre-med.
What about you?
I still have no clue, but we don't have to declare a major until our sophomore year.
So I've got time.
Oops!
I'm late for class.
Gotta run.
Okay, take care.
Hey, nice running into you.
Yeah, you too.