The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A very strong desire for something.
Craving Attractive Tempting A medicine or treatment Remedy Food that is sold by a store to be eaten elsewhere.
Takeout Delicious Appetizing Let's try that faster!
Delicious Appetizing Food that is sold by a store to be eaten elsewhere.
Takeout A very strong desire for something.
Craving A medicine or treatment Remedy Attractive Tempting Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Tempting The apple is so big and red, it's so tempting to take a bite.
Tempting Tempting The food looks so good, it's tempting to eat it all.
Tempting He's such a jerk, it's so tempting to just walk up and slap him.
Craving I've been craving Mexican food ever since I came to China.
Craving He quit smoking two days ago, so he's been craving a cigarette.
I'm craving something sweet right now.
Takeout Whenever I'm too tired, I get takeout and watch a movie at home.
Takeout Takeout If you don't have time to sit in the restaurant, you can get takeout.
Takeout Even though takeout is really convenient, it's better if you eat the food fresh.
Remedy Ice cream is a great remedy for a broken heart.
But a new fling is even better.
Remedy A Bloody Mary is the best remedy for a hangover.
Remedy An ice pack would be the best remedy for your black eye.
Appetizing Everything on the menu looks so appetizing.
Appetizing Appetizing I searched the menu, but couldn't find anything that looked remotely appetizing.
Appetizing My grandma's pies are so appetizing, you won't be able to resist.