EnglishPod.com This place has the best sesame chicken.
Yeah, I've been craving Chinese for such a long time.
I used to get takeout all the time.
It's definitely been a while.
Let's start off with some crab rangoon.
Oh yeah, that sounds good.
I think I'm going to get the sesame chicken with fried rice, a spring roll, and egg drop soup.
It's so tempting to order everything on the menu.
It all looks so appetizing.
I think I'll get General Tso's chicken, hot and sour soup, fried wontons, and white rice.
Aren't you supposed to be on a diet?
You should at least get brown rice.
I don't think so.
I hate brown rice.
And I'm so sick of eating healthy all the time.
I've been eating so much salad, I swear I've forgotten what meat tastes like.
There's no better remedy than some nice, greasy, calorie-laden Chinese food.
I might even get an order of broccoli beef.
Oh gosh, I'm so hungry.
Let's call the waitress over.