The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Become out of control.
Got a little out of hand.
Very drunk.
Wasted.
To go to a place.
Hit.
To vomit.
Barf.
To happen a certain way.
Turned out.
Medicine you take to cure a headache.
Painkillers.
I agree.
I understand.
Tell me about it.
I feel very bad.
I feel like death.
Feel like you are going to vomit.
Nauseous.
Drink alcohol when you have a hangover to cure it.
Hair of the dog.
Vomit.
Through up.
Lacking water.
Dehydrated.
To beat loudly and quickly.
Pounding.
Let's try that faster.
To beat loudly and quickly.
Pounding.
Feel like you are going to vomit.
Nauseous.
Drink alcohol when you have a hangover to cure it.
Hair of the dog.
To happen a certain way.
Turned out.
To go to a place.
Hit.
I agree.
I understand.
Tell me about it.
Lacking water.
Dehydrated.
Threw up.
Wasted.
Become out of control.
Got a little out of hand.
Medicine you take to cure a headache.
Painkillers.
To vomit.
Barf.
I feel very bad.
I feel like death.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Got a little out of hand.
Honey, the kids are getting a little out of hand.
Can you do something?
Got a little out of hand.
Guys, this argument is getting out of hand.
Let's all calm down.
Got a little out of hand.
The party last night got out of hand.
The neighbors called the police.
You have to come to the party tonight.
It's going to be a beer fest.
It was a real food fest last night at Pete's house.
There was enough food to feed a small country.
We have to go to Jessica's birthday party.
It's going to be a chick fest for sure.
Nauseous.
It's normal to feel nauseous sometimes during a pregnancy.
Every time I get on a boat, I feel really nauseous.
Nauseous.
If you get nauseous on the plane, take two of these pills.
Threw up.
Carl got on the roller coaster and threw up all over me.
If you feel like you are going to throw up, be sure to tell me so I can pull over.
Threw up.
If you have too much to drink, you will throw up later.
I have a pounding pain in my head.
Do you have any aspirin?
Pounding.
I can't take it anymore.
I've had a pounding headache all morning.
Pounding.
My head started pounding the moment I saw my ex-girlfriend.