EnglishPod.com Are you okay, man?
You don't look very well.
I feel terrible.
I went out last night with Trevor and things got a little out of hand.
Nice.
So where did you guys go?
We hit up a couple of local bars and met up with some friends.
Everything was cool until Mike came along.
And it turned out that it was his birthday yesterday.
Oh no!
Mike's birthday is a drink fest for sure.
Tell me about it.
We drank everything in the bar.
Is that why you missed work today?
Yeah, I woke up this morning feeling really nauseous.
I threw up like five times.
Ew!
I was so dehydrated that I drank a gallon of water and my head has been pounding all day.
I swear, I am never going to drink again.
Too bad, man.
Tonight is Tracy's going away party and she asked if you were going to go.
Oh yeah?
I'm there.