The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Wingman On the brink Tied Kick off Throw in No question about it By a mile Foul Penalty kick Goal kick Corner kick Out of bounds Offside Goalkeeper Defender Match Pitch Championship Kick off Defender Goal kick On the brink Wingman Penalty kick Championship Offside Goalkeeper No question about it Out of bounds Match Tied By a mile Pitch Throw in Foul Corner kick Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
On the brink Look, we don't have any money, we're on the brink of going bankrupt.
On the brink The two countries are on the brink of war.
On the brink We are on the brink of an important discovery.
No question about it No question about it, Ecuador has a great soccer team.
No question about it There's absolutely no question about it, that was the best game of the series.
No question about it There's no question about it, we're in a recession now.
By a mile He missed the goal by a mile By a mile No, that's wrong, you're off by a mile.
By a mile The competition is ahead of us by a mile.
We tied the game at 3-3.
What an amazing game, it's a tie.
We're tied for first place.
Foul Hey ref, that was a foul.
Foul Did you see that?
Delgado fouled him as he tried to take a shot.
Foul The Brazilian player has several fouls.