EnglishPod.com The ref calls the players for the kickoff and here we go.
Ecuador quickly passes the ball to the midfield.
But oh, it's out of bounds.
That'll be a throw in for Brazil.
Adriano has the ball and makes a long pass to Robinho.
And the ref has called him offside.
No question about it.
He was offside by a mile.
We have a goal kick for Ecuador.
Edison Mendez heads it to Valencia.
He shoots.
Deflected by the defender and we have a corner kick.
Delgado takes the corner.
We have a foul.
Oh no, Dita the goalkeeper has fouled the Ecuadorian player.
He gets a yellow card and that will be a penalty kick.
This is the perfect opportunity for Ecuador to get ahead in this match and become world champions.
He gets ready for the kick.
He shoots and he...