The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To place one's name on a roll or register, sign up.
Enroll Officially put your name on a list for something.
Sign up for A short piece of writing on one subject that argues one point of view.
Essay The field one studies in university.
Major A long piece of writing that you must do at the end of a course.
Term paper Points you receive towards your degree.
Credit An exam or big test given halfway through the course.
Midterm Time table, list of appointments and times.
Schedule The last exams at the end of a semester.
Finals Educational fees Tuition Let's try that faster!
A short piece of writing on one subject that argues one point of view.
Essay The last exams at the end of a semester.
Finals Educational fees Tuition The field one studies in university.
Major Points you receive towards your degree.
Credit Time table, list of appointments and times.
Schedule An exam or big test given halfway through the course.
Midterm To place one's name on a roll or register, sign up.
Enroll A long piece of writing that you must do at the end of a course.
Term paper Officially put your name on a list for something.
Sign up for Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sign up for I signed up for a one-year gym membership.
I really need to lose weight.
Sign up for If you want to assist our meeting, you need to sign up first.
Sign up for I hate signing up for things online because they just send you spam emails.
Major I wanted to become an arts major, but my parents wanted me to study business.
Major Paula majored in physics and applied sciences.
She is a real genius.
Major I don't know what I should major in.
What do you suggest?
Credit I need to take extra credits this year in order to make up for my laziness last semester.
Credit Tuition at some universities depends on the amount of credits you take.
Credit This class is really important since it's worth 6 credits.
Schedule Schedule I need to check my gym schedule because I want to go to my aerobics class this week.
Tracy has a really light working schedule.
She only works from 9am till noon.
Schedule I just got my class schedule today and I'm going to be busy 7 days a week.
Tuition College tuition in the United States can be very expensive.
Maybe you should study somewhere else.
Tuition I have to save up for my tuition for next semester.
Tuition I have a scholarship so I only have to pay half my tuition every year.