EnglishPod.com Excuse me, is this where I register?
I'd like to sign up for my courses for next semester.
Yes, of course.
I need your student ID, please.
Here you are.
Okay, Susan.
It says here that you are a business major and that you're in your second year.
Is this information correct?
Yes, I do want to take some additional credits this year to get a minor in psychology.
Sure, that's not a problem.
Do you have a list of courses that you want to take this semester?
Yeah, here's my list.
I'm not sure if the class schedule will allow me to take all of them, though.
Yeah, that's perfect.
What about the subjects for your minor?
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
I need to take fundamental linguistics, consumer psychology, and neuroanatomy.
Wow, you're going to be busy this semester.
Okay, here you go.
You're registered now.
You have to make your first tuition payment before classes start.