EnglishPod.com Hello ma'am can I help you find something?
Yes actually I'm looking to buy a camera.
We've got a wide selection Do you know if you'd like a point-and-shoot or something a little fancier?
Are you shopping for yourself or for someone else?
Actually I'm buying a camera for my husband Ah, well then I'd recommend a nice entry-level digital SLR.
Yeah?
Can I take a look at the SLRs you carry?
Sure thing, follow me.
This here is the...
The Canon EOS.
Yeah it's okay but I'm looking for something that performs better in low light has a better display panel and longer battery life.
Oh, ah, the Nikon D60 is a nice option?
Yeah but what kit lens does this camera come with?
I don't want some bulky telephoto lens.
Ah, well this one has the...
Looks to me like an 18 to 55 millimeter lens Pretty standard.
That'll do.
Not like my husband will be stalking celebrities or anything.
Haha so, um, can I interest you in any accessories?
Accessories?
Do you carry polarizing filters?
Polarizing filters?
Um, we...
we should.
I'm sorry ma'am looks like we're sold out.
No you're not.
There's some right here.
Oh well, would you look at that.
Polarizing filters.
Thanks for your help, Ralph.
No problem ma'am.