The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Any compact, non-SLR camera with non-interchangeable lenses using automatic settings and simplified controls.
Generally desired by novices and casual users.
Point and shoot Try to persuade someone to buy, do or eat something.
Interest someone in A transparent optical device used to converge or diverge transmitted light and to form images.
Lens A camera lens filter used to control the plane of polarization of light entering the lens.
Polarizing filter Simple and appropriate to an inexperienced person.
Entry level Let's try that faster.
Simple and appropriate to an inexperienced person.
Entry level A camera lens filter used to control the plane of polarization of light entering the lens.
Polarizing filter Any compact, non-SLR camera with non-interchangeable lenses using automatic settings and simplified controls.
Generally desired by novices and casual users.
Point and shoot A transparent optical device used to converge or diverge transmitted light and to form images.
Lens Try to persuade someone to buy, do or eat something.
Interest someone in Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Point and shoot A point and shoot camera is also called a compact camera because it is small and the lens can be compacted into the body of the camera.
Point and shoot Point and shoot A disposable camera is the cheapest point and shoot camera.
Point and shoot A fully automated camcorder can also be called point and shoot.
Lens Macro lenses are used for close-up photography.
Lens Convex lenses are used to converge light behind the lens, while concave lenses are used to diverge light behind the lens.
Lens Compound lenses Photographic lenses can be compound lenses, which means that they are made of a combination of convex and concave lenses and other optical devices.
Interest someone in Can I interest you in a drink?
Interest someone in While you're waiting, can I interest you in a tour of the facilities?
Interest someone in Can I interest you in buying a new car?
Polarizing filter Polarizing filters are also called polarizers.
Polarizing filter Linear polarizing filters are made for manual focus cameras, while circular polarizing filters are made for autofocus cameras.
Polarizing filter Polarized sunglasses have a coating on their lenses which acts as a polarizing filter to cut out the glare of the sun from reflective surfaces.
Entry level She's offering him an entry level job.
Entry level This new entry level camera has received glowing reviews.
Entry level This is an entry level class.