EnglishPod.com Just a normal sized TV for our living room.
I see.
Well, this set here is on sale.
It's a 46 inch HDTV screen and it has all the works.
Three HDMI connectors, USB, VGA and S-video ports.
It even has a DVI port so you can hook up your PC or laptop.
This is without a doubt the complete home theater experience.
This is exactly what I need.
Can you imagine watching movies or playing video games on this thing?
Honey, I think it's a bit too big.
I don't even think it will fit in our living room.
Not to worry.
We will deliver and install it in your home.
It comes with a wall mount so you can just hang it on the wall like a picture.
This is great.
How much will this set me back?
Lucky for you, this is the last one we have in stock so it's half off.
I'll take it.