The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A machine for projecting an image onto a screen or other surface.
Projector To be grateful for something.
Appreciate To connect an appliance to an electrical outlet.
Plugin Get something better, more modern or more useful.
Upgrade A device that converts electrical signals into sounds loud enough to be heard at a distance.
Speaker A device used to control an apparatus or machine from a distance.
Remote control A television service in which the subscriber's television is connected to a central receiver by cable.
Cable television Cost Set me back To connect Hook up The best things offered The works Let's try that faster!
To be grateful for something.
Appreciate A device that converts electrical signals into sounds loud enough to be heard at a distance.
Speaker The best things offered The works A machine for projecting an image onto a screen or other surface.
Projector Get something better, more modern or more useful.
Upgrade A television service in which the subscriber's television is connected to a central receiver by cable.
Cable television To connect Hook up A device used to control an apparatus or machine from a distance.
Remote control To connect an appliance to an electrical outlet.
Plug-in Cost Set me back Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Appreciate Appreciate With a telescope, you can really appreciate the brightness of the stars.
Appreciate I really appreciate your help during these tough times.
Appreciate You have to listen and focus to appreciate classical music.
Upgrade The government has designated funds in order to upgrade their military defenses.
Upgrade Upgrade My computer is old and slow.
I think I need to upgrade it with new components.
Upgrade If you want to have the sports channels, you need to upgrade to our premium cable package.
The Works The bridegroom was wearing a morning suit, top hat, gloves.
The Works The Works The Works He spent over $10,000 on his home theater system.
He got all the works.
The Works The Works I bought a new car with all the works.
Magnesium rims, custom paint, and leather seats.
Hook up The Works I finally got a Nintendo Wii.
Come on, help me hook it up to the TV.
Hook up I don't know how to hook up this new DVD player.
Can you help me?
Hook up I just hooked up my new HDTV.
Want to come over and watch a movie?
Set me back This unexpected expense is going to set us back a couple thousand dollars.
Set me back That fancy dinner at the restaurant last night really set us back.
Set me back I feel guilty about buying this coat.
It set me back over $300.