The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To cure an illness by medical means treat a jarring of the brain concussion to be disposed or inclined towards something tend to move or act swiftly rush begin with take up Let's try that faster.
To be disposed or inclined towards something tend to begin with take up a jarring of the brain concussion To cure an illness by medical means treat move or act swiftly rush Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
treat I think you should go to the doctor and get treated for that rash.
treat John is currently being treated for his wounds at the local hospital.
treat Many patients in this clinic are being treated for swine flu.
concussion I suffered a mild concussion when I fell off my skateboard.
concussion A concussion is a brain injury that is caused by a sudden blow to the head or to the body.
concussion I think you might have a concussion.
We should go to the hospital.
tend to My teacher always tends to undermark my tests.
tend to All my friends tend to ignore me since I broke up with Andy.
tend to Don't use this CD player.
It tends to damage the discs.
rush I'll do the dishes when I come back.
Now I have to rush to school.
rush I would like to stay with you, honey, but I have to rush to work.
rush My grandma had a heart attack this morning and was rushed to the hospital.
take up After my boyfriend criticised my cooking, I decided to take up a cooking class.
take up I decided to take up Spanish since I might move to Ecuador in the future.
take up I would like to take up guitar lessons, but my parents want me to start playing the piano instead.
I would like to take up music.