EnglishPod.com Steven, where have you been?
I've been trying to get a hold of you for hours.
I, uh, there was an emergency at work, so...
I was waiting for you in the restaurant for three hours.
And you didn't even have the decency to call me.
Do you have any idea how embarrassed I was?
Honey, I promise this won't happen again.
It's just that I- Yeah, right.
I've heard it all before.
I'm not going to take any more of your empty promises.
This is the fifth time you stood me up in two weeks.
You need to get your priorities straight.
I'm tired of you putting your job first all the time.
Come on, Veronica.
That's not fair.
I do care about you a lot, you know that.
I try to- You know what?
Maybe we should just take a break.
I need some time to think about where this relationship is heading.
But, Veronica, would you listen to me?