The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Sit down Seat Tooth pain Toothache Some parts are bigger than others due to a certain disease.
Swollen One of the four large teeth at the back of the mouth which grows only in one's adulthood.
Wisdom tooth Take a glance Have a look A hole in a tooth Cavity The part of the tooth which can be seen.
Crown Something that fills a hole in a tooth.
Filling A medical examination that takes a picture of your bones.
X-rays To use a thin thread or string to clean between your teeth.
Floss A liquid that is used to clean your mouth and teeth and make your breath smell better.
Mouthwash A disease in which the gums become red, swollen and sore.
Gingivitis A thin coating that forms on the teeth and contains bacteria.
Plaque Used to describe when someone has very bad breath.
Dog breath Let's try that faster.
Sit down Seat Take a glance Have a look The part of the tooth which can be seen.
Crown A thin coating that forms on the teeth and contains bacteria.
Plaque Something that fills a hole in a tooth.
Filling A liquid that is used to clean your mouth and teeth and make your breath smell better.
Mouthwash A disease in which the gums become red, swollen and sore.
Gingivitis One of the four large teeth at the back of the mouth which grows only in one's adulthood.
Wisdom tooth Used to describe when someone has very bad breath.
Dog breath Some parts are bigger than others due to a certain disease.
Swollen To use a thin thread or string to clean between your teeth.
Floss A hole in a tooth.
Cavity Tooth pain Toothache X-rays Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
My nose is swollen.
It's the size of a football.
Put some ice on your foot and the swelling will go down.
I got bitten by a spider and my hand is swelling up.
John told me that it doesn't look good for me.
I probably won't get the job.
It doesn't look good for Michael Jackson.
He's in a lot of debt.
You know, the economy doesn't look very good.
I just got my wisdom teeth out so I can't eat anything.
You're going to have to get your wisdom teeth pulled.
I think my wisdom teeth are coming in.
Cavity My tooth is really hurting.
I think I have a cavity.
Cavity If you don't brush your teeth, you'll get cavities.
Cavity You can see on this x-ray that you have four cavities.
Have a look.
So you're having car trouble.
Let's have a look at the engine.
Have a look.
Let's have a look at your computer and see what the problem is.
Let me have a look at your report.