The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Travel in a boat that is powered by wind.
Sail.
For a short amount of time.
For a little while.
A swim.
A dip.
Swim like a dog.
Doggy paddle.
A way of swimming where the person moves the arms and legs in a half circle in front of them, like a frog.
Breaststroke.
To swim on your back with arms moving up and down in a circle.
Backstroke.
Directly in the direction of something.
Straight towards.
Clothes you wear when you go swimming, American English.
Swimsuit.
Clothes you wear when you go swimming, British English.
Swimming costume.
A piece of soft cloth you use to dry yourself after swimming or bathing.
Towel.
Fly in the sun and try to make your skin more brown.
Tan.
Jump into the water with your head first.
Dive.
Let's try that faster.
Directly in the direction of something.
Straight towards.
Travel in a boat that is powered by wind.
Sail.
A piece of soft cloth you use to dry yourself after swimming or bathing.
Towel.
Clothes you wear when you go swimming, British English.
Swimming costume.
Swim like a dog.
Doggy paddle.
A swim.
A dip.
Fly in the sun and try to make your skin more brown.
Tan.
You swim on your back with arms moving up and down in a circle.
Backstroke.
For a short amount of time.
For a little while.
Jump into the water with your head first.
Dive.
Clothes you wear when you go swimming, American English.
Swimsuit.
A way of swimming where the person moves the arms and legs in a half circle in front of them, like a frog.
Breaststroke.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sail.
I've never been sailing before.
I always get sick when I go sailing.
Sail.
Did you watch the sailing race?
Let's anchor the boat here.
I drop the anchor over the side of the boat so we won't float away.
We can't anchor here because there are power lines under the water.
I'm tired.
I'm just going to sit down for a while.
It will only hurt for a little while.
Do you want to play tennis for a little while?
It was so hot that we took a dip before lunch.
Stephen and Nellie are taking a dip in the lake.
Do you want to take a dip in the pool?
Straight towards.
Swim straight towards the shore.
The boat is coming straight towards us.
Straight towards.
We're driving straight towards the cliff.