Good afternoon, ma'am.
My name is Mike and I'm selling subscriptions to all sorts of periodicals.
No, thank you.
I'm not interested.
Please, ma'am, if you could spare five minutes of your time, I'm sure we could find something that could interest you.
I wish I could, but I have to walk the dog and finish cooking, so if you'd excuse me.
We have a great variety of magazines all about cooking.
This one, for example, is a bimonthly publication with recipes from all over the world.
Wow, well, that would be kind of useful.
Do you have any other cooking magazines?
Sure do.
This one is a quarterly publication, but each issue has over 200 color pages of recipes and also many home decorating ideas.
Wow, this is nice.
Okay, sign me up for both publications.
You mentioned you have a dog.
Most pet owners sign up for this weekly newsletter that has information on dog care, pet shops, and even pet sitters.
That's exactly what I needed.
What else do you have?
Well, I also have...
Thank you.