The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A purchase by prepayment for goods or services Subscription Do you have, can you offer If you could spare At three month intervals Quarterly A final publication such as a magazine Issue A person that takes care of your pet while you are Pet sitter A purchase by prepayment for goods or services Subscription A person that takes care of your pet while you are Pet sitter Do you have, can you offer If you could spare At three month intervals Quarterly Issue Issue Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Subscription I have a subscription to several online newsletters.
Subscription I cancelled my newspaper subscription for the month that I will be away.
Subscription My subscription to this TV channel has increased in price.
If you could spare If you could spare a minute of your time I would like to give you some advice.
If you could spare I would greatly appreciate the help if you could spare the time.
If you could spare Hey roommate, if you could spare me some of your eggs and butter I'll let you have a piece of the cake.
Quarterly The research journal is a quarterly publication.
Quarterly This magazine switched from being issued monthly to being issued quarterly in order to cut costs.
Quarterly We make a quarterly payment on our loan.
Issue Learn how to manage your time and how to cook a gourmet meal in 20 minutes in this month's issue of Easy Life.
Issue He picked up the most recent issue of his girlfriend's favorite magazine and added it to the gift basket.
Issue I much prefer the older issues of this magazine because the contents of the newer issues are no different than all the other magazines on the shelf.
Pet sitter We need a pet sitter for our two dogs while we're away.
Pet sitter Being a pet sitter for my neighbors is not hard at all.
I just have to make sure that their birds have enough food and water in their dispensers.
Pet sitter Can you call the pet sitter and let her know that we will need her to look after the cats for a few more days?