The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To express emotion or feeling, like God, Jesus.
Oh man.
Become quiet or calm.
Relax.
Calm down.
A small computer which is easily carried.
Laptop.
To express one's own opinion or meaning.
I mean.
An electronic display that shows images.
Monitor.
A program designed to harm a computer.
Virus.
No.
Informal.
Nope.
A set of instructions to perform.
Program.
Stop working or functioning properly.
Crash.
A program designed to identify and remove computer viruses.
Antivirus.
To work or be in operation.
Run.
Software that secretly gathers information.
Spyware.
Let's try that faster.
To express one's own opinion or meaning.
I mean.
Software that secretly gathers information.
Spyware.
A set of instructions to perform.
Program.
Become quiet or calm.
Relax.
Calm down.
Stop working or functioning properly.
Crash.
To express emotion or feeling, like God, Jesus.
Oh man.
No.
Informal.
Nope.
A small computer which is easily carried.
Laptop.
A program designed to identify and remove computer viruses.
Antivirus.
To work or be in operation.
Run.
An electronic display that shows images.
Monitor.
A program designed to harm a computer.
Virus.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Calm down.
I need to calm down.
I am too nervous.
Calm down.
The doctor gave me these pills to help me calm down.
You need to calm down your dog before he bites someone.
Oh man.
I lost my wallet.
Calm down.
Oh man.
You are in big trouble.
That car is amazing.
Virus.
My computer has a virus that erased all my hard disks.
You have to be careful when you open a computer file because it might be infected with a virus.
Virus.
The disk you gave me had a virus on it.
Crash.
My computer is too old and crashes all the time.
I don't know what happened to my phone.
I was talking and all of a sudden it crashed.
Crash.
This program causes my computer to crash.
Run.
You should run an anti-virus program occasionally to check for viruses.
There are too many programs running.
That's why your system is so slow.
Run.
This program doesn't run on Windows XP.
You must have Windows 7 if you want to use it.