The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Correct, not able to be proved wrong.
Irrefutable Very full and complete study to find information.
Extensive research Using a careful system or method Systematic Having errors or mistake Flawed Crazy, foolish, or silly Preposterous Unaware or don't know Oblivious to Way of looking for information Investigative approach Do something on your own, without help Single-handedly A final judgment that is not able to be changed, that is final.
Definitive conclusion Find out if something is true Determine Show something to be true Indicate An argument that is capable of making people believe that point of view A compelling case A collection of facts that implies or suggests something to be true, but does not prove it.
Circumstantial evidence Linked or connected with Associated with Let's try that faster Unaware or don't know Oblivious to Having errors or mistake Flawed Find out if something is true Determine Correct, not able to be proved wrong Irrefutable A collection of facts that implies or suggests something to be true, but does not prove it.
Circumstantial evidence Way of looking for information Investigative approach A final judgment that is not able to be changed, that is final.
Definitive conclusion Very full and complete study to find information Extensive research Linked or connected with Associated with Show something to be true Indicate Systematic Crazy, foolish, or silly Preposterous An argument that is capable of making people believe that point of view A compelling case Do something on your own, without help Single-handedly Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Irrefutable Look, we have irrefutable evidence that he was the killer.
Irrefutable The facts are irrefutable.
Smoking has a negative impact on your health.
Irrefutable The irrefutable truth is that there is a monster living in Lake Erie.
Systematic We need to approach this problem in a systematic way.
Systematic We did a systematic evaluation of the evidence.
Systematic He is a very systematic guy.
He is very careful with his work.
Systematic Neil is oblivious to what's going on around him.
Are you oblivious to the truth?
I was oblivious to the fact that there was a virus on my computer.
Definitive conclusion We have not come to any definitive conclusions yet.
Definitive conclusion Before you make a definitive conclusion, make sure you examine all the evidence.
Definitive conclusion The researchers failed to arrive at any definitive conclusions.
We studied the problem carefully and we found conclusive evidence of global warming.
There is no conclusive evidence that links diet coke to health problems.
There is conclusive evidence showing that smokers die younger.