The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Let's talk about this problem and solve it.
Let's talk it over.
The quality of being honest and fair.
Integrity.
Confess.
Tell the truth.
Come clean.
Make people think there is danger when there is none.
Cry wolf.
Many times.
Time and again.
Be honest with someone.
Be straight with someone.
To cause to believe what is not true.
Mislead.
Deceive.
Speak honestly.
Level with someone.
Fool or joke.
Kidding.
Tell you true information.
Tell you the facts.
Give you the lowdown.
Direct.
Honest.
With no lies.
Forthright.
Endless.
Lasting forever.
Undying.
Showing or feeling strong loyalty or love.
Devoted.
To treat with affection and tenderness.
Cherish.
Soon, in this very instant.
At the drop of a hat.
The base of a structure.
Foundation.
Let's try that faster.
Speak honestly.
Level with someone.
Showing or feeling strong loyalty or love.
Devoted.
Tell you true information.
Tell you the facts.
Give you the lowdown.
Fool or joke.
Kidding.
Direct.
Honest.
With no lies.
Forthright.
To cause to believe what is not true.
Mislead.
Deceive.
Endless.
Lasting forever.
Undying.
Soon, in this very instant.
At the drop of a hat.
Make people think there is danger when there is none.
Cry wolf.
Confess.
Tell the truth.
Come clean.
The quality of being honest and fair.
Integrity.
Many times.
Time and again.
Be honest with someone.
Be straight with someone.
Let's talk about this problem and solve it.
Let's talk it over.
The base of a structure.
Foundation.
To treat with affection and tenderness.
Cherish.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Time and again.
Max, time and again I've told you to clean your room.
It's a mess in here.
Time and again.
I've told you time and again that I want to break up.
Time and again I've said that we need to rethink our strategy.
But no one listens to me.
Foundation.
Our friendship is built on a foundation of trust.
Any relationship that is built on a foundation of distrust and jealousy is doomed.
Foundation.
Mike and Rachel's marriage is built on a foundation of trust.
Deceive.
I thought I could trust Jack, but I was sadly deceived.
The newly elected president deceived the entire country by making false promises.
Deceive.
The man tried to deceive police officers by stating a false name.
Cherish.
Let's cherish every moment we have been given.
I cherish the memories of my childhood like a precious jewel.
Cherish.
Family is something that you should cherish forever.
At the drop of a hat.
My boss expects me to come into work at the drop of a hat.
Lara is always willing to help out at the drop of a hat.
At the drop of a hat.
I can't leave at the drop of a hat.
But I need time to prepare.