EnglishPod.com It's all over now.
My assignment is complete, and now I have to go back to India.
What?
Are you kidding?
Is there anything else I should know before I never see you again?
How could you deceive me like that?
Yes.
Veronica, I know that this isn't the best time, and you probably hate me right now, but I want to be completely forthright with you.
I know deep in my heart that you are the best thing that has ever happened to me.
Veronica, will you marry me?
Come with me to India, baby.
I can't make it for everything that's happened, but I can promise you my undying love.
I will be the most devoted husband, and I will cherish you always.
Steven, I can't just leave everything at the drop of a hat.
With everything that has happened between us, I just don't know you anymore.
I just can't build a relationship on a foundation of lies.
I do love you, but I can't go with you.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
This is the last call for flight 815 from Los Angeles to Hyderabad.
I'm sorry, sir.
We can't wait any longer.
You must board the plane.
Are you waiting for someone?
I was, but I don't think she's coming.