The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Worried or nervous of what may happen.
Anxious Rapid or successive change of your mood.
Mood swing Feeling very excited or happy.
Ecstatic Feeling sad, depressed.
Blue Feeling of showing lack of emotional involvement.
Detached Sad from being apart from other people.
Lonely Assurance, freedom from doubt.
Confident Not feeling any fear.
Brave Let's try that faster.
Feeling sad, depressed.
Blue Feeling very excited or happy.
Ecstatic Not feeling any fear.
Brave Rapid or successive change of your mood.
Mood swing Sad from being apart from other people.
Lonely Worried or nervous of what may happen.
Anxious Assurance, freedom from doubt.
Confident Feeling of showing lack of emotional involvement.
Detached Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Anxious I am feeling a bit anxious about my job interview tomorrow.
Anxious That movie left me feeling anxious and stressed.
Anxious This pill will help you feel less anxious about flying.
Mood swing Pregnant women often have mood swings.
Mood swing I don't know why I am having mood swings lately.
Mood swing If you are having mood swings too often, then you should consult with your doctor.
Ecstatic I am ecstatic with my new job.
Ecstatic I can't wait to go on vacation.
I am feeling so ecstatic.
Ecstatic Harry looks ecstatic with his new toy.
Lonely I have spent many lonely nights crying.
Lonely If you feel lonely, you should go out and have fun.
Lonely He is feeling very lonely since his girlfriend broke up with him.
Confident Make sure you seem confident at the job interview today.
Confident I feel confident that we will win the game.
Confident I am trying to be more confident and brave.
Thank you for watching.