The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Being attacked.
Under attack.
Not known.
Having no identity.
Unidentified.
To experience or suffer.
Sustain.
The engine system used by a spacecraft to travel faster than the speed of light.
Warp drive.
To start fighting.
Engage.
The basic reason.
Nature.
An organized group of people sent to look for someone or something that is missing or lost.
Search party.
Low in pitch.
Resonant.
Deep voice.
Artificial hair.
Wig.
A fictitious futuristic weapon that can stun or kill an enemy.
Phaser.
The central point of the ship where the captain commands and orders are taken.
Bridge.
A virtual reality simulation room where places and scenarios can be loaded.
Holodeck.
The action of transporting a person immediately from one place to another in less than a second.
Beam up.
A member of the crew with the lowest rank.
Ensign.
Let's try that faster.
The basic reason.
Nature.
A virtual reality simulation room where places and scenarios can be loaded.
Holodeck.
Low in pitch.
Resonant.
Deep voice.
An organized group of people sent to look for someone or something that is missing or lost.
Search party.
Artificial hair.
Wig.
To start fighting.
Engage.
To experience or suffer.
Sustain.
A fictitious futuristic weapon that can stun or kill an enemy.
Phaser.
The central point of the ship where the captain commands and orders are taken.
Bridge.
Being attacked.
Under attack.
The action of transporting a person immediately from one place to another in less than a second.
Beam up.
A member of the crew with the lowest rank.
Ensign.
Not known.
Having no identity.
Unidentified.
The engine system used by a spacecraft to travel faster than the speed of light.
Warp drive.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sustain.
John had a car accident and sustained a fatal injury.
The boxer sustained a severe neck injury in the championship fight.
Sustain.
Luckily, the warship didn't sustain any serious damage.
Nature.
What is the nature of your visit to the United States?
What is the nature of the threat against our country?
Nature.
The nature of my visit is personal.
Search party.
A 30-man search party was sent out to find survivors of the plane crash.
Our neighborhood organized a search party to find the missing children.
Search party.
Two search parties went out into the woods in search of an elephant that escaped from the local zoo.
Deep voice.
Luciano Pavarotti had a beautiful deep voice.
I think that it is very attractive when a man has a deep voice.
Deep voice.
My dad has such a deep voice that it even scares the cat.
Wig.
I got a very bad haircut once and decided to wear a wig.
We had a Halloween party last year and I wore a red wig.
No one recognized me.
Wig.
The bank robbers were wearing masks and wigs to avoid being recognized.
Thanks for watching!