The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An arrangement to secure accommodations at a restaurant or hotel.
Reservation To decide that something will not happen.
Cancel The quality or state of being inconvenient.
Inconvenience Important Urgent Planned at a specific time Scheduled Let's try that faster.
Planned at a specific time Scheduled Important Urgent To decide that something will not happen.
Cancel The quality or state of being inconvenient.
Inconvenience An arrangement to secure accommodations at a restaurant or hotel.
Reservation Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Urgent Sir, I have an urgent call for you.
I think it's your wife.
Urgent Dad, this is urgent.
I need the car now.
Urgent I didn't think the matter was urgent enough to warrant my attention.
Cancel I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to cancel our meeting.
Cancel The football match was cancelled due to poor weather.
Cancel The movie store cancelled my contract because of late fees.
Inconvenience Sorry about the inconvenience.
Please wait a little longer.
Inconvenience This is such a big inconvenience.
How rude.
Inconvenience Reservation I don't want to be an inconvenience, but could you please pass me the salt.
Reservation Hello sir, we are only letting people in who have a reservation at this moment.
Reservation I got a reservation for dinner tonight.
Want to come?
Reservation It will take six months to get a reservation for the opera.
Scheduled The flight has yet to depart on its scheduled time.
Scheduled I don't think I will be able to finish the work on schedule.
Scheduled I wish trains would run on schedule.