EnglishPod.com Good afternoon, sir.
May I please see your passport and reservation?
Here you go.
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
This flight has been canceled due to some mechanical problems.
Canceled?
What am I supposed to do now?
We apologize for any inconveniences that may be caused by this.
If your flight is urgent, I could put you on a waiting list for another flight this evening, but it's on a first-come, first-serve basis, so there's no guarantee you'll be able to take that flight.
What are my other options?
Well, if you can wait until tomorrow, we will put you up in a hotel for today, and you can take the scheduled flight for tomorrow morning.
That's fine.
I'll do that then.
Thank you for your understanding, sir.
I'll book your flight now.