The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Always becoming different.
Ever-changing.
A written promise that a seller will repair a product if a problem arises.
Warranty.
No longer useful.
Obsolete.
A portable computer.
Laptop.
The direction of an event.
Where something is going.
To change into a more advanced state.
Evolve.
To be completely unaware of something.
I have no idea.
A device that allows computers to communicate without wires.
Wireless modem.
To suddenly stop functioning.
Freeze.
A system for communicating between computers.
Network.
A computer application.
Program.
Unit to measure a computer storage capacity.
Gigabyte.
Part of computer that temporarily stores information.
Random access memory.
Part of computer that stores data.
Hard disk.
Measurement of computer processor speed.
gigahertz.
Device in a computer that manages operations.
Processor.
To suddenly stop functioning.
Crash.
To make a written promise.
Guarantee.
Let's try that faster.
A computer application.
Program.
Measurement of computer processor speed.
gigahertz.
The direction of an event.
Where something is going.
Unit to measure a computer storage capacity.
Gigabyte.
No longer useful.
Obsolete.
Device in a computer that manages operations.
Processor.
Always becoming different.
Ever-changing.
A device that allows computers to communicate without wires.
Wireless modem.
A written promise that a seller will repair a product if a problem arises.
Warranty.
Part of computer that stores data.
Hard disk.
To suddenly stop functioning.
Crash.
To make a written promise.
Guarantee.
Part of computer that temporarily stores information.
Random access memory.
To suddenly stop functioning.
Freeze.
A portable computer.
Laptop.
To change into a more advanced state.
Evolve.
A system for communicating between computers.
Network.
To be completely unaware of something.
I have no idea.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Ever-changing.
There is always something new in this ever-changing world.
Times are ever-changing and we must prepare ourselves better every day.
Ever-changing.
The flu is an ever-changing virus that continues to claim many lives.
Obsolete.
This fleet of battleships from World War II is completely obsolete.
Broom is an obsolete word that means mist or fog.
Obsolete.
A VHS is a device that is practically obsolete nowadays.
Who buys tapes anymore?
Where something is going.
We fight every day.
I don't know where this relationship is going.
Where something is going.
Where is this movie going?
I don't understand what's happening.
Where something is going.
You want to do what?
Where are you going with this conversation?
I have no idea.
I can't find my keys.
I have no idea where I put them.
I have no idea.
I have no idea where Tom went.
Maybe he's in the bathroom?
I have no idea.
You have no idea how embarrassed I was.
I mean, I accidentally burped while presenting my project to the board of directors.
Freeze.
If your computer freezes, you'll have to shut it down.
Something is wrong with my mobile phone.
It keeps freezing.
Freeze.
The files are not ready yet because my computer froze last night.