EnglishPod.com So, can you fix it?
I'm sorry, sir.
This computer is not broken or damaged.
It's simply just too old.
That's why your programs and applications are running slow.
There really isn't much I can do.
What do you mean?
I bought this computer just three years ago.
Yes, but technology is ever-changing and technology is becoming obsolete faster and faster.
Okay, I know where this is going.
How much will it cost me to get a new computer?
Well, this desktop over here is our latest model.
It has a 4 gigahertz processor with 16 gigabytes in RAM and a hard disk with 1 terabyte.
Of course, it includes a mouse, keyboard, and desk speakers.
I have no idea what you are talking about.
I just want to know if it's good and if I'll be able to play Solitaire without the computer crashing or freezing all the time.
This PC is top of the line and I guarantee it will never freeze.
If it does, we'll give you your money back.