EnglishPod.com and mama in her kerchief and I in my cap had just settled down for a long winter's nap.
When out on the lawn there arose such a clatter I sprang from the bed to see what was the matter.
Away to the window I flew like a flash tore open the shutters and threw open the sash.
The moon on the breast of the new fallen snow gave the luster of midday to objects below when what to my wondering eyes should appear but a miniature sleigh and eight tiny reindeer.
With a little old driver so lively and quick I knew in a moment it must be Saint Nick.
More rapid than eagles his coursers they came and he whistled and shouted and called them by name.
Now dasher, now dancer, now prancer and vixen on comet, on cupid, on donder and blitzen to the top of the porch, to the top of the wall now dash away, dash away, dash away all.
As dry leaves that before the wild hurricanes fly when they meet with an obstacle mount to the sky.
So up to the housetop the coursers they flew with the sleighs full of toys and Saint Nicholas too.
And then in a twinkling I heard on the roof the prancing and pawing of each little hoof.
As I drew in my head and was turning around down the chimney Saint Nicholas came with a bound.
He was dressed on fur from his head to his toe and his clothes were all tarnished with ashes and soot.
A bundle of toys he had flung on his back and he looked like a peddler just opening his pack.
His eyes how they twinkled, his dimples how merry.
His cheeks were like roses, his nose like a cherry.
His droll little mouth was drawn up in a bow and the beard of his chin was as white as the snow.
The stump of a pipe he held tight in his teeth and the smoke had encircled his head like a wreath.
He had a broad face and a little round belly that shook when he laughed like a bowl full of jelly.
He was chubby and plump a right old jolly elf and I laughed when I saw him in spite of myself.
A wink of his eye and a twist of his head soon gave me to know I had nothing to dread.
He spoke not a word but went straight to work and filled all the stockings then turned with a jerk.
And laying his finger aside of his nose and giving a nod up the chimney he rose.
He sprang to his sleigh, to his team gave a whistle and away they all flew like the down of a thistle.
But I heard him exclaim air as he drove out of sight Happy Christmas to all and to all a good night.