The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Beef that has been put through a grinder.
Ground beef.
A type of meat from a large bird, similar to chicken.
Turkey.
Having a low-fat content.
Lean.
Used to express the listener is aware of something that is assumed to be known.
If you know what I mean.
A type of small sausage.
Hot dog.
A cut of pork in a individual size.
Pork chop.
A type of knife a butcher uses.
Cleaver.
With the bones removed.
Boneless.
The table that a butcher works on.
Chopping block.
The meaty breast portion of a chicken.
Chicken breast.
The waxy paper a butcher uses to wrap meat in.
Butcher paper.
The upper leg portion of meat on a chicken.
Chicken thigh.
A ham which has been seasoned with smoke.
Smoked ham.
Cold cooked meat used for sandwiches.
Cold cuts.
Spicy dry sausage.
Salami.
A thick piece of beef with a T-shaped bone in it.
T-bone.
A tender cut of beef from the outer side of the rib.
Rib eye.
A piece of beef from the lower back of the cow.
Sirloin.
A slice of beef.
Steak.
The place where animals are killed for their meat.
Slaughterhouse.
Wide sausage that is sliced.
Bologna.
Let's try that faster.
The meaty breast portion of a chicken.
Chicken breast.
Spicy dry sausage.
Salami.
Used to express the listener is aware of something that is assumed to be known.
If you know what I mean.
A type of small sausage.
Hot dog.
A ham which has been seasoned with smoke.
Smoked ham.
Wide sausage that is sliced.
Bologna.
Having a low fat content.
Lean.
Cold cooked meat used for sandwiches.
Cold cuts.
A slice of beef.
Steak.
The upper leg portion of meat on a chicken.
Chicken thigh.
A cut of pork in an individual size.
Pork chop.
A thick piece of beef with a T-shaped bone in it.
T-bone.
The place where animals are killed for their meat.
Slaughterhouse.
Beef that has been put through a grinder.
Ground beef.
A type of knife a butcher uses.
Cleaver.
A type of meat from a large bird similar to chicken.
Turkey.
With the bones removed.
Boneless.
A tender cut of beef from the outer side of the rib.
Rib eye.
A piece of beef from the lower back of the cow.
Sirloin.
The waxy paper a butcher uses to wrap meat in.
Butcher paper.
The table that a butcher works on.
Chopping block.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Ground beef.
You should be sure that ground beef is cooked well.
Otherwise, you can get sick.
Ground beef.
Today's special is ground beef at only 99 cents a pound while supplies last.
These Italian meatballs are made from ground beef, salt, pepper, and a pinch of beef.
A type of garlic powder.
Lean.
Tommy is on a diet, so he only eats extra lean meat.
Look at that girl over there.
She is so lean.
I don't think there is an ounce of fat on her body.
Lean.
We want to make the company leaner and more responsive to the demands of the market.
If you know what I mean.
This beef is so fresh, I think I can still hear it mooing, if you know what I mean.
I know what you mean.
The internet is so slow, I'm not sure I'm even connected.
If you know what I mean.
Boy, John's wife is really mad at him.
I guess he's really in the doghouse.
If you know what I mean.
Cold cuts.
Are we all prepared for the picnic?
Let's see here.
We have bread, cold cuts, mustard, silverware, plates.
Cold cuts.
Honey, don't forget to buy the cold cuts on your way home.
Buy some sliced roast turkey and whatever else you want.
Cold cuts.
Steak.
I would prefer a bowl of steaming noodles rather than some stale bread and cold cuts.
Before I got this great job, I was so poor, but now it's steak for dinner every night.
Steak.
I can't finish this whole steak.
It's bigger than my head.
Steak.
You can choose how long your steak is cooked.
Rare steak often still has blood in it, while well done is almost entirely burnt.