EnglishPod.com Hi, what can I get for you?
I'd like half a pound of ground beef, please.
Good choice.
Our ground beef is extra lean, if you know what I mean.
Could I also have half a dozen pork chops and two pounds of boneless chicken breast?
No, no, no.
Chicken breasts at the moment.
But we have some nice chicken thighs.
No, that won't do.
I'll take this smoked ham you have here.
Okay, is there anything else?
Is this salami and bologna you have here?
Yes.
It's very fine meat.
Made it myself.
Sounds good.
Okay, that's it.
Wait, we have t-bone, ribeye, and sirloin sticks.
They are very fresh.
Just came from the slaughterhouse.
No, that's okay, really.
I think that's all for today.
Okay, that'll be $34.50.
Thanks for watching.