The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Eating plan to help you lose weight.
Diets Change Transform Remove, eliminate Cut out Usual ways of behaving.
Eating habits Continue doing something.
Stick to Remain in a state in which you expect something to happen and see if it does.
Wait and see Filled with food, no longer hungry.
Stuffed Let's try that faster.
Change Transform Remove, eliminate Cut out Change Transform Remain in a state in which you expect something to happen and see if it does.
Wait and see Usual ways of behaving.
Eating habits Change Transform Usual ways of behaving.
Eating habits Remain in a state in which you expect something to happen and see if it does.
Wait and see Eating plan to help you lose weight.
Diets Change Transform Remove, eliminate Cut out Filled with food, no longer hungry.
Stuffed Usual ways of behaving.
Eating habits Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Diets I gained 10 pounds during the vacation.
I need to go on a diet.
Transform Do you still remember Lori from high school?
She has totally transformed into a new person.
Cut out You have to cut out the salt from your diet.
No more chips, no more french fries, no more popcorn.
Stick to You'd better stick to your promise.
Wait and see The test result will come out in two weeks.
We'll have to wait and see.
Stuffed I can't eat anything else.
I'm stuffed.
Wait and see The test result will come out in two weeks.
We'll have to wait and see.
Stuffed I can't eat anything else.
I'm stuffed.