So, where is this mystery restaurant that we're going to?
It's an Indian restaurant.
I know you have never had Indian food, so I thought you might want to try it.
That sounds great!
I am craving some type of beef dish.
Well, Indian cuisine actually doesn't serve beef.
You see, cows are a sacred animal, a very important element in the Hindu religion, so beef is not eaten.
I see.
So, what are we having, chicken?
There are many amazing dishes to choose from.
We can have some chicken tikka masala, which is an amazing curry.
It's a bit spicy, but I think you can handle it.
Sounds good!
I've always heard that Indian spices give a rich flavor to food.
Yeah.
Also, we can have some naan bread, which is baked in a tandoori oven.
Since you don't use any utensils to eat, you can use this bread to scoop up the curry or rice.
What about veggies?
Oh, they have a good variety of vegetable-based dishes like palak paneer, vegetable samosas, or dal.
It all sounds so exquisite.
I can't wait.