The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something that is unknown or lacking in information.
Mystery A person who adheres to the religion of Hinduism.
Hindu A style or quality of cooking.
Cuisine A stuffed pastry, triangular in shape.
Samosa A meal containing lentils.
Possessing qualities of unusual delicacy and fine craftsmanship.
Exquisite Chicken marinated in yogurt and spices.
Served in tomato sauce.
Chicken tikka masala.
Holy Sacred Want something very much.
Craving Let's try that faster.
Holy Sacred A meal containing lentils.
Dal A person who adheres to the religion of Hinduism.
Hindu A stuffed pastry, triangular in shape.
Samosa A style or quality of cooking.
Cuisine Chicken marinated in yogurt and spices.
Served in tomato sauce.
Chicken tikka masala.
Possessing qualities of unusual delicacy and fine craftsmanship.
Exquisite Want something very much.
Craving Something that is unknown or lacking in information.
Mystery Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Cuisine I'm a big fan of Italian cuisine.
Always fills me up.
Cuisine My friend is coming over tonight to cook his regional cuisine for me.
Cuisine Indian cuisine is too spicy for my liking.
I prefer Chinese.
Craving I'm craving for some chocolate right now.
Craving I've got such a craving for blueberry pancakes.
Craving My friend is always craving for cigarettes.
He should quit.
Exquisite The new art at the museum was truly exquisite.
Exquisite Her voice is exquisite when she sings.
Exquisite His performance was an exquisite example of how to cook.
Sacred Cows are sacred in India.
That's why they do not eat beef.
Sacred He always takes time off to visit the sacred temple.
Sacred Many religions around the world have sacred books or items such as the Bible.
Mystery It was a mystery as to who stole the cookie from the cookie jar.
Mystery No one knows how to solve this mystery.
Mystery Mystery She didn't know where her boyfriend was taking her.
It was a big mystery.