The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Quickly, as soon as possible.
Right away.
In a difficult situation.
In the weeds.
A chef that assists and helps the head chef.
Sous-chef!
Remove the outer skin of a fruit or vegetable.
Peel!
Cut into small pieces.
Chop!
Do not have so much, having not enough.
Running low on.
Move or mix something, usually with a spoon.
Stir!
Cut meat into pieces taking out bones and organs.
Butcher!
Put butter on something.
Butter!
Do cut something into small pieces.
Dice!
A flat piece of kitchen equipment for cooking with fire.
Stove!
A deep, round container that is used for cooking.
Pot!
A usually shallow and open metal container that has a handle and that is used for cooking or baking.
Pan!
To cook food at a very high and dry heat.
Bake!
Let's try that faster!
Quickly, as soon as possible.
Right away!
A deep, round container that is used for cooking.
Pot!
A chef that assists and helps the head chef.
Sous-chef!
A flat piece of kitchen equipment for cooking with fire.
Stove!
Move or mix something, usually with a spoon.
Stir!
To cut something into small pieces.
Dice!
Put butter on something.
Butter!
In a difficult situation.
In the weeds.
A usually shallow and open metal container that has a handle and that is used for cooking or baking.
Pan!
Cut into small pieces.
Chop!
Cut meat into pieces taking out bones and organs.
Butcher!
Do not have so much, having not enough.
Running low on.
Remove the outer skin of a fruit or vegetable.
Peel!
To cook food at a very high and dry heat.
Bake!
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Peel!
You should peel tomatoes before eating them to avoid getting sick.
I hate peeling potatoes.
It takes me a very long time.
Can you peel this orange for me, please?
Chop!
When you chop onions, it makes you cry.
You must be careful when chopping vegetables and not cut yourself.
Chop!
When you chop vegetables, make sure you have a sharp knife.
Running low on.
We need to find a gas station.
We are running low on gas.
Running low on.
We are running low on beer.
Can you go to the store and get some more?
Running low on.
My flashlight is running low on battery.
Do you have another flashlight?
Stir!
Stir this can of paint so we can start painting the room.
You need to stir your coffee if you add sugar.
Stir!
Can you please stir the rice?
It will burn if you don't.
Butcher!
It's difficult to butcher meat.
I don't know how you do it.
Butcher!
I spent all day butchering the cow.
Now it's ready to cook.
Butcher!
You have to butcher the chicken before cooking it.
You have to make sure it's cooked.
Thanks for watching!