EnglishPod.com Right away, sir.
Your order will be ready shortly.
Jean-Pierre, we have another special for Table 7.
I'm working as fast as I can.
We are wheeling the weeds.
Where is my sous-chef?
Look!
I need you to peel more potatoes.
Marie, chop some onions and carrots for the stew.
Thank you.
Jean-Pierre, another special.
We're really patched tonight.
We're running low on wine.
Is there any left in the cellar?
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
Wow, we're really doing well tonight.
Hi.
Stop talking and get over here.
I need some sous-tide and the fish needs to be butchered and buttered.
Okay, I'm on it.
Jean-Pierre, Table 7 has requested to see the chef.
I think there are food critics from Cuisine Magazine.