This is Madeline Wright for BCC News reporting live from Washington D.C.
where very shortly the new President will deliver his inaugural address.
Just moments ago the President was sworn into office following the United States Constitution.
The President sought an oath to faithfully execute the office of the presidency.
And what exactly is going on now, Madeline?
Well Tom, true to American tradition, the band has just played Hail to the Chief and the President has been honored with a 21-gun salute.
Now we're waiting for the President to take the stage and deliver his speech.
Tom is like the who's who of the political world here on Capitol Hill, with dignitaries representing several different countries.
What's the mood on the ground like, Madeline?
In a word, the mood here is electric.
The excitement in the air is palpable.
I've never seen a larger crowd here on Capitol Hill.
The audience is shouting, crying and embracing each other.
On this, a most historic day, you can feel the hope and the excitement in the air.
The 20th of January will go down in history as the...
Oh Tom, it looks like the President is about to begin.
My fellow Americans, I stand before you today...