The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
November 2 observed in some Christian churches as the day of the dead.
All souls' day Among Among Confer on or on Honour The people who have passed away The departed Let's try that faster.
Among Among November 2 observed in some Christian churches as the day of the dead.
All souls' day The people who have passed away The departed Confer on or on Honour Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
All souls' day We surrender our souls to his holy presence.
All souls' day Some would say that he is a damned soul.
All souls' day Many live their lives in fear of what could be of their souls in an afterlife.
Among I believe that the spirit of my grandfather walks among us.
Among There is a traitor among our lines.
Among He is no longer among the living.
Honour It is respectful to honour those who died for a better life for us.
Honour They are honouring their traditions by dancing for three days non-stop.
Honour She couldn't have been honouring her name by doing such things.
The departed The day to honour the departed is about to come.
The departed The departed Many members of my family have departed from my side.
The departed We should remember and respect the departed.