The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A particular shape formed by a group of stars.
Constellation Produce light every several seconds.
Blink Unidentified flying object.
UFO Human beings that live on Earth.
Earthlings From a long distance.
From afar.
Any of numerous large-scale collections of stars, gas, and dust that make up the visible universe.
Galaxy The ability to do something.
Capacity A monumental human creation that is amazing.
Wonder Wonderful pieces of work.
Masterpiece A logical result or effect of an action.
Consequence The desire to achieve more.
Ambition Something that brings failure.
Downfall Completely understand, comprehend.
Figure out Decide the fate of someone or something.
Play God Angry, aggressive, wanting to fight.
Belligerent Very strong and terrible physical or mental pain.
Torment.
Anguish A vehicle that travels in space.
Spacecraft An event when people do something to play a joke on or fool others.
Hoax The study of the stars and space.
Astronomy Unable to be explained by science.
Supernatural A name for a UFO.
Flying saucer Let's try that faster.
The ability to do something.
Capacity A logical result or effect of an action.
Consequence A monumental human creation that is amazing.
Wonder Something that brings failure.
Downfall An event when people do something to play a joke on or fool others.
Hoax A vehicle that travels in space.
Spacecraft From a long distance.
From afar Unable to be explained by science.
Supernatural Very strong and terrible physical or mental pain.
Torment Anguish Unidentified flying object UFO The study of the stars and space.
Astronomy Completely understand, comprehend.
Figure out A particular shape formed by a group of stars.
Constellation Produce light every several seconds.
Blink Decide the fate of someone or something.
Play God Any of numerous large-scale collections of stars, gas, and dust that make up the visible universe.
Galaxy The desire to achieve more.
Ambition A name for a UFO.
Flying saucer Angry, aggressive, wanting to fight.
Belligerent Human beings that live on Earth.
Earthlings Wonderful pieces of work.
Masterpiece Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Their fans came from afar to watch their national team play in the World Cup.
This is a picture of the Earth as it is seen from afar.
I have loved her from afar for more than a year now.
I need to tell her how I feel.
Consequence There are very serious consequences for committing a crime in this country.
Consequence You knew the possible consequences for your actions.
Now you must pay the price.
Consequence His decision had serious consequences for his business.
Downfall His addiction to alcohol will be his downfall.
Downfall The downfall of the Roman Empire was an important event in history.
Downfall Our company made some bad investments and ultimately caused our downfall.
Figure out Have you figured out the solution to that math problem yet?
Figure out I think I figured out what is wrong with my car.
Figure out Scientists have figured out a way to make cars run on water.
Belligerent Don't take that belligerent tone with me.
I don't want to argue with you.
Belligerent Thomas is always so belligerent.
It is impossible to talk to him.
Belligerent Stacey was fired for her belligerent attitude.