EnglishPod.com Oh, honey, this is so romantic.
I've never seen, like, so many stars before.
It's beautiful.
See that constellation there?
That's Orion.
And the very bright star?
Well, it's not a star because it doesn't blink.
That's actually Venus.
What's that, um, big, flashy one?
I don't know.
I think it's a UFO.
Greetings, earthlings.
I come from afar, from a distant galaxy known only to a few.
Why are you here?
Where did you come from?
We have been observing you for the last three thousand years.
We have seen the amazing capacity that humans have to create such wonders as the Taj Mahal, or masterpieces such as the Hafner Symphony.
Unfortunately, your intelligence and creativity does not come without consequence.
Your ambition and desire for more will be your downfall, and we are here to save your planet from you.
You think you have us figured out?
What gives you the right to come and judge us?
Who are you to play God with our fate?
Silence, human.
It is that belligerent attitude that has caused years of pain and anguish among yourselves.
Now you will pay the price.