The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Go over what has been learned.
Review Add Plus The student a teacher likes best.
Teacher's pet Take away, subtract Minus To multiply Times A person who always tries to make the teacher or boss like him or her.
Suck up Separate to some parts Divided by A person who tries to show he is so smart.
Smarty pants The number obtained when a number is multiplied by itself.
Square root I think something is likely to happen.
I'll bet The person claims or pretends to know everything.
Know it all A math problem where each side is equal.
Equation A mathematical process such as adding, multiplying, subtracting, etc.
Operation The process of adding a number to itself a certain number of times.
Multiplication The process of adding two numbers together.
Addition The process of taking one number away from another.
Subtraction The process of dividing something into parts.
Division Let's try that faster.
The number obtained when a number is multiplied by itself.
Square root The process of dividing something into parts.
Division A person who tries to show he is so smart.
Smarty pants A math problem where each side is equal.
Equation To multiply Times Take away, subtract Minus The student a teacher likes best.
Teacher's pet Go over what has been learned.
Review Add Plus I think something is likely to happen.
I'll bet The process of adding a number to itself a certain number of times.
Multiplication The person claims or pretends to know everything.
Know it all A person who always tries to make the teacher or boss like him or her.
Suck up Separate to some parts Divided by The process of taking one number away from another.
Subtraction A mathematical process such as adding, multiplying, subtracting, etc.
Operation The process of adding two numbers together.
Addition Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Plus Everyone knows that two plus two equals four.
Plus We need five tickets plus an extra one for John.
Plus I have two thousand dollars in my bank account plus an extra five hundred under my bed.
Minus The ticket costs one hundred dollars minus a ten percent discount.
Minus I don't understand this.
Do you know what one minus one equals?
Minus There were five cans of tuna here minus two that I ate this morning.
Where are the rest?
Divided by Divided by To solve this problem you'll need to divide the number of days in a year by the number of days worked.
Divided by I weigh one hundred and forty pounds so if I divide that by two point two I will know my weight in kilograms.
Divided by I don't think we have enough food.
We only have two pizzas and we need to divide them by twenty people.
Mommy, everyone at school says I'm a teacher's pet.
There was a kid that used to bring my teacher an apple every day.
He was such a teacher's pet.
I always hated the kid that was the teacher's pet.
He would always get more attention.
Suck up Suck up We have a colleague at work who's the biggest suck up.
He's always being nice to our boss.
Suck up I hate it when someone tries to suck up to you just because you work with Britney Spears.
Suck up There is a job opening next month for a managerial position.
I think I'm going to have to act like a suck up to get that job.