EnglishPod.com Oh look, there's Caroline and her boyfriend.
She's always going on about him at the office.
Great, they saw us.
They're coming this way.
Oh man.
Jessica!
Arthur!
Hi!
I'd like you to meet my boyfriend Greg.
He's the VP of Quality and Safety for a top Fortune 500 food company.
Nice to meet you.
This is my husband Arthur.
Hey, how's it going?
Hello.
Caroline talks about you all the time.
I guess you must be pretty busy at work.
Well, yeah, a VP position is not easy, you know.
I implement policies and procedures nationwide in various departments, as well as train junior managers in FDA and EPA regulations.
I also have to oversee daily operations of our quality control for the entire East Coast.
That alone means I have 1,500 employees under me.
Wow, yeah, that sounds exciting.
And what about you, Arthur?
What do you do for a living?
Oh, I'm a top gun pilot.