The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Talk about something a lot.
Go on about.
Top 500 companies rated by revenue.
Fortune 500.
Begin to do something, put into action.
Implement.
Have the duty or job of taking care of something.
Responsible.
In the whole country.
Take care of.
Look after.
Watch indirect to make sure a job is done correctly.
Oversee.
Checking goods to make sure that they are good enough to sell.
Quality control.
Working for me.
Under me.
Develop relationships.
Look after or take care of complaints.
Handle complaints.
Make arrangements or plans with a group of people.
Coordinate.
Watch and check.
Monitor.
Be in charge of something, watch and direct.
Supervise.
Make sure.
Ensure.
Let's try that faster.
In the whole country.
Nationwide.
Make arrangements or plans with a group of people.
Coordinate.
Watch indirect to make sure a job is done correctly.
Oversee.
Top 500 companies rated by revenue.
Fortune 500.
Take care of.
Look after.
Working for me.
Under me.
Checking goods to make sure that they are good enough to sell.
Quality control.
Be in charge of something, watch and direct.
Supervise.
Watch and check.
Monitor.
Have the duty or job of taking care of something.
Responsible.
Make sure.
Ensure.
Begin to do something, put into action.
Implement.
Develop relationships.
Look after or take care of complaints.
Handle complaints.
Talk about something a lot.
Go on about.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
My boss is always going on about how we need to save money.
It's all he talks about.
Go on about.
Gary is always going on about his kids.
He's always talking about how smart they are.
Go on about.
My mom is always going on about how I should get married.
Implement.
Our company has to implement this sales strategy.
Sarah will be responsible for implementing the plan.
Implement.
I implemented several new policies.
According to company regulations, we have to fly economy class.
You need to make sure that you follow the rules and regulations.
Government regulations do not allow us to import raw meat.
Oversee.
In my last job, I oversaw recruitment.
Jason, can you oversee this project?
Oversee.
I'm overseeing the budget in my department.
Nationwide.
Nationwide, we have 500 stores.
The government will be starting nationwide testing of grade 4 students.
Nationwide.
There is a nationwide shortage of doctors.
Under me.
In your new job, you'll have 18 employees under you.
I don't have any employees under me.
Under me.
Frank has 12 managers working under him.
Quality control.
Our quality control measures help make sure that there are no mistakes in our product.
I am responsible for quality control in our factory.
Quality control.
We have poor quality control, and so there are a lot of problems with our product.