The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A circular saw mounted under a table or bench so that large pieces of wood could be cut.
Table saw To try your best.
To give 110%.
A decorative strip used for ornamentation or finishing on the edges of a wall.
Molding A piece of wood that is 2 inches thick and 4 inches wide.
2 x 4 A wall or ceiling constructed of a prefabricated material such as plasterboard or paneling.
Drywall Let your effort be a reflection of your skill.
Take pride in your work.
A person or firm that supplies materials or labor for other companies.
Contractor Set of actions to complete a task.
Plans A person who makes or repairs wooden structures.
Carpenter A tool used to measure how long something is.
Measuring tape Let's try that faster.
Let your effort be a reflection of your skill.
Take pride in your work.
A circular saw mounted under a table or bench so that large pieces of wood could be cut.
Table saw A piece of wood that is 2 inches thick and 4 inches wide.
2 x 4 To try your best.
To give 110% A decorative strip used for ornamentation or finishing on the edges of a wall.
Molding A tool used to measure how long something is.
Measuring tape Set of actions to complete a task.
Plans A person or firm that supplies materials or labor for other companies.
Contractor A wall or ceiling constructed of a prefabricated material such as plasterboard or paneling.
Drywall A person who makes or repairs wooden structures.
Carpenter Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
To give 110% It's not enough to try your best.
You have to give 110% if you want to be successful.
To give 110% We really have to give 110% today if we want to finish this project on time.
To give 110% Good job team.
You really gave 110% out there today.
2 x 4 We need another 2 x 4 to finish this deck.
2 x 4 I can't come to work today because a 2 x 4 fell from my roof and hit me on the head.
2 x 4 2 x 4 Did you see that?
That wrestler pulled out a 2 x 4 and broke it on the other guy's back.
Take pride in your work.
When you take pride in your work, you will start to enjoy it more and may even want to learn more to improve yourself.
I respect Jim a lot because he really takes pride in his work and is very dedicated.
Take pride in your work.
How can I take pride in my work if I don't enjoy what I'm doing?
Plans Carl, I need the kitchen plans today so I can start putting up the kitchen cabinets.
Plans These floor plans are in Chinese.
We need to get them translated before we start construction.
Plans Plans Our architect isn't done drawing our floor plans but I'm sure the house is going to look great.
Measuring tape This measuring tape is in inches.
I need one that has centimeters on it.
Measuring tape Measuring tapes were originally used by tailors and dressmakers.
Measuring tape Check out my new digital measuring tape.
All I have to do is point at an object and it will tell me how far away it is.