All right, ladies and gentlemen, we've been hired to build a deck on this here house and turn this boring and drab lawn into a backyard oasis.
There is one catch though.
We've only got one day to finish this, so I'm going to need everyone to give 110% today.
It's going to be tough, but we've got a great team here and I know that together we can tackle this project.
That being said, let's get to work.
That's right.
Now, remember, we've been over the plans, but we really need to make sure that everything is up to code.
The home inspectors here are pretty thorough, so please make sure you follow the plans exactly.
And remember the carpenter's rule of thumb, measure twice, cut once.
Okay guys, let's get at it.
Bob, pass me that hammer.
The nails won't go in.
The wood is too hard.
I think I'm going to need the nail gun.
That did it.
Hey, do me a favor and help me cut this two by four, will ya?
Pass me that circle saw and grab hold of the end of the board.
Now help me drill some holes in it so we can place the bolts.
I think you should sand the edges.
Look at all these splinters.
Someone could get hurt.
Geez, you gotta take pride in your work.
Yeah, you're right.
Pass me the sander and I'll take care of it.
Julia, get over here with that level, measuring tape, and that box of screws.
Oh no!
Look out below!