The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Disorder Mess To be punished and not allowed to go outside.
Grounded To clean the floor with a broom or brush.
Sweep To help or collaborate in the household.
Pull your weight.
To remove dust and dirt.
Dust To clean the floor with water and a mop.
Mop To use an electric device to suction dust and dirt.
Vacuum Let's try that faster.
To help or collaborate in the household.
Pull your weight.
To clean the floor with water and a mop.
Mop To remove dust and dirt.
Dust To use an electric device to suction dust and dirt.
Vacuum To clean the floor with a broom or brush.
Sweep To be punished and not allowed to go outside.
Grounded Disorder Mess Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Grounded My parents grounded me for arriving home late.
Grounded Tom is grounded for a month because he got bad grades in school.
Grounded I think that it is necessary to ground your children when they misbehave.
Pull your weight I told my roommate he really has to start pulling his weight and help me with the bills.
Pull your weight I am tired of you not pulling your weight around here.
Pull your weight Mess My parents told me that since I am 18, I have to start pulling my weight and pay rent.
Mess The house was a mess after the party Saturday night.
Mess Every time you cook, you always leave a mess in the kitchen.
Mess My hair is a mess.
I should get a haircut.
Mop We need to get a new mop.
Mop I hate mopping the floors.
Mop Please be careful.
The floor is slippery because I just mopped.
Vacuum The vacuum cleaner broke, so now I can't clean the rug.
Vacuum I need to vacuum the carpet.
Vacuum I don't like sweeping the floors, so I just use the vacuum instead.