Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
critical condition ICU ER Tefibrillator Chest compressions Let's try that faster!
ICU critical condition Tefibrillator Pulse ER Hookup BP Flatline Chest compressions CPR Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Hookup I finally got a Nintendo Wii.
Come on, help me hook it up to the TV.
Hookup I don't know how to hook up this new DVD player.
Can you help me?
Hookup I just hooked up my new HDTV.
Want to come over and watch a movie?
Hookup If you don't hold still, I can't see if you have something in your eye.
Hookup Hold still while she cuts your hair or else she might make a mistake.
Hold still.
You have a bee on your back.
Hookup The patient is unconscious and not breathing.
We have to intubate.
His throat is obstructed and he's not breathing.
We're going to have to intubate.
Luckily, the doctors intubated me in time and pumped air into my lungs.
We need to stabilize the patient before we can put him in the ambulance.
Your husband has been stabilized and the bleeding has stopped.
The first person to treat an injured person must try and stabilize him before he can be moved.
Critical condition The patient is in critical condition, so we need to keep him here for a few weeks.
Critical condition Carl had a terrible car accident.
He's now in the hospital in critical condition.
Critical condition The disease is very serious and the patient is now in critical condition.