EnglishPod.com Halb!
Are you a doctor?
My poor little Frankie has just stopped breathing.
Oh my gosh, help me!
I tried to perform CPR, but I just...
I don't know if I could get any air into his lungs.
Oh, Frankie!
Ellen, get him hooked up to a monitor.
Somebody page Dr.
Hauser?
Get the patient to hold still.
I can't get a pulse.
Okay, he's on the monitor.
His BP's falling.
He's flatlining.
No!
Frankie!
Doctor, do something!
Someone get her out of here!
Get me the defibrillator!
Okay, clear!
Again, clear!
Come on, dammit, I'm not letting go of you.
Clear!
I got a pulse.
Okay, what's happening?
Patient is in acute respiratory failure.
I think we're going to have to innovate.
All right, tube's in.
Bag him.
Somebody give him 10 cc's shot of adrenaline.
Let's go!
People, move!
Move!
Doctor!
Oh, thank God!
How is he?
We've managed to stabilize Frankie, but he's not out of the woods yet.
He's still in critical condition.
We're moving him to intensive care, but...
Doctor, just do whatever it takes.
I just want my little Frankie to be okay.
I couldn't imagine life without my little hamster.