The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A dish made of raw vegetables.
Salad Truly Positively Very hungry Famished To be as loud as possible At the top of one's lungs An impolite way of calling someone foolish Dumbass Sexy to the greatest degree Sexy Someone who is stupid or useless Tool Control your emotions Get it together An impolite way of saying something is foolish Crap Someone who is very stupid Moron Calm down, relax Chill The belief that men and women should have equal rights and opportunities Feminism A romantic outing with someone that you have not met before Blind date A person who is very clumsy or awkward Spaz The way people see or perceive you the first time you meet First impression To miss an opportunity or chance Blow it Let's try that faster An impolite way of calling someone foolish Dumbass Calm down, relax Chill Very hungry Famished Someone who is stupid or useless Tool To be as loud as possible At the top of one's lungs Truly Positively Sexy to the greatest degree Sexy Someone who is very stupid Moron An impolite way of saying something is foolish Crap Control your emotions Get it together A dish made of raw vegetables Salad To miss an opportunity or chance Blow it A person who is very clumsy or awkward Spaz The way people see or perceive you the first time you meet First impression The belief that men and women should have equal rights and opportunities Feminism A romantic outing with someone that you have not met before Blind date Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Dumbass You're such a dumbass You can't carry marijuana into the airport Dumbass James is such a dumbass No wonder girls don't like him Dumbass That was a really dumbass thing to do Who the hell forgot to lock the office door?
Nick is 4 hours late Where the hell is he?
Why the hell would I know who started the fight?
I wasn't there I was screaming at the top of my lungs but no one heard me That guy looks crazy.
He's screaming at the top of his lungs We were screaming at the top of our lungs because we were so excited Get it together Get it together.
Now is not the time to start crying Get it together I'm so stressed out.
I just can't seem to get it together Get it together We were having a terrible game But then we got it together and won the match Chill Chill Chill.
I'll be there in 5 minutes Chill I'm just chilling with my friends Chill Chill out man.
It's not a big problem Chill out.