The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A professional who kills pests.
Exterminator An annoying and harmful insect or animal.
Pest To spray with smoke or other chemicals.
Fumigate Not be able to deal with.
Can't handle Simply Just Let's try that faster.
Simply Just An annoying and harmful insect or animal.
Pest A professional who kills pests.
Exterminator To spray with smoke or other chemicals.
Fumigate Not be able to deal with.
Can't handle Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Exterminator Can I get an exterminator to get rid of the wasps in our yard?
Exterminator I need to call an exterminator to take care of our termite problem.
Exterminator The exterminator came and sprayed the entire house.
So it should be bug free now.
Pest Our house is infested with all sorts of pests.
It's horrible.
Pest Pest Mosquitoes, termites, cockroaches, rats and fleas are all considered pests.
Pest Pest He's a pest.
He annoys everyone he comes in contact with.
Fumigate Pest If you have cockroaches in your home, you should fumigate it.
Fumigate Fumigate You shouldn't stay in your apartment when you fumigate it.
It's bad for your health.
Fumigate Fumigate She's staying with us for a few days because the exterminator is fumigating her house.
Can't handle Can't handle There is a large workload.
I can't handle it.
Can't handle Can't handle He's really good at fixing computers.
No matter how complicated the problem is, there's nothing he can't handle.
Can't handle Can't handle I can't handle any more criticism.
Just I don't care what you have to do.
Just take care of the problem.
Just Stop making excuses and just finish your work.
Just When you're done, you can just leave everything on the table and I'll clean it up.