You should have seen the TV show that was on last night.
The topic it covered was really interesting.
Animal rights.
Do you really believe in that?
If they're going to focus on something, they should do it on civil rights.
Yes, but we can't deny that animals are vulnerable, defenseless, and are completely at the mercy of human beings.
I understand your point, but we continue to have transgressions against human rights.
If so much attention weren't devoted to the topic of animals, we would then concentrate more on saving a human being instead of protecting a koala.
You can't compare apples and oranges.
I believe that both topics are important, and that we can't ignore them.
The mistreatment of animals can cause a great environmental imbalance.
I believe that governments should prohibit activities like poaching.
Well, you are right on that point.
This is the reason that I don't buy leather, and I try to buy synthetic products.
At least you're doing your part.
My contribution is to have a pet in the house that I treat like a member of the family.
As long as you don't treat it better than your wife, it's fine.