The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The rights people have.
Civil rights.
Capable of being decomposed by natural means.
Biodegradable.
Easily hurt or harmed.
Vulnerable.
A prolonged period of time during which no rain falls.
Drought.
Defenseless.
A severe shortage of food.
Famine.
In a position where you can be harmed.
At the mercy of.
The part of the Earth's surface and atmosphere inhabited by living things.
Biosphere.
Something that is not allowed.
Transgression.
A general term for the research activity that creates a copy of some biological entity.
Cloning.
An unfair comparison of two different things.
Apples and oranges.
To illegally hunt protected animals.
Poach.
Not natural.
Synthetic.
To help accomplish a goal.
Do your part.
Let's try that faster!
The rights people have.
Civil rights.
The part of the Earth's surface and atmosphere inhabited by living things.
Biosphere.
Something that is not allowed.
Transgression.
Easily hurt or harmed.
Vulnerable.
An unfair comparison of two different things.
Apples and oranges.
In a position where you can be harmed.
At the mercy of.
To illegally hunt protected animals.
Poach.
Defenseless.
A severe shortage of food.
Famine.
Capable of being decomposed by natural means.
Biodegradable.
Not natural.
Synthetic.
A general term for the research activity that creates a copy of some biological entity.
Cloning.
To help accomplish a goal.
Do your part.
A prolonged period of time during which no rain falls.
Drought.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Vulnerable.
The wound is vulnerable to infection.
A dry forest is vulnerable to fires.
Vulnerable.
The spawning salmon is vulnerable to predators.
At the mercy of.
The city is at the mercy of the forest fire.
The lost sailors were at the mercy of the vast ocean that lay ahead of them.
At the mercy of.
Our city is at the mercy of criminals and gangsters.
Something must be done.
Transgression.
All transgressions of the law will be severely punished.
She was guilty of the worst moral transgression.
Transgression.
There are legal consequences for those that transgress the law.
Apples and oranges.
You can't compare Batman and Superman.
It's like apples and oranges.
Apples and oranges.
The two operating systems are so different.
They're like apples and oranges.
Apples and oranges.
You can't compare those two authors.
It's like comparing apples to oranges.
Do your part.
Don't litter.
Your wife looks so tired.
You haven't been doing your part around the house.
Do your part.
Do your part to prevent climate change and try riding your bike to work.