The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Commemorate, fail in exams, flunk, memorize, commemorate, an agreement to stop a war, armistice, agreement, treaty, fail in exams, flunk, Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
armistice The two nations signed an armistice.
The key aspect in an armistice is the fact that all fighting ends with no one surrendering.
armistice The Korean War armistice was a major example of an armistice which was not followed by a peace treaty.
armistice Pain is remembrance.
You cannot forget pain.
armistice Nothing is more fatal to happiness than the remembrance of happiness.
armistice If it seems a childish thing to do, do it in remembrance that you are a child.
treaty This commerce treaty will bring prosperity between our great nations.
treaty We shall sign a peace treaty with the invaders.
treaty This treaty is not valid until I sign it.
commemorate We are gathered here today to commemorate the lives sacrificed in an act of heroism.
commemorate commemorate On November 11th, we commemorate the fallen with a march.
commemorate The cenotaph commemorates the fallen.
flunk I just found out that I flunked in math.
flunk If you flunk any school subject, you will be screwed.
flunk flunk I really hope the teacher doesn't flunk me.