So, Casey, how are things going with the photos for the press kit?
Yeah, I've been meaning to talk to you about that.
I might need to ask for an extension on that deadline.
You've had over a month to get this finalized.
Why are things delayed?
Well, the thing is, we ran into a lot of problems.
I'm not looking for excuses here.
I just want to get this finished on time.
I know, and I apologize for the delay, but some things were just beyond my control.
I had trouble booking the photographer, and then Michael was sick for three weeks, so I couldn't include him in the photos.
And the design team lost all the files, so I had to redo the pictures.
I'm not going to put this off any longer, Casey.
I want those photos ASAP.