The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
an advertisement or advert ad to give work hire a female whose job is to clean and cook maid a person that is hired to clean, a maid cleaning lady a servant who is paid to perform tasks around the house domestic help per hour hourly the current price or fee of something going rate discuss and reach a mutual deal negotiate the lowest legal salary a person can earn minimum wage Let's try that faster!
discuss and reach a mutual deal negotiate per hour hourly a female whose job is to clean and cook maid an advertisement or advert ad the current price or fee of something going rate the lowest legal salary a person can earn minimum wage a person that is hired to clean, a maid cleaning lady to give work hire a servant who is paid to perform tasks around the house domestic help Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
hire I would like to hire a full-time chef.
hire He was hired to help with marketing and promotion.
hire Our company will hire over 50 people this month.
cleaning lady I told a cleaning lady to sweep the floors.
cleaning lady My cleaning lady is great.
She cleans the house very well.
cleaning lady I fired my cleaning lady because she wasn't doing a good job.
going rate What is the going rate for a translator?
going rate The price you quoted me is much higher than the going rate.
going rate The going rate for a new car is over $10,000.
negotiate We need to negotiate the terms of this contract.
Negotiate I am not very good at negotiating.
I feel uncomfortable doing it.
I will negotiate my contract with the company tomorrow at our meeting.
minimum wage I barely earn minimum wage.
minimum wage The government is considering increasing minimum wage by 30%.
minimum wage Waiters and waitresses earn less than minimum wage because they earn tips.