EnglishPod.com Can you help me write a newspaper ad?
Sure.
What are you looking to buy or sell?
Actually, I want to hire someone to help me around the house.
Oh, you want to get a maid?
Well, I think it's better if you call her a cleaning lady or domestic help.
Okay, so what do you want her to do?
Well, let's see.
I want her to come in three times a week for a couple of hours to clean the kitchen, bathroom, and maybe do some cooking.
Got it.
And how much do you offer per month?
I would pay her hourly.
I don't know what the going rate is, though.
I know for sure it's more than minimum wage, but maybe you should just negotiate with the person that answers the ad.
Great.
Thanks for your help.