EnglishPod.com It's almost midnight.
We're about to start a brand new year.
I know.
It's so exciting.
A new year is always like a clean slate.
A fresh start to accomplish any dreams, objectives and goals.
Do you have a new year's resolution?
I was thinking about it, but I'm never able to keep my new year's resolutions.
Last year, for example, I joined a gym and only went twice.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
That's why this year I am keeping things more simple.
Maybe like getting together with friends I haven't seen in a long time or doing some volunteering work.
That seems reasonable.
We should get together and watch the ball drop in Times Square.
Sure.
As long as you don't try to kiss me at midnight.
Well, we can't break tradition.
It's bad luck!