The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
You won't believe.
You will never guess.
The principal groomsman at a wedding.
Best man.
You don't know what news I have.
You will never guess.
A party held for a man that is getting married.
Bachelor party.
A male friend who attends a bridegroom at his wedding.
Groomsman.
Absurdly or amusingly eccentric or irrational.
Wacky.
Funny or adult type toys or gifts.
Gag gift.
Extreme, excessive.
Over the top.
An unmarried woman.
Bachelorette.
Let's try that faster.
A party held for a man that is getting married.
Bachelor party.
You won't believe.
You will never guess.
A male friend who attends a bridegroom at his wedding.
Groomsman.
Absurdly or amusingly eccentric or irrational.
Wacky.
An unmarried woman.
Bachelorette.
Extreme, excessive.
Over the top.
You don't know what news I have.
You will never guess.
The principal groomsman at a wedding.
Best man.
Funny or adult type toys or gifts.
Gag gift.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
You will never guess.
You'll never guess who I just saw at the supermarket.
Brad Pitt!
You will never guess.
You'll never guess what just happened to me.
I won the lottery!
You will never guess.
You'll never guess how late I stayed at work until last night.
11pm.
Bachelor party.
For many men, a bachelor party is a way to say goodbye to having a free life.
Often it's the best man who arranges the bachelor party.
Bachelor party.
His fiance is really against the idea of a bachelor party.
Over the top.
Those purple jeans are just over the top.
I'm not looking for anything too over the top.
Just a nice quiet evening with friends.
Over the top.
Did you see his mowalk?
It's really over the top.
Gag gift.
They don't like to take birthdays too seriously, so they always buy each other gag gifts.
I love shopping for gag gifts.
They're always so silly.
Gag gift.
He didn't want a serious gift, so I just bought him a gift.
He just got him a whoopee cushion as a gag gift.
Best man.
He doesn't know if he should choose his brother or his best friend to be his best man.
At American weddings, the best man traditionally gives a toast to the bride and groom.
Best man.
The best man has many responsibilities at a wedding.
Some say even more than the groom himself.