EnglishPod.com Hi honey!
You'll never guess what.
My friends Julie and Alex are getting married!
Wow, that's great news.
They're a great couple.
I know.
Anyways, I just talked to Alex's best man and he is organizing the bachelor party.
It's gonna be so much fun!
All the groomsmen are thinking up all the wacky and crazy things we were gonna do that night.
You aren't going to a strip club, are you?
I don't want you getting a lap dance from some stripper with the excuse that it's your friend's party.
Aw, come on.
It's just some innocent fun.
You know how these things are.
We're gonna play drinking games, get him some gag gifts, and just have a good time.
Nothing too over the top.
Well, I don't know.
Come on.
If one of your friends was getting married, I wouldn't mind you going to her bachelorette party.
Good.
Because my friend Wendy is getting married and I'm organizing her party.
What?