The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An average size, not too big or small.
Medium A spicy sausage, usually on pizza.
Pepperoni A small, egg-shaped black or green fruit that is used as food or for making oil.
Olive Pay for one and get another one free.
Two for one In replacement of Instead Seems or appears to be okay, I agree.
Sounds good The border of a pizza or bread.
Crust Complete amount you must pay.
Total Transported or taken to your house.
Delivery A mix of flour and water that is used to make the base of a pizza.
Dough Food that is quickly made and convenient if you are in a hurry.
Fast food Sum of everything Total Food you take away from the restaurant to eat.
Takeout Let's try that faster.
Complete amount you must pay.
Total An average size, not too big or small.
Medium Pay for one and get another one free.
Two for one Food you take away from the restaurant to eat.
Takeout The border of a pizza or bread.
Crust Sum of everything Total A mix of flour and water that is used to make the base of a pizza.
Dough Seems or appears to be okay, I agree.
Sounds good A spicy sausage, usually on pizza.
Pepperoni In replacement of Instead Transported or taken to your house.
Delivery A small egg-shaped black or green fruit that is used as food or for making oil.
Olive Food that is quickly made and convenient if you are in a hurry.
Fast food Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
I'd like to talk to the manager.
She'd like a glass of water, please.
We'd like a sweet on the top floor.
Sounds good Your idea for this new project sounds good.
I like it.
Sounds good You want to go on vacation to Jamaica?
That sounds good.
Sounds good All the things you say sound good, but I don't believe you.
Two for one Today in the supermarket, they have a two for one offer on laundry detergent.
Two for one It's amazing.
There is a two for one sale at the car dealer.
Two for one I usually buy pizza when they have a two for one special.
Brust My sister always removes the crust from her bread.
Brust When I eat pizza, I always throw away the crust.
Brust When my mom made apple pie, she would let me make the crust.
Total Here is your bill, sir.
Your total is 125.
Total My total income last year was $30,000.
Total Total of today's dinner was $300.