EnglishPod.com Hello, Samantha speaking.
Hi, Samantha.
This is Angela calling.
Oh, hi, Angela.
What's up?
I'm just calling about our meeting today.
I wonder, is it possible to reschedule our appointment in the afternoon?
I have a bit of an emergency that I need to take care of.
Let me see.
It shouldn't be too much of a problem.
I'm really sorry.
I hope it doesn't inconvenience you too much.
It's just this thing came up and...
Angela, you know what?
I can't make it to our meeting either.
Why don't we postpone it to tomorrow afternoon at the same time?
Sounds great.
See you tomorrow.
Angela?
Angela, look up.
See that lady over there who's trying on a red leather jacket?
Isn't that Samantha?
What?
No wonder she told me she couldn't make it to the meeting.
Oh, no.
I think she saw me.