The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Rise rapidly, as in price.
Sky rocket Beyond the ability to direct the actions of something.
Out of control Plan the way to spend money in order to save more.
Budget Assign Allocate To be honest, to say it directly.
Frankly speaking, Let's try that faster.
Assign Allocate Beyond the ability to direct the actions of something.
Out of control To be honest, to say it directly.
Frankly speaking, Plan the way to spend money in order to save more.
Budget Rise rapidly, as in price.
Sky rocket Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sky rocket The ratings for this TV show have skyrocketed in the past month.
Sky rocket Sky rocket Her popularity skyrocketed after she won the competition.
Sky rocket Out of control The company's profits skyrocketed with their new advertising campaign.
Out of control Budget I really need to learn how to budget because my spending is out of control.
Out of control Out of control Her anger was out of control when she learned that they had killed him.
Out of control His driving was out of control.
Budget Out of control My roommates and I really need to start budgeting the money we spend on food.
Budget Her family has started to budget the money they spend on shopping.
Budget He needs to start budgeting his time better.
Allocate The teacher allocated tasks to different students.
Allocate I need to allocate my study time between my different courses.
Allocate Allocate He allocated the prize money to different charities.
Frankly speaking Frankly speaking you should break up with him.
Frankly speaking The government is just trying to get away with raising taxes again.
Frankly speaking To be frank, I don't think this is a good decision.
Thank you for watching.