Hey Lydia, what are you reading?
I'm looking at my horoscope for this month.
My outlook is very positive.
It says that I should take a vacation to some place exotic and that I will have a passionate summer fling.
What are you talking about?
Let me see that.
What are horoscopes?
It's a prediction of your month based on your zodiac sign.
You have a different sign for the month and date you were born in.
I was born on April 15th, so I'm an Aries.
When were you born?
January 5th.
Let's see, you're a Capricorn.
It says that you'll be feeling stress at work, but you could see new exciting developments in your love life.
Looks like we'll both have interesting summers.
That's bogus.
I don't feel any stress at work and my love life is practically non-existent.
This zodiac stuff is all a bunch of nonsense.
No it's not.
Your astrology sign can tell you a lot about your personality.
See it says that an Aries is energetic and loves to socialize.
Well you certainly match those criteria, but they're so broad they could apply to anyone.
What does it say about me?
A Capricorn is serious minded and practical.
She likes to do things in conventional ways.
That sounds just like you.