The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Important Needing immediate action Urgent Guide someone along the process Take one through A series of actions Procedure An occurrence in which money is transferred from one account to another Transaction Not paid at an expected or required time Missing the deadline Overdue Let's try that faster An occurrence in which money is transferred from one account to another Transaction Important Needing immediate action Urgent Not paid at an expected or required time Missing the deadline Overdue A series of actions Procedure Guide someone along the process Take one through Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Urgent Where's Mr.
Jameson?
I have some urgent news for him.
Urgent Could you call me back as soon as you get my message?
It's urgent.
Urgent I could tell something was wrong by the urgent tone of Lydia's voice.
Take one through Let me take you through the manufacturing process.
Take one through He took me through the steps and helped me fix my computer.
Take one through If you just follow my secretary, Ms.
Finn, she will take you through what we do at this company.
Procedure The company has a set manufacturing procedure that you must follow.
Procedure We check the quality of our products through a complicated procedure.
This is how we make sure our products are safe.
Procedure There was not really a procedure, so we just did what we wanted.
Transaction The transaction with the bank went smoothly.
Transaction If you come prepared, it will really help speed up the transaction.
You can go online and see all the transactions you made with your credit card.
Overdue He wouldn't accept my paper because it was overdue.
Overdue You are charged a dollar every day that your library books are overdue.
Overdue Manny always forgets to pay his bills, so many of them are overdue.