Have an inclination or desire for, feel like, piece of cow meat, steak, a person who does not eat meat or fish, vegetarian, a person who does not eat or use animal products, vegan, made with animal skin that is chemically treated, leather, originates from, come from, continuing to become larger in number, more and more.
Let's try that faster.
A person who does not eat or use animal products, vegan, continuing to become larger in number, more and more.
A person who does not eat meat or fish, vegetarian, originates from, come from, made with animal skin that is chemically treated, leather, piece of cow meat, steak, have an inclination or desire for, feel like.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Feel like.
I don't like ice cream, I want cookies instead.
What do you feel like doing today?
Feel like.
He doesn't feel like doing his homework, his mother will be angry with him.
Steak.
There is no steak on the menu, this is a vegetarian restaurant.
He loves to eat steak on special occasions.
Steak.
I refuse to eat rare steak, I only eat it when it's well done.
Vegetarian.
All my friends are vegetarian, but I love my meat.
Now that he is a Buddhist, he is a strict vegetarian.
Vegetarian.
She stopped being a vegetarian as soon as she saw her favourite food, hot dogs.
Vegan.
In my opinion, you're not a real vegan if you eat cheese.
She believes that being vegan is not just a choice, it's a lifestyle.
Vegan.
Now that my friend is a vegan, he no longer wears the leather.
Lever.
Wow, check out my new leather jacket, I'm so cool.
She saved up all her money to buy a leather couch.
Lever.
I don't like leather, it's ruined if it gets wet in the rain.
Come from.
Where do you come from?
I come from Australia.
Come from.
All the people who come from here seem to love chocolate.
You scared me, where did you come from?
More and more.
As it gets closer to dinner, I'm feeling more and more hungry.
More and more bugs flew into her room.
More and more.
The police were becoming more and more convinced that he was the killer.