The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Many times.
A hundred times.
Take care of.
Take responsibility for.
Look after.
To wash.
Bathe.
A particular kind of dog.
Breed.
To begin with.
Take it from there.
Extremely good.
Awesome.
Let's try that faster.
Extremely good.
Awesome.
To begin with.
Take it from there.
To wash.
Bathe.
Many times.
A hundred times.
A particular kind of dog.
Breed.
Take care of.
Take responsibility for.
Look after.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
A hundred times.
I've told you a hundred times already to keep your hands off the stove.
I've told you a hundred times don't date guys who still live with their parents.
A hundred times.
We have been through this a hundred times and for the last time nobody goes into my room without my permission.
Look after.
I need to look after my friend's goldfish while she's away.
Honey, can you look after the baby while I go get some groceries?
Look after.
It's my son's job to look after the lawn in the summer.
Bathe.
The cat bathes in the sunlight on the porch all afternoon.
I bathe my dog every second week.
Bathe.
I think it's time to give you a bathing.
Breed.
What breed of dog were you looking for?
My dog is a mixed breed of poodle and Maltese.
Breed.
The local pet store only carries two breeds of birds which are budgies and lovebirds.
Take it from there.
Let's solve this problem first and we'll take it from there.
We need to perfect this section of the dance routine and then we'll take it from there.
Take it from there.
We'll see how our users respond to the new website and we'll take it from there.