We have been over this a hundred times.
We are not getting a pet.
Why not?
Come on!
Just a cute little puppy.
Or a kitty!
Who's going to look after a dog or a cat?
I will!
I'll feed it, bathe it, and walk it every day.
We can get a Labrador or a German Shepherd.
What if we want to take a vacation?
Who will we leave it with?
Plus, our apartment is too small for that breed of dog.
Okay, how about we get a cat or a ferret?
We're planning on having children soon.
I don't think those animals are a good idea with a baby in the house.
Fine, let's get a bird then.
We can keep it in its cage and teach it to talk.
A parrot would be awesome.
I'll tell you what, I can get you some hamsters and we'll take it from there.
Yay!