The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
afraid a light fall of rain drizzle fall of rain accompanied by lightning and thunder thunderstorm probability chance rain that is frozen into chunks of ice hail Let's try that faster.
rain that is frozen into chunks of ice hail probability chance a light fall of rain drizzle scared afraid fall of rain accompanied by lightning and thunder thunderstorm Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
afraid The project is due tomorrow, but he just gave it to us this morning.
I'm afraid we're in for a long night.
afraid I'm sorry.
I'm afraid you misunderstood me.
afraid I'm afraid that he can't make it tonight.
I've made other plans.
drizzle It's drizzling outside, so you should take your umbrella when you go out.
drizzle It's not raining hard.
Just a light drizzle.
drizzle drizzle I like to drizzle some maple syrup on my pancakes.
thunderstorm We planned to have a picnic in the park, but the weather report said there would be a thunderstorm today.
thunderstorm My little sister is terrified of lightning.
She always cries during the thunderstorms.
thunderstorm It's dangerous to go out with an umbrella during the thunderstorm.
hail hail There's a 70% chance of rain today, so it might not be the best day to go to the beach.
hail You have a high chance of getting the job.
The boss seems to like you.
hail If you are careful and follow the rules, you have a very small chance of hurting yourself rock climbing.
hail hail There is a chance that it will hail today, so we should stay inside.
hail The last time it hailed, the roof of my car was badly damaged.
hail It's hailing really badly outside.
The hail is the size of tennis balls.