The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Occasion Occasion A word used to describe 12 units.
Dozen Says something deserves to be chosen.
Null Null More polite way of calling someone fat.
Chubby Let's try that faster.
Occasion Occasion Null Null A word used to describe 12 units.
Dozen Says something deserves to be chosen.
Null More polite way of calling someone fat.
Chubby Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Dozen I would like to buy a dozen of eggs.
Dozen He sent her six dozen flowers, representing the six years that they have been married.
Dozen Take a dozen of your best men and scout the forest.
Occasion On this occasion, I would like to buy something very special.
Occasion Occasions like this don't come so often in my life.
Occasion Occasion What's the occasion for your visit?
Null I recommend you to stay away from that jungle.
Null Null He would recommend many unnecessary things.
Null He recommended me to hire this man.
Null The fragrance of lilies is very pleasant.
Null He always has such a sweet fragrance.
Null Null She bought a new perfume with a fragrance too sweet for my taste.
Chubby She got so much chubbier over the summer.
Chubby My dog keeps getting chubbier.
Chubby He was a lot chubbier last time I saw him.