EnglishPod.com Hello, sir.
How may I help you?
I would like to buy some flowers, please.
Something really nice.
I see.
May I ask what the occasion is?
It's not really an occasion.
It's more like I'm sorry.
Very well.
This arrangement here is very popular among regretful husbands and boyfriends.
It has a dozen long-stemmed red roses with a couple of sunflowers and a single orchid that stands out.
It includes a small teddy bear to achieve the effect of immediate forgiveness.
I think I'm going to need more than just a dozen red roses and a bear.
What else do you recommend?
Well, this is our I'm sorry I cheated on you package.
Two dozen red roses lined with tulips, carnations and lilies.
The fragrance and beauty of this flower arrangement is sure to make her forgive you.
I don't think that's going to cut it.
I need something bigger and better.
I'm sorry, sir, but what exactly did you do?
Well, I may have accidentally insinuated that she is getting chubbier.
Get out of my store, you jerk!