The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A small, natural indentation in the flesh.
Dimple A small, dark brown spot on a person's skin.
Mole A small, brownish spot on someone's skin.
Freckle Having the shape of an egg.
Oval Let's try that faster.
A small, dark brown spot on a person's skin.
Mole Having the shape of an egg.
Oval A small, natural indentation in the flesh.
Dimple A small, brownish spot on someone's skin.
Freckle Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Oval Your baby has the cutest little dimples on her face.
Oval I like to make her smile because I can see her dimples.
Oval I heard some actresses have dimples surgically put on their face.
Mole She has the biggest mole on her nose.
Mole You should have that mole checked out by a doctor.
Mole Mole I think that little mole above your lip is beautiful.
Dimple Most redheads have lots of freckles on their face.
Dimple Sometimes I wish I had freckles because I think they are fun.
Dimple I wonder what it would look like if I connected all the freckles on your face with a pen.
Oval Some people think an American football is shaped like an oval.
Oval Her face is long, almost like an oval.
Miss Smith, what is the difference between a circle and an oval?