The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Spend money on something in order to get back more.
Invest A U.S.
government program to protect certain groups.
Social Security Let's try that faster.
Spend money on something in order to get back more.
Invest A U.S.
government program to protect certain groups.
Social Security Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Social Security Excuse me, sir, please fill in your social security number in these blanks.
Social Security Throughout a worker's career, the Social Security Administration keeps track of his or her earnings.
Social Security If a worker covered by Social Security dies, a surviving spouse can receive survivor's benefits.
Invest I was hoping to get my money invested in something safe.
Invest He was in such a hurry to get that money invested that he didn't realize his decision was horrible.
Invest How do you think I should get this money invested?
Social Security Peter was deducted half a month's salary when he became ill.
Social Security Some banks will deduct a monthly fee from your account.
Social Security The referee deducted three points from the opposite team.
Invest The thief ran off with over half a million dollars.
Invest A dog came into my house and ran off with my shoe.
Invest The police chased the criminal through the neighborhood, but he managed to run off into the forest.
Social Security I really don't understand some of the business jargon that is used in my office.
Social Security My brother is really into computers and knows all the computer jargon used in the cyber world.
Social Security I get lost in marketing meetings when they start using jargon such as POP or POS.