The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The history of the education you've had.
Educational background.
With special recognition for receiving very high marks.
With honors.
The main field of study in an undergraduate degree.
A limited area of study.
To have a secondary area of study in an undergraduate program.
The combination of courses taken in a degree program.
Course of study.
Track.
Masters or Ph.D.
Education above the bachelor's degree level.
Postgraduate.
For that reason.
Hence.
Try to do something over a longer period of time.
Pursue.
Try hard to do something.
Strive.
A wide range or scope of something.
Breath.
Important and large enough to have a noticeable effect.
Significant.
Adding or giving something.
Contribution.
University education.
Tertiary education.
Take the chance to do something before others do.
Take initiative.
Make something different in a special way.
Distinguish.
A good quality or feature that someone has.
Attribute.
Examine something in a careful and critical way.
Scrutinize.
Let's try that faster.
Take the chance to do something before others do.
Take initiative.
A good quality or feature that someone has.
Attribute.
To have a secondary area of study in an undergraduate program.
Minor.
With special recognition for receiving very high marks.
With honors.
The history of the education you've had.
Educational background.
Try to do something over a longer period of time.
Pursue.
Course of study.
Track.
Masters or PhD.
Education above the bachelor's degree level.
Postgraduate.
For that reason.
Hence.
University education.
Tertiary education.
Adding or giving something.
Contribution.
The combination of courses taken in a degree program.
Course of study.
The main field of study in an undergraduate degree.
Major.
A limited area of study.
Specialization.
Try hard to do something.
Strive.
Important and large enough to have a noticeable effect.
Significant.
Make something different in a special way.
Distinguish.
Examine something in a careful and critical way.
Scrutinize.
A wide range or scope of something.
Breath.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Course of study.
I chose this course of study because it offers a wide range of work opportunities.
I want to change my course of study before the next semester starts.
Course of study.
My sister didn't choose her course of study.
My parents decided for her.
Pursue.
They wanted to pursue their dream of traveling around the world, but it didn't happen.
My mother wants me to pursue a career in law.
Pursue.
You should really pursue that master's degree.
It would really help your career.
Strive.
If you want to be successful, you must strive to achieve your goals.
We strive to bring you outstanding customer service.
Strive.
Our company always strives to make our products better and better.
Hence.
The project was a complete failure.
Hence, the project manager was fired.
Hence.
The project was postponed for three months.
Hence, the delay in delivery.
Hence.
I never studied for my exams.
Hence, my low marks.