EnglishPod.com Thanks for coming in today.
Did you have any trouble finding us?
Please, take a seat.
Thank you.
Well, let's get started.
Tell me a bit about your educational background.
Sure.
Well, I graduated with honors from Chesterton University with a major in Business Administration with a specialization in Information Management, and I minored in Psychology.
I chose this course of study for two reasons.
I wanted to gain some practical, marketable skills, which the Information Management track provided, and I also feel that the interpersonal skills are essential for professional success, hence the minor in Psychology.
Interesting.
And your postgraduate studies?
Well, I am really passionate about consumer behavior, so I pursued a Master's in that area.
I also strive to keep my professional skills current, so I continuously attend seminars and conferences related to management and customer service.
Very good.
Now, tell me a little bit about your work experience.
I see here that you previously worked at Oracle.
Yeah, I worked as their Customer Support Manager, which brought me a breadth of experience in both client care and process management.
I supervised and coordinated the customer support team, as well as implemented new strategies to achieve better customer satisfaction.
Interesting.
Yes, in this position, I was able to make some pretty significant contributions to the overall success of the company.
With the different initiatives that we implemented, we lowered our churn rate to about 5%, which had a direct impact on revenue.