EnglishPod.com This is the operator.
How may I help you?
Yes, I would like to make a collect call.
Okay, sir.
Please dial the number.
Now, please state your name.
Tommy.
Please wait a moment.
Hello.
You have a collect call from Tommy.
Would you like to accept the charges?
Yes, of course.
Dad?
Yeah, Tommy.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah, Dad.
Everything is okay.
I'm calling you because I want to know if it's okay for me to go to my friend's house today after school.
Yeah, sure.
No problem.
You scared me to death.
I've told you to make a collect call in case of an emergency only.
Why didn't you call me from your mobile phone?
I ran out of credit and I also didn't have 25 cents for the payphone.
Sorry, Dad.