The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A person who operates a telephone switchboard.
Operator Amount of money to be paid.
Charge The positive balance in a person's mobile phone account.
Credit A public telephone operated by coins or a phone card.
Payphone A telephone call that the receiving party is asked to pay for.
Collect call Let's try that faster.
A person who operates a telephone switchboard.
Operator A public telephone operated by coins or a phone card.
Payphone The positive balance in a person's mobile phone account.
Credit A telephone call that the receiving party is asked to pay for.
Collect call Amount of money to be paid.
Charge Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Payphone I need to make a call but I can't find my mobile.
Guess I'll use a payphone.
Payphone Payphones are becoming less relevant in today's world since the invention of mobile phones.
Payphone Payphone I only have small change left, just enough to use the payphone.
Operator Hello operator, please put me through to the local library.
Operator The operator was so rude and unhelpful.
Operator I waited on the line for ages, but no operator answered.
Credit After that international call to Ecuador, the operator called me.
I have no credit left.
Credit I need to buy some more credit for my mobile as I can't call anyone.
Credit I like to text people as it doesn't cost me that much credit.
Collect call I'm going to make a collect call to my friend in Pakistan.
Hope mum doesn't mind.
Collect call Collect call My friend had no money, so I took a collect call from him.
He better pay me back.
Collect call My dad never takes a collect call from me anymore.
He says I waste his money talking about nothing.
Charge I'm going to get a huge charge for that long phone call I made last night.
Charge She got another charge for using the internet.
This time she can't afford to pay it off.
Charge She is going to be charged for the bill, even though it was her brother who ordered the limo.