The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A large, strong, dangerous fire.
Blaze.
Far from a city or town.
In the middle of nowhere.
Temporary stop in a romantic relationship.
Break.
Early in the morning.
First thing in the morning.
Everything is okay.
Everything is normal.
Everything seems to be in order.
Date when the doctor thinks the baby will be born.
Due date.
Be created.
Conceived.
Having no mistakes or errors.
Accurate.
An appointment to see the doctor to make sure the person is healthy.
Checkup.
A medical test done to see if a woman is pregnant.
Pregnancy test.
Early in the afternoon, before anything else.
First thing in the afternoon.
A place far from cities or towns.
Informal.
The boonies.
A person whose job is to put out fires, male or female.
Firefighter.
Let's try that faster.
An appointment to see the doctor to make sure the person is healthy.
Checkup.
A person whose job is to put out fires, male or female.
Firefighter.
A place far from cities or towns.
Informal.
The boonies.
Everything is okay.
Everything is normal.
Everything seems to be in order.
Far from a city or town.
In the middle of nowhere.
A medical test done to see if a woman is pregnant.
Pregnancy test.
Having no mistakes or errors.
Accurate.
Early in the afternoon, before anything else.
First thing in the afternoon.
A large, strong, dangerous fire.
Blaze.
Temporary stop in a romantic relationship.
Break.
Early in the morning.
First thing in the morning.
Date when the doctor thinks the baby will be born.
Due date.
Be created.
Conceived.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Blaze.
The family escaped the blaze just in time.
Minutes later, the house burnt down.
Blaze.
The fireman rescued two kittens from the blaze.
Four people were injured in the blaze after the stove caught fire.
Accurate.
Are you sure that your watch is accurate?
This data isn't accurate because it's five years old.
Accurate.
I need you to be more accurate.
When exactly did this happen?
In the middle of nowhere.
I have no idea where the nearest town is.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
In the middle of nowhere.
We were in the middle of nowhere when the car ran out of gas.
What?
You want to move to Kansas?
That's in the middle of nowhere.
First thing in the morning.
I'll call you first thing in the morning.
Will you be awake at seven?
First thing in the morning.
We left first thing in the morning to avoid traffic.
He sent me the email first thing in the morning.
Everything seems to be in order.
I've checked your files and everything seems to be in order.
Everything seems to be in order for your visa application.
Everything seems to be in order.
The doctor told me everything seemed to be in order.