The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
unavoidable inevitable Money that is saved to pay for something in the future, usually a house or retirement.
nest egg A state of confusion, disorder, disturbance.
Turmoil Amount of money the government uses to improve the economy.
Stimulus package State of not being stable, being likely to change.
Nations undergoing quick industrialization.
Emerging market Combined Reduced in value Devalue Ask for money Hit up Let's try that faster!
unavoidable Inevitable Ask for money Hit up Amount of money the government uses to improve the economy.
Stimulus package State of not being stable, being likely to change.
Money that is saved to pay for something in the future, usually a house or retirement.
nest egg A state of confusion, disorder, disturbance.
Turmoil State of not being stable, being likely to change.
A state of confusion, disorder, disturbance.
Turmoil Unavoidable Inevitable Reduced in value Devalue Nations undergoing quick industrialization.
Emerging market State of not being stable, being likely to change.
Nations undergoing quick industrialization.
Emerging market Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Inevitable Jason knew he was going to get laid off, but he was trying to delay the inevitable.
nest egg I invested in the stock market 5 years ago and built a nice nest egg.
Turmoil With a civil war, a famine, and inflation, the country has been in turmoil for 10 years.
Emerging market Demand for luxury goods is growing quickly in emerging markets like China.
Devalue The currency has been devalued by nearly 40%.
Hit up I'm going to hit up the boss for a raise.
Inevitable Inevitable Jason knew he was going to get laid off, but he was trying to delay the inevitable.
Emerging market Demand for luxury goods is growing quickly in emerging markets like China.
Devalue The currency has been devalued by nearly 40%.
Hit up I'm going to hit up the boss for a raise.