EnglishPod.com Hello everyone and welcome to Open Mic Night.
You're in for a real treat as we've got a lot of great comics here with us tonight.
First up, we have a very funny man coming straight from the state of Montana, Robert Hicks.
Thank you everyone.
Well, what a lovely crowd.
You know, there's nothing I love better than stand-up comedy.
You know, I've been working on my routine for months now and I've got some real zingers for you tonight.
Let's start out with some short jokes.
How about that?
Where do you find a one-legged dog?
Where you left it?
Get it?
Anyways, what do you call a sheep with no legs?
A cloud.
Tough crowd.
Alright, now you're going to love this joke.
It's hilarious.
What do cows do for entertainment?
They rent movies.
Movies.
Okay, we've got a few hecklers in the audience, but this one is good.
What does a fish say when it runs into a wall?
Damn!
Get out of here!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, last one.
Why do gorillas have big nostrils?
Because they've got big fingers.
They've got big fingers.
Thanks everyone, that was my time.
Thanks for watching!