The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
When a club or restaurant allows for anyone to sing or perform.
Open mic night.
A reply to an insult, a witty retort.
Come back.
When someone performs comedy while standing on a stage.
Stand-up comedy.
Insulting or in some other way defaming someone or something.
Dis.
A series of things such as movements or jokes.
Routine.
To play a joke or prank someone.
Punk.
A quick and clever comment that criticizes.
Zinger.
Make fun of or laugh at someone.
Mock.
Someone who interrupts, someone such as a speaker.
Heckler.
In an unrestrained manner, spontaneously.
Ad lib.
Let's try that faster.
When a club or restaurant allows for anyone to sing or perform.
Open mic night.
To play a joke or prank someone.
Punk.
Make fun of or laugh at someone.
Mock.
When someone performs comedy while standing on a stage.
Stand-up comedy.
In an unrestrained manner, spontaneously.
Ad lib.
A series of things such as movements or jokes.
Routine.
Insulting or in some other way defaming someone or something.
Dis.
A reply to an insult, a witty retort.
Comeback.
Someone who interrupts, someone such as a speaker.
Heckler.
A quick and clever comment that criticizes.
Zinger.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Open mic night.
Tonight there's an open mic night at the local comedy club.
Wanna go?
Open mic night.
This is the last time I go to an open mic night.
The performers were horrible.
Open mic night.
Tom wants to go to the open mic night tonight since his friend is going to perform.
Stand-up comedy.
Many famous comedians and actors started by doing stand-up comedy.
I love watching stand-up comedy.
All those jokes and funny stories put me in a good mood.
Stand-up comedy.
Did you hear?
The bar down the street is going to have stand-up comedy tonight.
Let's go.
Routine.
Carle has an amazing magic trick routine that he always performs at parties.
Madonna's dance routine is perfect.
She's such a good dancer.
Routine.
A good performer should have a solid routine when they get on stage.
Zinger.
Max is such a funny guy.
He always greets me with a new zinger.
Zinger.
I like to come up with witty zingers from time to time.
That comedian made me laugh so hard.
He had so many funny zingers.
Heckler.
The crowd was full of hecklers and Routine had a great time.
And really gave the performer a hard time.
Heckler.
That meeting was horrible.
Everyone was acting like a group of hecklers.
Heckler.
There was a heckler today at the press conference who really gave the president a hard time by being loud and obnoxious.
Thanks for watching!