The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Existing, happening, or available in a store In store To emphasize a point Hammer home To show or reveal Unveil A more forceful way of saying each Each and every Let's try that faster Existing, happening, or available in a store In store To show or reveal Unveil To emphasize a point Hammer home A more forceful way of saying each Each and every Now say the word and hear it in a sentence In store We have an exciting day in store for you In store James, you're such a good person.
I'm sure the universe has good things in store for you.
In store When Mary comes to work Monday, we will have a real surprise in store for her.
Hammer home Hammer home I like to use real life examples in my speeches as they really hammer home the point I'm trying to make.
Hammer home He used striking photographs to hammer home the tragedy caused by the earthquake.
Hammer home Khrushchev once famously hammered home his point by beating the table with his shoe.
Hammer home We installed a state of the art production line in our new factory.
Hammer home You think my baseball shoes are ugly, but they're state of the art.
Hammer home Today's state of the art technology will be out of date next year.
Each and every That's a serious mistake.
Now we will have to go back and check each and every piece for flaws.
Each and every Each and every one of you has a vital role to play in this organization.
Each and every I want to personally invite each and every member of our audience this evening to join us for their opening ceremony next week.
Unveil We are all ready to unveil the brand new line of smartphones to the media today.
Unveil Next year's company strategy will be unveiled this evening.
Unveil It gives me great pleasure to unveil our company's new logo design.