The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Disturb or bother.
Trouble A period of time when the economy of a country is bad.
Recession Had a strong, negative effect on me.
Hit me pretty hard.
The amount of money you owe to a person, bank, company, etc.
Debt Besides that, in addition to.
On top of all that.
Not have any money.
Broke Let's try that faster.
The amount of money you owe to a person, bank, company, etc.
Debt Besides that, in addition to.
On top of all that.
Disturb or bother.
Trouble Not have any money.
Broke Disturb or bother.
Trouble Besides that, in addition to.
On top of all that.
Had a strong, negative effect on me.
Hit me pretty hard.
A period of time when the economy of a country is bad.
Recession Not have any money.
Broke Had a strong, negative effect on me.
Hit me pretty hard.
The amount of money you owe to a person, bank, company, etc.
Debt A period of time when the economy of a country is bad.
Recession Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Trouble Can I trouble you for a moment?
I just need you to sign this for me.
Recession The recession is causing many businesses to close down.
Hit me pretty hard.
My divorce hit me pretty hard.
I'm so depressed.
My uncle just bought a new house and now he's in a lot of debt.
On top of all that.
My car was stolen yesterday and on top of all that, my house burned down.
Broke I spent all my money on a new TV so now I'm broke.
Recession The recession is causing many businesses to close down.
Hit me pretty hard.
Depression My divorce hit me pretty hard.
I'm so depressed.
On top of all that.
My car was stolen yesterday and on top of all that, my house burned down.