The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Loose-fitting undershorts with an elastic waistband.
Boxes.
Clothes that need to be washed.
Laundry.
Close-fitting legless underpants with an elastic waistband.
Briefs.
Very amusing.
Hilarious.
Underwear.
Undies.
Let's try that faster.
Clothes that need to be washed.
Loose-fitting undershorts with an elastic waistband.
Boxes.
Now, say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Laundry Okay, it's your time to do the laundry.
Laundry Give me all your dirty laundry, I'm doing the washing today.
Laundry She had nothing else to do, so she did the laundry.
Hilarious It was very hilarious when my friend fell over.
Hilarious She didn't think it was hilarious when her brother chucked a tomato at her.
Hilarious The comedy show I saw last week was hilarious, I want to see it again.
Undies I think I will wear blue undies today.
Undies I forgot to pack my undies for this trip, I'll have to buy some more.
Undies I can't find my undies, what will I do?
Briefs These briefs fit nicely against my body.
Briefs Briefs I prefer briefs over boxes because they don't fall down all the time like boxes tend to.
Briefs These briefs are too tight for my liking.
Boxes I like boxes because they are not too tight.
Boxes He looked in his drawer for some boxes to wear, but they were all dirty.
Boxes Boxes I heard a rumour that it is better for a man's health if he wears boxes.