Next, please.
May I help you, sir?
Hello.
Yes.
I'd like to open a bank account.
Certainly.
I can help you with that.
What type of account would you like to open, a checking or a saving account?
What features do they offer?
Well, if you just take a look here, see, with our checking account, you can have unlimited daily transactions for a small monthly fee.
And our savings account has a higher interest rate, but you must carry a minimum balance of $10,000.
I see.
Well, I think I'm more interested in a checking account.
I'd like to have easy access to my money.
All right, then.
With this checking account, you'll be issued a debit card and a checkbook.
Will you require overdraft protection?
There is an extra fee for that.
No, that won't be necessary.
In that case, I'll get you to fill out this paperwork.
I'll need your social insurance number and two pieces of government ID.
If you could just sign here and here and here, we'll be all set.
Would you like to make a deposit today?
Yes.
I'd like to deposit $1 billion.
One billion dollars!