The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Without doubt, of course.
Certainly.
Polite way to ask for someone's name.
May I take your name?
Tell someone.
Let someone know.
In a very short time.
Momentarily.
Is prepared to meet with you.
Be ready for you.
Show a person the way to a place.
Show someone too.
Phrase you use to show someone the direction to walk.
Right this way.
Secretary.
Administrative assistant.
Lobby.
The desk at the entrance of a building where the receptionist sits.
Front desk.
Receive and direct phone calls.
Field calls.
A system used to connect phone calls to many different phone lines within a building.
Witch board.
Let's try that faster.
Lobby.
Show a person the way to a place.
Show someone too.
Secretary.
Administrative assistant.
Without doubt, of course.
Certainly.
Receive and direct phone calls.
Field calls.
Is prepared to meet with you.
Be ready for you.
Phrase you use to show someone the direction to walk.
Right this way.
Tell someone.
Let someone know.
Polite way to ask for someone's name.
What's your name?
A system used to connect phone calls to many different phone lines within a building.
Witch board.
The desk at the entrance of a building where the receptionist sits.
Front desk.
In a very short time.
Momentarily.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
May I take your last name please?
May I take your phone number and call you back later?
May I take your full name and ID number please?
Momentarily.
Food will arrive momentarily.
Ladies and gentlemen, the movie will begin momentarily.
Momentarily.
The flight was delayed, but it will arrive momentarily.
Right this way.
I will show you where the bathroom is.
Right this way please.
Right this way.
The meeting room is right this way.
Right this way please.
The exit is straight ahead.
Watch your step here.
The floor is wet.
Please watch your step on the stairs.
Watch your step as you exit the train.