Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
originally calm or tranquil peaceful to form a mental image of imagine excite exciting Let's try that faster.
to form a mental image of imagine excite exciting high-tech modern originally originally a person who is travelling tourist causing wonder or astonishment amazing calm or tranquil peaceful Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
peaceful peaceful This town is really peaceful.
I wish I could live here.
peaceful I love it when my cat is nice and peaceful.
peaceful peaceful When my son goes to university, I'm sure this house will be peaceful.
modern This building is very modern.
There is even a wave pool.
modern Japan is a very modern city.
I wish my country was like that.
modern I don't like modern architecture.
It feels very cold and unwelcoming.
tourist I've lived here for ages, but I still feel like a tourist.
tourist I think having a map and being curious is what a tourist needs.
tourist Tourist groups are so annoying.
They never see the real side of a country.
originally Originally, we were going to go to America, but instead we went to Jamaica.
originally Originally, I'm from Ecuador, but now I'm a proud Australian.
originally I originally liked PlayStation, but now I play Nintendo.
imagine I imagine that other people think I'm fat.
imagine Can you imagine a world with no war?
imagine Who could have imagined that Obama would become president?