The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Out of bed and beginning to move around.
Up and about.
To keep time for a particular purpose.
Set aside.
Often.
Frequently.
Almost never.
Seldom.
Whenever.
At which time.
Once in a while.
From time to time.
Frequently.
Often times.
Cosmetics apply to improve your appearance.
Makeup.
A set of clothes.
Outfit.
Let's try that faster.
Often.
Frequently.
Out of bed and beginning to move around.
Up and about.
Cosmetics apply to improve your appearance.
Makeup.
Frequently.
Often times.
Almost never.
Seldom.
Once in a while.
From time to time.
A set of clothes.
Outfit.
To keep time for a particular purpose.
Set aside.
Whenever.
At which time.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Up and about.
Once in a while.
Once I started taking the medication, I was up and about in no time.
Up and about.
He's usually up and about by 7am.
Everyone else in the house is usually already up and about by the time I wake up.
Set aside.
I set aside 20 minutes every day to meditate.
You really need to set aside some time this week to work on your final project.
Set aside.
I set aside food for the next day's lunch and then ate the rest for dinner.
Frequently.
She frequently visits her grandfather on the weekends.
I frequently like to take drives in the countryside to get out of the city.
Frequently.
I eat the fish, but not frequently, maybe once or twice a month.
Seldom.
He seldom speaks about his family.
My roommate is always in her room.
She seldom comes out.
Seldom.
I seldom manage to see my family now that I'm living on the other side of the country.
At which time.
I walked in the room, at which time my dog leaped up and gave me a huge kiss.
Dessert was served after dinner, at which time a string quartet began to play.
At which time.
He found a dead end so he turned around and started to walk back down the alleyway, at which time several gang members turned the corner and stopped in front of him.