The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Get through by force.
Breakthrough.
The parts of a spaceship that are used for emitting bombs.
Blaster.
Finish.
End.
Settle.
Forever.
Once and for all.
Not wise.
Silly.
Unwise.
Be able to do.
Manage.
A device used for attracting one project to another from a distance.
Tractor beam.
The 92,458 meters per second.
Speed of light.
A robot that looks like a person.
Android.
Any one of the very large groups of stars that make up the universe.
Galaxy.
A group of celestial bodies, usually stars, that appear to form a pattern in the sky or appear visibly related to each other.
Constellation.
Is a unit of length equal to just under 31 trillion kilometers or about 3.26 light years?
Parsec.
The distance traveled in one year traveling at the speed of light.
Light year.
Let's try that faster.
The distance traveled in one year traveling at the speed of light.
Light year.
Forever.
Once and for all.
A group of celestial bodies, usually stars, that appear to form a pattern in the sky or appear visibly related to each other.
Constellation.
Finish.
End.
Settle.
Be able to do.
Manage.
Not wise.
Silly.
Unwise.
A device used for attracting one project to another from a distance.
Tractor beam.
Any one of the very large groups of stars that make up the universe.
Galaxy.
The 92,458 meters per second.
Speed of light.
Is a unit of length equal to just under 31 trillion kilometers or about 3.26 light years?
Parsec.
Get through by force.
Breakthrough.
The parts of a spaceship that are used for emitting bombs.
Blaster.
A robot that looks like a person.
Android.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Breakthrough.
After 15 minutes, the workers broke through the wall and rescued everyone from the fire.
He is such a good player.
He broke through the entire defense.
Breakthrough.
They are breaking through our impenetrable wall.
Run.
Don't make me have to ask you again.
Clean your room.
Don't make me fire you.
Finish those reports now.
Don't make me do something that I will regret later.
Once and for all.
I'm fed up with arguing about this.
Let's just settle this argument once and for all.
Once and for all.
He claims his photographs prove once and for all that UFOs do exist.
I told him once and for all that I don't want to be his girlfriend anymore.
They will no longer be in jail since they are innocent.
My dad told me he will no longer send me money each month.
What am I going to do?
I started taking Chinese classes, but after a month, I no longer assisted.
He somehow managed to get into the concert for free.
Charles doesn't have a job or money, but he somehow managed to go on vacation.
We somehow managed to convince the mayor to rename the streets.
Thanks for watching!