They are breaking through.
Search your blasters to full power.
Excellent job.
Search the ship.
She's gotta be in here somewhere.
Bring her to me.
Lord Hater, we have a survivor here.
Where is she?
Don't make me destroy you.
Tell me where she is.
Not so fast.
She will no longer be a prisoner.
It's time you and I settled this once and for all.
You are unwise to think you can defeat me.
You know nothing of the power of the obscure side.
We will stop you.
Lord Hater, we have an unidentified spacecraft taking off from the rear dock.
They somehow managed to escape our tractor beam.
After them.
They're accelerating towards the speed of light.
We lost them, sir.