The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Acquire bills or debts.
Run up.
Increase the intensity of a device.
Turn up.
Very cold.
Chilly.
Become infected with a cold.
Catch a cold.
Thankful.
Grateful.
Let's try that faster.
Acquire bills or debts.
Run up.
Increase the intensity of a device.
Churn up.
Thankful.
Grateful.
Become infected with a cold.
Catch a cold.
Very cold.
Chilly.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Run up.
He ran up a very expensive tab at the local bar.
The new heating system they installed ran up their electric bill.
Run up.
They were running up huge bills with his new spending habits.
Turn up.
Honey, could you please turn up the heat?
It's freezing in here.
Turn up.
I need to turn up the heat or I'll freeze.
I wish I could turn up the heat, but I don't have any control in this hotel room.
Chilly.
It's starting to get a little chilly in here.
He said that it was so chilly that he had to put two sweaters on.
Chilly.
It is very chilly in this room.
Catch a cold.
You will catch a cold if you don't put a sweater on.
My friend Amy caught the flu and had to stay home for a week.
Catch a cold.
He caught a cold last week and now we all have it too.
Grateful.
I am so grateful that the police came just in time.
He was so grateful that he could finally see his daughter again.
Grateful.
She was very grateful to have such wonderful friends.