The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To ignore someone or not appear to an appointment.
Blow someone off.
Difficult in an enjoyable way.
Challenging.
Defeat.
Beat.
Addicted.
Hooked.
Use more than necessary.
Waste.
Let's try that faster.
To ignore someone or not appear to an appointment.
Blow someone off.
Defeat.
Beat.
Difficult in an enjoyable way.
Challenging.
Use more than necessary.
Waste.
Addicted.
Hooked.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Blow someone off.
I can't believe she blew me off again.
I swear if you blow me off again, I won't talk to you again.
Blow someone off.
You can't let him blow me off like that.
Challenging.
I like games that are challenging.
I was expecting something a little bit more challenging.
Challenging.
Beat.
Everyone says this career is so challenging, but it hasn't been for me so far.
Two guys showed up out of nowhere and started beating me up.
Beat.
Try and beat me if you can.
I want to beat that guy up so hard.
Hooked.
He got really hooked on that game.
She seems to be really hooked on you.
Hooked.
Some drugs are so strong that you can't avoid getting hooked on.
Waste.
I have wasted enough time by doing nothing.
I don't want to waste my time doing something I don't enjoy.
Waste.
He wasted so much time on a project that was rejected.