EnglishPod.com Mark, where have you been?
I've been calling you all morning.
I've been playing computer games.
What?
So you blew me off yesterday and today over a stupid video game.
What game is so important that you have no time for me anymore?
What are you playing?
It's called Counter Strike.
It's a first person shooter game.
It's awesome!
It's a multiplayer game where you can go online and compete against players from all over the world.
You've been wasting your time on this?
I can't believe it.
It doesn't even look fun or challenging.
My laptop is on my bed.
If you think it's so easy, then get online and try to beat me.
Fine.
Damn it!
How are you killing me with a single shot?
It's not fair!
I don't want to play anymore.
Let's go get something to eat.
Can you bring me something?
I'm totally hooked on this game.