The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The increase of the world's temperature due to pollution.
Global warming.
The change in the world's temperature and weather patterns.
Climate change.
The act of making others believe something false.
Deception.
Fuel made with dead animals or plants, such as oil, gas, natural gas.
Fossil fuel.
Of or relating to planets.
Planetary.
The action of cutting down forests.
Deforestation.
Everything that exists in a certain environment.
Ecosystem.
The act of producing gas.
Emission.
The thick layer of ice or snow on the poles.
Polar ice cap.
Support a point of view.
Endorse.
Be led to make believe something not true.
Mislead.
A polite way to show you do not agree with someone.
Beg to differ.
Highlight.
Emphasize.
Give out.
Announce the public.
Put forth.
So true that does not need to be discussed anymore.
Indisputable.
Influence someone's ideas for your own benefit.
Manipulate.
Saying something so as to frighten people.
Scaremongering.
A gas that increases the global temperature.
Greenhouse gases.
Type of animal in danger of dying out.
Endangered species.
To say that you do not deny something's true.
Concede.
With total power.
Autocratic.
Result or outcome.
End.
Deceiving, dishonest.
Duplicitous.
Being illegally bribed or paid by someone.
In the pocket of.
Used to show the name is not really suitable.
So-called.
Let's try that faster.
The act of making others believe something false.
Deception.
Type of animal in danger of dying out.
Endangered species.
So true that does not need to be discussed anymore.
Indisputable.
Result or outcome.
End.
The thick layer of ice or snow on the poles.
Polar ice cap.
With total power.
Autocratic.
The action of cutting down forests.
Deforestation.
The act of producing gas.
Emission.
Be led to make believe something not true.
Mislead.
Saying something so as to frighten people.
Scaremongering.
Give out.
Announce the public.
Put forth.
The change in the world's temperature and weather patterns.
Climate change.
Highlight.
Emphasize.
The increase of the world's temperature due to pollution.
Global warming.
Of or relating to planets.
Planetary.
Support a point of view.
Endorse.
Used to show the name is not really suitable.
So-called.
A gas that increases the global temperature.
Greenhouse gases.
To say that you do not deny something's true.
Concede.
A polite way to show you do not agree with someone.
Beg to differ.
Influence someone's ideas for your own benefit.
Manipulate.
Everything that exists in a certain environment.
Ecosystem.
Fuel made with dead animals or plants such as oil, gas, natural gas.
Fossil fuel.
Being illegally bribed or paid by someone.
In the pocket of.
Deceiving, dishonest.
Duplicitous.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Beg to differ.
You said money is the most important thing in life.
But I beg to differ.
In my opinion the best things in life are free.
Beg to differ.
Most people believe that the internet is giving us greater freedom of expression.
I beg to differ.
Beg to differ.
I would beg to differ with the idea that we need to downsize.
If we just reorganize our system of communication we could optimize efficiency.
I know that you don't believe in raising taxes.
But at the very least you have to admit that this is the best way for our government to raise money.
If we're not going to learn from our mistakes, at the very least, let's not repeat them.
Even if you can't say the whole time, at the very least show up at the party and say hi.
In the pocket of.
You know Judge Smith is in the pocket of the criminals because he always declares them innocent.
Car manufacturers are in the pockets of the big oil producers.
That's why they haven't developed electric cars yet.
In the pocket of.
I think the Senator is in the pocket of the tobacco industry.
He keeps promoting their interests.
So called.
My so called friends are spreading rumors about me.
This so called cost savings plan is actually costing us more money.
So called.
The so called disaster actually opened up a lot of opportunities for us.
You're so full of it.
You've never been to the moon.
Don't believe a word Tom says.
He's full of it.
I think this argument is full of it.
There's no way that the global temperature is getting cooler.