The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Sudden strong movement of air, especially that causes a plane to move up and down in the air.
turbulence Having or causing sudden violent movements.
Rough Small area.
Patch Having sudden up and down movements.
Bumpy Do up, connect one part with another.
Fasten Suitcase and luggage that travels inside the plane with the passengers.
Cabin baggage Put something in a place where it is safe but can be accessed easily.
Though Stop something for a short time.
Suspend Refrain A room with a sink and a toilet, chiefly on an airplane or train.
Lavatory Luggage Suitcases or bags that travel inside the plane with you.
Cabin baggage Place above the seat in an airplane where you can store luggage.
Overhead bin A suitcase that you bring onto the plane.
Carry-on A table that folds down from the seat in front of you on an airplane.
Table tray A piece of clothing that you wear to stay floating in the water.
Life jacket A mask worn over your mouth and nose so you can breathe.
Oxygen mask Let's try that faster.
Having sudden up and down movements.
Bumpy Having or causing sudden violent movements.
Do up, connect one part with another.
Fasten Suitcase and luggage that travels inside the plane with the passengers.
Cabin baggage Refrain Stop something for a short time.
Suspend A table that folds down from the seat in front of you on an airplane.
Table tray Luggage suitcases or bags that travel inside the plane with you.
Cabin baggage Sudden strong movement of air especially that causes a plane to move up and down in the air.
Place above the seat in an airplane where you can store luggage.
Overhead bin A suitcase that you bring onto the plane.
Carry-on A room with a sink and a toilet chiefly on an airplane or train.
Lavatory Put something in a place where it is safe but can be accessed easily.
Though A mask worn over your mouth and nose so you can breathe.
Oxygen mask A piece of clothing that you wear to stay floating in the water.
Life jacket Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Turbulence There was a lot of turbulence on the flight.
Turbulence I don't think there will be any turbulence on this flight.
We'll have a nice trip.
Turbulence We hit some turbulence when we were flying over the Atlantic.
Though You stole this under your desk for me?
Though You didn't stole your bags, you put them somewhere.
Though I'll store your computer under my seat, okay?
Patch We hit a patch of turbulence.
Patch There were some icy patches on the road.
Patch We drove through some foggy patches on the way here.
Bumpy It was a bit of a bumpy ride because the roads were terrible.
Bumpy We might have a bumpy ride because there is a lot of turbulence.
Bumpy It was a long and bumpy ride through the desert.
Refrain Please refrain from smoking until you have left the building.
Refrain I refrained from telling her what I really thought of her.
Refrain Please refrain from using your mobile phone in the hospital.