EnglishPod.com And the next thing you know, we're running towards the...
Oh, did you feel that?
Yeah, don't worry about it.
We're just going through a bit of turbulence.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your captain speaking.
It looks like we've hit a patch of rough air, so we're going to have a bit of a bumpy ride for the next several minutes.
This is why I hate flying!
At this time, I'd like to remind all of our passengers to fasten their seatbelts and remain seated until the Fasten Seatbelt sign is turned off.
Please ensure that all cabin baggage is carefully stowed under the seat in front of you.
I'll be back to update you in a minute.
Did you hear that?
Oh my God!
Brent!
Don't worry about it.
This is totally normal.
It happens all the...
Ladies and gentlemen, this is your captain again.
We've got quite a large patch of rough air ahead of us, and so, for your safety, we will be suspending in-flight service.
I would ask all the in-flight crew to return to their seats at this time.
I would also ask that all our passengers refrain from using the lavatory until the seatbelt sign has been switched off.
We can expect...
Thanks for watching!