The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Appear, come to a place.
Show up.
Crazy, not normal.
Insane.
Follow and watch a person, usually dangerous.
Stalk.
Crazy person.
Nut job.
Angry, excited, or upset about something.
Get worked up.
With intention.
On purpose.
Phrase used to show you always do something.
Not a day goes by.
A close friend who has a deep understanding of you.
Soul mate.
Despite of anything may happen.
No matter what.
Deal with something that is difficult.
Tackle.
Severe mental illness, the state of being crazy.
Insanity.
To annoy or bother someone many times.
Harass.
Say that you will do something to hurt or cause harm to a person.
Threaten.
Person who commits a crime.
Perpetrator.
A person who follows someone for a long period of time in a way that is dangerous.
Stalker.
Let's try that faster.
Crazy person.
Nut job.
Crazy, not normal.
Insane.
Say that you will do something to hurt or cause harm to a person.
Threaten.
Appear, come to a place.
Show up.
Despite of anything may happen.
No matter what.
To annoy or bother someone many times.
Harass.
With intention.
On purpose.
Follow and watch a person, usually dangerous.
Stalk.
A close friend who has a deep understanding of you.
Soulmate.
Phrase used to show you always do something.
Not a day goes by.
Person who commits a crime.
Perpetrator.
A person who follows someone for a long period of time in a way that is dangerous.
Stalker.
Severe mental illness, the state of being crazy.
Insanity.
Angry, excited, or upset about something.
Get worked up.
Deal with something that is difficult.
Tackle.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Show up.
We were waiting for you like an hour and you never showed up.
I didn't invite him to the party.
He just simply showed up uninvited.
Show up.
After months of being lost, my dog finally showed up.
Don't worry about the bill.
I'll take care of it.
I'm glad we hired a wedding planner.
She is taking care of everything.
I hired a lawyer that will take care of everything for the divorce process.
Get worked up.
It's not a problem.
You are getting all worked up for no reason.
Get worked up.
Don't get worked up.
I will cook dinner and have it ready by the time your boss arrives.
Get worked up.
Pete gets easily worked up over small problems at work.
No matter what.
You can always tell me anything, no matter what it is.
No matter what, I have to pay the phone bill today.
No matter what.
My dad told me I have to go to college, no matter what.
Tackle.
The company has a very big problem that we must tackle in order to survive.
I don't know how you do it, tackling all these problems at once.
Tackle.
In life, there are many obstacles that we must tackle in order to be successful.