Thank God you showed up when you did.
He's insane.
Do you think we should call the police?
Don't worry about it.
I'll call my friend and have him take care of it.
I can't believe he was stalking you all these years.
What a nutjob.
I know.
Well, he said I'm not pregnant.
I'm sorry if I got you all worked up over nothing.
I want you to know that I didn't do it on purpose.
Don't apologize.
From the moment I met you, not a day has gone by when I haven't thought of you.
And now that I'm with you again, I'm just scared, Veronica.
The closer I get to you, the worse it gets.
The thought of not being with you, I mean, I just can't handle it.
We were made for each other, Veronica.
You're my everything, my soulmate.
What can I do?
Just hold me.
I'll always be here for you, no matter what.
And together, we can tackle whatever life throws at us.
I believe in us, Steven.
I'm so happy to hear that.
I know we belong together.
I love you so much.