EnglishPod.com Okay, so if we could dim the lights, Jonathan, we can kick off with the first TV advert.
Please note that we are still in the early days with this advert, so it might seem a bit rough around the edges.
Okay, so I just need to click this and the advert should pop up on the screen.
Hmm, sorry about this.
Bear with me a second.
There seems to be a problem with the projector.
Let me see.
Jonathan, could you lend a hand a second?
It looks like the projector is not recognizing the computer.
Let me check the connection a second.
Well, the connection seems okay and the computer is running normally.
Hmm.
Okay, sorry guys.
Obviously a problem with the system.
Let's just reboot and start over.
Let's see if this resolves the issue.
Right, let's try again.
No, still nothing, Michael.
There might be a technical issue with the projector.
I think maybe the projector has overheated.
We might need to cool it down for 10 minutes and start again.
I'll call IT support to come over right now.
Okay, guys.
Unfortunately, technical problems do crop up from time to time, don't they?
But it's not a huge problem.
In the meantime, while the IT guys get to work on that, I can talk a little bit more about the advertising concept and what we are looking to achieve overall with this campaign.