The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Too expensive, can't afford it.
Out of my price range.
Agreement to buy something.
Deal.
Not common, unique.
Exclusive.
A good deal, a cheap price.
Bargain.
Look in many stores and try and find the best price.
Shop around.
A lowering of the price of something.
Discount.
Expensive.
Pricey.
An opportunity to buy something at a low price.
Offer.
Money in the form of coins and bills.
Cash.
Card that is used to buy things and pay at a later time.
Credit card.
A special discount or offer on goods and services.
Promotion.
To discuss and fight for a better price.
Negotiate.
A free item that is usually given to promote a product.
Freebie.
Let's try that faster.
A lowering of the price of something.
Discount.
A good deal, a cheap price.
Bargain.
A free item that is usually given to promote a product.
Freebie.
Too expensive, can't afford it.
Out of my price range.
To discuss and fight for a better price.
Negotiate.
Card that is used to buy things and pay at a later time.
Credit card.
Money in the form of coins and bills.
Cash.
A special discount or offer on goods and services.
Promotion.
Agreement to buy something.
Deal.
An opportunity to buy something at a low price.
Offer.
Look in many stores and try and find the best price.
Shop around.
Expensive.
Pricey.
Not common.
Unique.
Exclusive.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Bargain.
I got this shirt for half price.
What a bargain.
Bargain.
Let's go shopping.
Everything is on sale and I'm sure we'll find some great bargains.
Bargain.
If you look around, you'll find some great bargains.
Shop around.
I'm not sure about it yet.
I'm going to shop around for a while.
Shop around.
Let's shop around and see if we can find it cheaper in another store.
I was shopping around and I found this computer on sale.
Pricey.
This restaurant is too pricey for me.
Can we go somewhere else?
Pricey.
This phone is a little pricey, but it is a really good phone.
I can't afford that trip.
It's just too pricey.
Out of my price range.
No, that computer is out of my price range.
Do you have something cheaper?
Out of my price range.
Honey, you know this restaurant is out of my price range.
We can't afford to buy a house in this neighborhood.
It's out of our price range.
This house is a little bit more than we wanted to spend.
We can't afford that car.
It's more than we wanted to spend.
$100 is more than I wanted to spend.