EnglishPod.com I can't believe we're here!
Carnival in Rio!
Seriously, this is like a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Can you believe it?
We're here at the biggest party in the world!
I know!
We're so lucky we found tickets for the samba drum.
Good thing we found that ticket scalper.
Look!
It's starting!
Wow, this is amazing!
Look at how many dancers there are!
Oh my gosh, the costumes are so colorful!
This is so cool!
It says here that the school that is dancing now is one of the oldest and most prestigious samba schools in Rio.
No kidding!
Look at them!
They're amazing!
Look at that girl on top of that float!
She must be the Carnival Queen!
Move over there so I can get a picture of you.
Okay!
Hurry up!
Take the picture!
Oh, really?
No, I can't.
Really, I don't know how to dance.
Honey, I'll see you later!
Patrick, don't just leave me here!