The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Something that happens very rarely, not common.
Once in a lifetime.
Person that buys and resells tickets at a higher price.
Ticket scalper.
Being respected and admired for being successful or important.
Prestigious.
A vehicle with a platform used to carry an exhibit in a parade.
Float.
It is good that something happened.
Good thing.
A large structure where sport events are held.
A special time or event when people gather to celebrate something.
The capital of Brazil.
Take a risk.
Do something that you would not normally do.
Take a chance.
Leave someone on purpose.
Informal.
Ditch.
Let's try that faster.
Take a risk.
Do something that you would not normally do.
Take a chance.
Something that happens very rarely, not common.
Once in a lifetime.
Being respected and admired for being successful or important.
Prestigious.
A vehicle with a platform used to carry an exhibit in a parade.
Float.
A special time or event when people gather to celebrate something.
Festival.
A large structure where sport events are held.
Batium.
The capital of Brazil.
Brasilia.
Leave someone on purpose.
Informal.
Ditch.
Person that buys and resells tickets at a higher price.
Ticket scalper.
It is good that something happened.
Good thing.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Once in a lifetime.
If you have a once in a lifetime opportunity to make this trip, you should really go.
Swimming with the sharks and dolphins was a once in a lifetime experience.
Once in a lifetime.
Michael Jackson's concert in Budapest was a once in a lifetime event.
Good thing.
Good thing I studied for my exam.
It was really hard.
Good thing.
It's a good thing I brought my umbrella.
It rained the whole day.
Good thing.
It's a good thing that I bought my house before the prices went up.
Ticket scalper.
Police arrived and arrested three ticket scalpers outside of the stadium.
The concert was sold out, but I was able to buy some tickets from a ticket scalper.
Ticket scalper.
I hate ticket scalpers.
They always resell tickets at a much higher price.
Prestigious.
Harvard University is one of the most prestigious schools in North America.
The Academy Award is the most prestigious prize an actor can get in the film industry.
Prestigious.
He worked really hard and now he is a very prestigious heart surgeon.
Tony, don't just leave your toys on the ground.
Don't just buy the first thing that you see.
Look around first.
Don't just cross the street without looking.
It's dangerous.