EnglishPod.com I'm glad you could find time to meet with me, Mr.
Johnson.
I can't think of a nicer environment for our meeting today.
The ambience here is lovely.
No problem.
If possible, I always combine business with pleasure.
Now let's hear more about these chocolates you're offering.
Well, as you know, I have recently become the sole distributor for Grengers Gourmet Bon Bons here in the United States.
They're a new manufacturer and are looking to break into the luxury market.
Naturally, your restaurant sprang into my mind immediately.
I think your brand exemplifies many of the same traits as Grengers, and serving these chocolates would really add to your reputation for providing elegant, luxurious, first-class dining.
Hmm, sounds interesting.
Gourmet chocolates.
Where are they produced?
Belgium?
Actually, the factory is located in Scotland.
Really?
I didn't think they were known for their luxury chocolate production.
That's what makes this such a fantastic opportunity.
The government is 100 percent supportive of creating new export markets and has guaranteed a low tariff for all wholesale orders of over 1,000 units.
They've also reduced the red tape involved at customs as well.
Here, I brought these especially for you.
Try one.
Oh, thanks.
Hmm.
Creamy texture.
Very smooth.
Unique, aren't they?
I bet you've never tasted anything like it.
Quality is assured as I personally visit the factory to make sure no one's cutting corners with the ingredients.
Only the crème de la crème make it through inspection.
Yes, very interesting flavors.
Slightly spicy.
Hmm, very unique, that's for sure.
Exactly what are the ingredients?
I have it on highest authority that this traditional secret recipe has been handed down in the granger family for generations.
I'm sure you can keep a secret.
Buttermilk, cacao beans, sugar, and haggis.
Haggis?
What's haggis?
It's a traditional Scottish delicacy.
You take sheep's liver, heart, and lung, and stuff it inside the sheep's stomach.
I'll get back to you.
Mr.
Johnson?
Johnson!