The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A quality that makes someone effective or useful.
Strengths Giving attention and effort to a specific task.
Focus Worked hard.
Hardworking Show the truth by some evidence.
Prove Group of people who work together to achieve a common goal.
Team Person taking part in a sporting event.
Player Good Positive Have a lot of interest in or passion for a particular Passionate Enthusiam that one has been doing things.
Passion Let's try that faster.
Show the truth by some evidence.
Prove Giving attention and effort to a specific task.
Focus Group of people who work together to achieve a common goal.
Team Enthusiam that one has been doing things.
Passion Have a lot of interest in or passion for a particular Passionate Person taking part in a sporting event.
Player A quality that makes someone effective or useful.
Strengths Worked hard.
Hardworking Good Positive Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Strengths Many companies shifted strategies to focus more on their core strengths.
Strengths Our company is making great progress.
We're moving from strength to strength.
Strengths Bill's greatest strength is his ability to solve problems.
Focus Everyone, please.
I need you all to focus on the work at hand.
Focus Don't distract Lillian.
She's really focused on getting the report finished by don't.
Focus Keep your eyes focused on my finger as I move it.
Hardworking John makes up for his lack of experience by being hardworking.
Hardworking The HR department is looking for two hardworking engineers.
Hardworking Ants are extremely hardworking insects.
Team Some basketball stars are really Team We need someone who can both work independently and be a good team player.
Team I'm just not sure Ryan has the ability to work as a team player.
Passionate Jane is really passionate about human rights issues.
Passionate How could anyone be passionate about accounting?
Passionate Their relationship was passionate, but not long lasting.