EnglishPod.com Okay, Rebecca, now you've given me a good idea of your work and academic background, but what about you as a person?
How would you describe your key strengths?
Well, Mr.
Parsons, as I mentioned before, I'm someone who needs new challenges.
I'm really focused and hardworking.
I think my academic results prove this.
Yes, true, but how about other personal qualities?
Well, I believe I'm a good team player, but I can also work well independently.
I'm very enthusiastic and, well, I hope my colleagues would agree.
I'm fun to work with.
What would you say is your most positive quality?
Hmm, that's a tough question, but I would have to say my passion.
I'm really passionate about journalism and passionate about my career.