EnglishPod.com This is such a nice restaurant.
I feel so classy.
Yeah, it's a little bit pricey, but they serve the best seafood in town.
May I take your order?
Yes, I would like some marinated grilled shrimp for starters, and I'll also have the lobster.
Excellent choice, sir.
And for you, madame?
I would like the baked oysters and the seafood platter.
Very good, madame.
That seafood platter sounds good.
Excuse me, what does the platter have?
It's a great combination of clams, scallops, mussels, calamari, and filet of salmon and tuna.
It comes with a side of butter sauce and french fries.
That sounds great.
Cancel the lobster and give me one of the same, please.
Very well, sir.
Anything to drink?
Can we get a bottle of your house-wiped wine, please?
Superb choice.
I will be back shortly with the wine.