EnglishPod.com Hello sir, may I help you?
Yes, I would like some information for requesting a loan.
Very well.
Here are the general terms of our loan policies.
We pride ourselves in having the lowest interest rate in the country for personal loans.
I see.
So let me get this straight.
If I borrow, let's say, $10,000, how much will I have to pay each month?
It depends on how long you take to pay it back.
If we lend you $10,000 at an annual interest rate of 10% for 48 months, you would have to pay each month a portion of the loan, which is called the principal, and another small portion of the annual interest rate.
This, of course, is considering that you don't default on a payment.
It sounds good, but there's just one problem.
I have a terrible credit score.
That is a very serious problem, you see.
The bank must assess your personal information, past loans, assets, and any other relevant information, such as your credit score, in order to approve your loan.
You know what?
I don't really need the money.
Thanks anyways.