The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Percentage of the money paid to you by the bank.
Interest rate.
Common rules listed in an agreement.
General terms.
Calculate.
Credit score.
Let's try that faster.
Measure.
Calculate.
Common rules listed in an agreement.
General terms.
Credit score.
Percentage of the money paid to you by the bank.
Interest rate.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Calculate.
I have calculated the interest rate and things are starting to look better.
Give me a moment to calculate your salary for this month.
Calculate.
Someone at work miscalculated my salary and now I have to wait for another month to get paid.
Credit score.
I have a perfect credit score.
There is no way I'm not getting this loan.
Credit score.
I forgot to pay my credit card bill and now my credit score is compromised.
I really hope this doesn't ruin my credit score.
Interest rate.
This interest rate is insane.
I wish I could get a loan with a lower interest rate.
Interest rate.
The bank's interest rate is lower than it used to be last month.
General terms.
I can help you understand this topic in general terms.
I'm not so familiar with the details.
General terms.
In general terms, your behavior must improve or else we will have to let you go.
He explained some complicated science, but only in general terms.
I forgot to read the fine print and now I'm in trouble.
Please make sure you read the fine print before you sign any document.
I just read something in the fine print.
I don't completely understand.
Can you explain?