EnglishPod.com I have made up my mind.
I'm getting a tattoo.
Really?
Are you sure?
Yeah, why not?
They're trendy and look great.
I want to get a dragon on my arm or maybe a tiger on my back.
Yeah, but it's something that you'll have forever.
They use indelible ink that can only be removed with laser treatment.
On top of all of that, I've heard it hurts a lot.
Really?
Of course!
They use this machine with a needle that pokes your skin and inserts the ink.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I thought they just painted on your skin or something.
I think you should reconsider and do some more research about tattoos.
Also, find out where the nearest tattoo parlor is and make sure that you use sterilized needles and the place is hygienic.
Maybe I should just get a tongue piercing.
Ew!