EnglishPod.com Ah, Michelle.
Hi.
I was hoping to see you.
How have you been?
How's the family?
Oh, hello, Mr.
Campbell.
I'm fine and Jack's doing well.
How are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
I got your report this morning.
Thanks for that.
Are you joining the conference today?
Yes, I'm leaving at 4 p.m.
Good, well we can discuss this more then.
But I think the figures are looking very good for this quarter.
Yes, me too.
I'm planning to discuss the advertising budget at the conference.
I don't think we should continue with the TV advertising.
No, me neither.
It's far too expensive.
Well, let's discuss this more at the conference.
Maybe we can share a taxi there?
Yes, sure.