Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod, my name is Marco.
My name is Catherine and we've got another lesson in our series about Smalltalk today.
That's right, today we are at the office again and we're going to be talking very briefly about something, a business meeting that we're going to have soon.
That's right, so let's check out our dialogue, we'll be back in a moment.
Ah Michelle, hi, I was hoping to see you, how have you been, how's the family?
Oh hello Mr.
Campbell, I'm fine and Jack's doing well, how are you?
I'm fine thanks, I got your report this morning, thanks for that, are you joining the conference today?
Yes, I'm leaving at 4pm.
Good, well we can discuss this more then, but I think the figures are looking very good for this quarter.
Yes, me too.
I'm planning to discuss the advertising budget at the conference, I don't think we should continue with the TV advertising.
No, me neither, it's far too expensive.
Well let's discuss this more at the conference, maybe we can share a taxi there?
Yes, sure.
Alright we're back so now let's take a look at some vocab on Language Takeaway.
Language Takeaway.
Today in Language Takeaway we have a number of phrases and words about business, the first one we have is are you joining the conference today?
That's right, so we're going to go to a conference actually, which is a little bit different than a meeting.
That's right, a meeting is something you normally do with people at your own company, but a conference is when people from many different companies meet.
That's right, and also I think you don't really have too much input at a conference, you mostly listen to other people speak about a topic or a subject.
That's right, and I think these are normally held in conference centers or hotels, you have a nice lunch, so they're pretty big deals.
That's right.
Alright so it's more of a formal business conference that we're going to, and well they're actually going to discuss different aspects of the company as well, especially the figures.
Alright so in the context of business the word figure actually means number, so we can say the sales numbers for this year are a kind of figure.
That's right, so we're talking about money basically when we're talking about numbers.
That's right, so when the figures look good it means that our income, our revenue, this looks good.
That's right, and when we usually talk about income or revenue we usually have to separate it into time, and here in the dialogue we're talking about a quarter.
Alright so quarter, QU, quarter, is a period of time, very common in business, that is a quarter of the year, so three months.
Three months, that's right.
January, February, March, April, May, June, and so on.
That's right, so you have four quarters, and that's actually why you call it a quarter because it's one fourth.
So we can say the figures for the first quarter were very good, but unfortunately the figures for the second quarter were very bad.
That's right, and actually another similar way that you use quarter is the 25 cent coin, it's called a quarter because it's a quarter of a dollar.
That's right, and if you're in America you know that it has an eagle, a bird on one side of it.
That's right, alright so we are taking a look at the figures for the quarter, and they're saying well it's not looking too good because we need to talk about the advertising budget.
Alright so this is something that you think is very important, it's budget, it's how much money you have to spend on something, and in this case you're spending it on advertising, so this is ads that you make.
That's right, so as you said a budget is the amount of money that you have available to spend on something, and on this occasion we're talking about advertising.
Now you can have a budget for different things right?
You could have a marketing budget.
So the money you have for marketing.
You could have a personnel budget, which is the money you would set aside for people.
So how much you pay your employees.
Right so you can pretty much mix up many different nouns with budget, even you can have a budget for your home, how much you spend at home.
That's right, so many people have this for their families, they say this month I will spend $100 on shopping and $200 on shoes.
So it's like a family budget you would call it.
That's right.
Okay so that's all the words we have for you on Language Takeaway, let's review everything quickly and we'll be back in a bit with Fluency Builder.
Well I'm fine and Jack's doing well.
How are you?
I'm fine thanks.
I got your report this morning.
Thanks for that.
Are you joining the conference today?
Yes I'm leaving at 4pm.
Good well we can discuss this more then.
But I think the figures are looking very good for this quarter.
Yes me too.
I'm planning to discuss the advertising budget at the conference.
I don't think we should continue with the TV advertising.
No me neither, it's far too expensive.
Well let's discuss this more at the conference.
Maybe we can share a taxi there?
Yes sir.
Alright in today's Fluency Builder we have a number of phrases you could use in a small talk situation.
The first one's a question.
How's the family?
Now it's how apostrophe s the family right so how is the family would be the extended way of saying it.
That's right but this is a short way to say it.
It's very common and you normally say this with people who are a little bit older, people who have kids.
So I haven't seen you in a long time Marco and I know you have some kids and I can say how's the family?
How's the family that's right and it's actually it may seem strange the way that this sentence is made but it's very very much similar to how are you.
You have how to be and you in the subject.
That's right and this is a very polite way to say hi, how are you, how is your family?
How is the wife?
How's the wife?
And she said well you know what everything is great I'm fine and Jack's I guess that that's her husband is doing well.
Jack is doing well so doing well thanks this means good okay but you know when we say when we say the answer to this question how are you I'm well that's that's the correct answer I'm good is not correct.
Right so if somebody says how are you you can say I'm well or you can say I'm doing well that's a positive answer things are going well you could say not so well that's not good things are happening very good and it's very important to point out the difference as Catherine said you don't you don't you shouldn't use good I'm doing good or I'm good yeah no it's incorrect because good is an adjective and we're looking for an adverb here that's right well that's right all right and to finish things off Mr.
Campbell and Michelle were headed headed the same way so they decided to share a taxi that's right so to share a taxi means two people or three people will pay for one taxi together so maybe Marco I see you on the street and I know that you have to go to a conference I'm going to the same conference let's share a taxi it will cost less that's right so you will share the cost between all the people in the cab now there's another way of saying it as well more common I think in the in the United States that's right we say split a taxi let's split a cab the split a cab now remember that it's a taxi cab so sometimes people just don't say taxi they say a cab let's split a cab let's share a cab that's right cab taxi both are okay all right very good good stuff let's listen to everything one last time ah Michelle hi I was hoping to see you how have you been how's the family oh hello mr.
Campbell I'm fine and Jack's doing well how are you I'm fine thanks I got your report this morning thanks for that are you joining the conference today yes I'm leaving at 4 p.m.