The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A formal meeting where many people talk about ideas.
Conference A written document that provides information about something.
Report Talk about Discuss One fourth of the calendar or fiscal year Quarter Money available to spend Budget To announce or praise in order to raise awareness in a product or service Advertise Let's try that faster.
Talk about Discuss A written document that provides information about something.
Report A formal meeting where many people talk about ideas.
Conference One fourth of the calendar or fiscal year Quarter Money available to spend Budget To announce or praise in order to raise awareness in a product or service Advertise Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Conference I need to go to a big conference this weekend.
I'm a little nervous.
Conference My boss at the company will pay for all the expenses at the conference.
Conference The only thing I like about conferences is all the free stuff I get.
Discuss Please come into my office.
I have something to discuss with you.
Discuss We need to discuss this idea.
Over a glass of wine.
Discuss I think I should discuss the results of my recent maths exam with my dad.
Budget Due to increased costs our budget this year will be smaller.
Budget I can't operate on this budget.
I'm going to ask the boss for a bigger one.
Budget With this new budget we can afford to buy those new computers for everyone.
Report Could you please hand in the report by this afternoon please.
Report The report on the company's financial health does not look good.
Report I have so much work today that I couldn't finish the report on company sales.
Quarter This quarter I hope we can reach the sales target.
Quarter The last quarter was very bad for our firm.
We will have to cut costs.
Quarter Quarter We expect this quarter to see an increase in demand for our product.