The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Incredible Amazing Unbelievable Calm down Relax Very long Be a mile long It's impossible There's no way Move in front of someone waiting in line Cut in line Let's try that faster Calm down Relax Incredible Amazing Unbelievable Calm down Relax Very long Be a mile long Calm down Relax Move in front of someone waiting in line Cut in line Calm down Relax Incredible Amazing Unbelievable Calm down Relax Move in front of someone waiting in line Cut in line Calm down Relax Now say the word and hear it in a sentence Unbelievable It's unbelievable how fast the city is changing There's no way There's no way I can have these reports finished today Be a mile long This beach is so beautiful.
It must be a mile long.
Relax I like to relax by the beach.
Cut in line Excuse me.
I'm really late.
Can I cut in line, please?
Unbelievable It's unbelievable how fast the city is changing There's no way There's no way I can have these reports finished today Relax I like to relax by the beach Cut in line Excuse me.
I'm really late.
Can I cut in line, please?
Thanks for watching!