So, what are you doing for Thanksgiving?
Not much, really.
It's more of an American tradition, so back home we don't really celebrate it.
In fact, I'm not even sure of what exactly is being celebrated.
Well, you know, it's a time to get together with all of your family and be thankful for everything.
Yeah, but how did this holiday come to be?
Well, the first settlers of Massachusetts arrived there because of religious persecution from England and King James.
Once in the New World, they befriended a native named Squanto who taught them how to harvest food from the area such as corn.
And then what happened?
Well, they had enough harvest for the next winter, and in celebration they decided to have a big feast with the natives, giving thanks to the land and everyone for their food, health, and new lives.
Interesting.
I am amazed how big and delicious Thanksgiving dinners are.
Come to my house for Thanksgiving.
We're having turkey, pumpkin pie, mashed potatoes with gravy, and lots of stuffing.
Count me in!