EnglishPod.com Sorry to bother you, sir, but I have some bad news.
What is it?
Well, the stock market just took a huge plunge and we've lost a lot of money.
What do you mean?
What happened?
There are many factors that weigh in, but Nasdaq is down 200 points.
The Dow Jones indicator also suffered.
Our portfolio is worth half of what it was worth one week ago.
How is this possible?
You are supposed to be talking to our stockbrokers and making sure that our securities and investments are safe and making a profitable return.
I know, sir.
We didn't expect a bull market to become a bear market all of a sudden.
On the other hand, you still have some high-yield trash bonds and government bonds that will give us enough liquidity to cut our losses and reinvest in emerging markets.
We could potentially make this tragedy work for us and make us think outside the box.
Do what you have to do.
One other thing, don't tell the rest of the stockholders about this.
If they find out, it's the end of this company.