EnglishPod.com Right, Rebecca.
Now I see that after graduating from university, your first job was...
For a local paper in York called the York Herald.
Actually, I started with them as an intern.
I was really keen on getting some experience in journalism, and this seemed like a good first step.
Certainly.
And after your internship?
They seemed impressed and offered me a position as a junior local news reporter.
I ended up staying two years there, actually.
I was in charge of the sports news section of the newspaper.
I really enjoyed it there, and it really helped me build my skills.
Yes, I see.
But you decided to leave them in 2006, right?
Yes, that's right.
My husband and I moved to London, and so I managed to find a position with a national newspaper based in London.
To London Weekly, right?
Yes!
In some ways it was a step down from my previous job, but it did offer me much better prospects for the future.