The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Step down.
A mental picture of something to come.
Prospect.
Let's try that faster.
Be responsible for.
In charge of.
A mental picture of something to come.
Prospect.
Turned out or resultant.
End up.
Be able to.
Managed to.
A decrease or reduction in size or amount.
Step down.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
End up.
If you don't start driving more carefully, you're going to end up in an accident.
We had meetings with several different suppliers and we ended up choosing Acme because of their excellent customer service.
End up.
Which country do you think will end up winning the FIFA World Cup 2010?
In charge of.
This is Elizabeth.
She's in charge of our Chilean customer accounts.
In charge of.
Annie, we would like to put you in charge of this project.
Roberta has been in charge of the sales department for three years now.
Managed to.
It was difficult to keep a straight face, but I managed not to laugh.
I have so many things to do this week.
I don't know how I'll manage to get through them all.
Managed to.
It's almost impossible to get weekend tickets to the Shanghai World Expo now, but Ben managed to get a pair.
Step down.
After the scandal hit the news, Mr.
Williams decided to step down as mayor.
Step down.
Going from corporate CFO to working at a startup may seem like a step down to some, but Jackie is excited about the change.
Bill Gates stepped down as CEO of Microsoft in 2000 to devote more time to creating software.
Prospect.
The prospect of living and working abroad is very appealing.
Your son has been accepted to four different universities.
Wow, he has so many prospects open to him.
Prospect.
It's true, Q3 was rough, but I think our prospects look very good for the rest of the year.