EnglishPod.com.
And so that concludes my outline for our marketing strategy next year.
Thank you very much for your time.
Hey, that was quite the presentation.
Honestly, I was completely blown away by your strategy outline.
I've got to say, Alex, you really wowed me today.
Ah, come on.
It was nothing.
I'm just doing my job.
No.
I think you deserve some recognition here.
I mean, if I look back on your previous presentations, this is a huge improvement.
Well, Kristen did give me a hand with the slides.
She's a real whiz on PowerPoint.
And I saw that you took on board my feedback about pricing strategies.
I really appreciate you taking the time to think through my suggestions.
Yeah, well, that was some good advice.
You made some really good points.
Well, I just wanted to say, well done.
Really, you did a great job.