The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Used to say it was good.
Quite the...
Praise given to someone for doing a good job.
Give credit.
The action of saying a person did a good job.
Praise.
Speech, demo, a meeting where you present something.
Presentation.
Make someone confident, help them do better.
Encourage.
To tell the truth, frankly speaking.
Honestly.
To publicly give special attention to someone for doing a good job.
Recognize.
Impressed by.
Blow someone away.
Suggestions for improvement.
Constructive criticism.
Amaze, impress.
To wow someone.
Used to show humbleness.
It was nothing.
Are entitled to.
Deserve.
Praises, credit.
Recognition.
Recall the past.
Look back on.
Advance progress.
Improvement.
Help someone.
Give someone a hand.
A genius.
Adopt.
Take on board.
Other people's opinions.
Feedback.
To carefully consider and think about it.
Think through.
Good job.
Well done.
Let's try that faster.
Used to show humbleness.
It was nothing.
Amaze, impress.
To wow someone.
A genius.
Whiz.
Make someone confident.
Help them do better.
Encourage.
Give someone a hand.
Are entitled to.
Advance progress.
Improvement.
Recall the past.
Look back on.
Adopt.
Take on board.
Recognition.
Other people's opinions.
Feedback.
Good job.
To tell the truth, frankly speaking.
Used to say it was good.
To carefully consider and think about it.
Think through.
Suggestions for improvement.
Constructive criticism.
The action of saying a person did a good job.
Praise.
Blow someone away.
To publicly give special attention to someone for doing a good job.
Recognize.
Praise given to someone for doing a good job.
Give credit.
Speech demo.
A meeting where you present something.
Presentation.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Quite the.
I heard you are quite the dancer.
Can you teach me some moves?
Quite the.
Carl is quite the ladies man.
He is very good when it comes to talking to girls.
Quite the.
That's quite the car.
You must have spent a lot of money on it.
Blow someone away.
Carl blew me away with his knowledge of political science.
I was blown away when I heard that Jenny and Rick had gotten married.
They have known each other for less than a month.
Blow someone away.
My parents were blown away when they found out I had a tattoo.
Look back on.
When I look back and remember everything I did in high school I feel so stupid.
When I look back I am amazed at all I have accomplished.
Look back on.
We raised three kids and worked full time so sometimes I look back and wonder how we did it.
Take on board.
Banks really need to take on board the views of their customers to understand them better.
It seems that young people are finally taking on board the message that it's not cool to smoke.
Take on board.
Mike is not the type of person that takes on board any feedback.
Think through.
I really need to think through my options in order to make a decision.
We can't afford a mistake so think things through and make sure you have everything ready.
Think through.
You should think through all these questions before you start writing your report.