Wow, that terrible movie is finally over.
Next time I'm picking the film because I don't want to end up seeing a chick flick.
Well, you should have picked.
In the end you always complain about everything.
Not everything.
Just this film.
Even the title was ridiculous.
And it's so long.
Those were the two and a half most wasted hours of my life.
So much so that I'm thinking about asking them to give me my money back.
I'm thinking of taking you back home.
I thought we could have a nice evening but you're always so negative.
I'm only complaining about a movie that I could have rented or bought and then thrown in the garbage.
You see, that's what I'm talking about.
I can't stand your sarcastic jokes anymore.
Next time go with your gay friend who is more in touch with his feelings.
Well, he's more of a man than you are.
At least he appreciates love stories.
Love stories?
More like one night stands.
Don't criticize Mario or else I'll start on those fat drunk friends of yours.
They're no scenes.
My friends?
Fat?
What about those whales you call friends?
You're unbearable.
You can walk home.
I'm leaving.
Fine.