The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A film that appeals to women.
Chick flick The use of words to show irritation.
Sarcastic To be in close contact with.
In touch with A random and temporary romantic encounter.
To express disapproval.
Too bad to be accepted or endured.
Unbearable Let's try that faster.
To be in close contact with.
In touch with To express disapproval.
Criticize Chick flick The use of words to show irritation.
Sarcastic A random and temporary romantic encounter.
One night stand Too bad to be accepted or endured.
Unbearable Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Chick flick My girlfriend dragged me to go see another chick flick.
Chick flick This channel only shows chick flicks.
Chick flick The chick flick genre enjoyed great success a few years ago.
I can't stand the weather here.
It's too hot.
She told me she can't stand me and then she left.
Now I'm all alone.
Turn that music down.
I can't stand country western.
Sarcastic Don't be so sarcastic because it's really obnoxious.
Sarcastic Thank you for the wonderful service the customer said sarcastically.
Sarcastic Many performers use sarcasm for comedic effect.
In touch with Let's see this chick flick and get in touch with our feminine side.
In touch with He's just more in touch with his feelings.
But he's not gay.
In touch with Please remember to write and stay in touch.
Unbearable I couldn't stand the flight attendants unbearable politeness.
Unbearable The summers here are unbearable because of the heat.
Unbearable This music is unbearable.
Turn it down.