The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To make an arrangement to hold something for later.
Make a reservation.
To make arrangements for later.
Book.
To not have any.
Have no.
The protection that is offered by an insurance policy.
Coverage.
Contract signed with details of car rental.
Rental agreement.
To have no more.
Run out.
You should.
You better.
To leave money when you rent a car and that you get back if you return the car in good condition.
Leave a deposit.
To purposefully abuse something.
Beat the hell out of.
A medium-sized car.
Mid-sized vehicle.
The amount of money to be paid per day the car is rented.
Daily rate.
At the present time.
At the moment.
A small car.
Compact.
Sport utility vehicle.
SUV.
Protection from costs of accidental damage.
Insurance.
Let's try that faster.
To make an arrangement to hold something for later.
Make a reservation.
Contract signed with details of car rental.
Rental agreement.
To not have any.
Have no.
A small car.
Compact.
At the present time.
At the moment.
Sport utility vehicle.
SUV.
Run out.
The protection that is offered by an insurance policy.
Coverage.
The amount of money to be paid per day the car is rented.
Daily rate.
A medium-sized car.
Mid-sized vehicle.
Protection from costs of accidental damage.
Insurance.
You should.
You better.
To purposefully abuse something.
Beat the hell out of.
To make arrangements for later.
Book.
To leave money when you rent a car and that you get back if you return the car in good condition.
Leave a deposit.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Make a reservation.
I've made a dinner reservation at our favorite restaurant for tomorrow night.
I'm sorry, sir.
You need to make a reservation in order to eat here.
Make a reservation.
Many hotels now offer a service where you can make an online reservation.
Have no.
You have no right to tell me what to do.
We have no electricity in the building.
Have no.
Susan has no money since she lost her job.
Run out.
We're going to run out of gasoline.
You need to find a gas station soon.
Run out.
Can you buy some milk on your way home?
We ran out last night.
Run out.
My pen ran out of ink.
Can you lend me one, please?
You better.
You better go to the doctor before that cold gets any worse.
You better watch out.
It's dangerous to go out this late.
You better.
She better change her attitude or her boss is going to fire her.
Beat the hell out of.
Our team beat the hell out of the other team last week in the game.
If you ever do that again, I'm going to beat the hell out of you.
Beat the hell out of.
Did you see that?
That dog just beat the hell out of that poor cat.