The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An appointment, engagement, or occasion with another person.
Date.
Talk with another person.
Chat.
Over the internet.
Online.
A crazy person.
Psycho.
A distinguishing feature or quality.
Characteristic.
The favouring of one thing over another.
Preference.
Spend time with a friend.
Hang out.
Let's try that faster.
Over the internet.
Online.
Spend time with a friend.
Hang out.
The favouring of one thing over another.
Preference.
A distinguishing feature or quality.
Characteristic.
An appointment, engagement, or occasion with another person.
Date.
Talk with another person.
Chat.
A crazy person.
Psycho.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Wow, that psycho just attacked that old man.
Psycho.
Quick, call the police.
That psycho has a knife.
Psycho.
Sometimes my brother goes psycho if he can't play video games.
Online.
Hey, can you go online and find a hotel for me?
Careful, you can find a lot of weird stuff online.
Online.
He showed me the funniest thing online.
A dancing panda.
Hang out.
Where do you want to hang out today?
How about we hang out downtown and play some pool?
Hang out.
Let's just hang out at home and play some video games.
Chat.
I want to chat to you about something important.
He was angry about the chat he had with his mother.
Chat.
I don't want to do anything tonight.
Let's just chat online.
Date.
He was very excited about the big date he had later that day.
Hey, can I ask you out on a date?
Date.
Remember, we have a date to play golf tomorrow morning.