EnglishPod.com Do you want to hang out tomorrow?
Oh, I can't.
I have a date.
Really?
Wow, with who?
This girl I've been chatting with for the past couple of months.
She's really cool and she's driving over here this weekend.
Wait a minute.
You mean you met her online?
Yeah.
I signed up for a website called Match.com and it's great.
You fill in all your details and preferences, like if you are a smoker or if you have any pets.
Then you find people that have similar characteristics and you can email them or chat.
That's kind of weird.
What if she's a psycho or something like that?
It's the same as meeting people anywhere and dating them.
I'm just tired of going to bars or being set up for dates by my friends.
I think this is a really cool alternative, especially if you are a bit shy.
I guess it does seem logical.
I'll have to check it out.
Thanks for watching!