The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Money and benefits given to someone for the work.
Remuneration package Each year Per annum Money that a company provides for rent of a house.
Housing allowance Able to change or to do different things.
Flexible To study or look at something in a careful way.
Go through Let's try that faster.
To study or look at something in a careful way.
Go through Each year Per annum Able to change or to do different things.
Flexible Money and benefits given to someone for the work.
Remuneration package Money that a company provides for rent of a house.
Housing allowance Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Housing allowance This company doesn't offer a housing allowance, but the salary more than makes up for it.
Housing allowance MNCs MNCs don't usually offer housing allowance to employees hired locally.
Housing allowance And how much is the housing allowance you offer?
Per annum Molly from HR will have to explain our bonus scheme to you.
Per annum The bonus scheme is designed to reward only the highest achieving employees.
Per annum We will be making some changes to the bonus scheme this year.
Flexible I have a flexible working schedule.
Flexible Flexible I'm afraid the company is really not flexible when it comes to working hours.
Flexible When it comes to change, many people are not flexible.
Go through Do you have a few minutes to go through the quarterly report?
Go through I'll ask Angela to go through the new company policy with us.
Go through Brent has already gone through the preliminary information.
Remuneration package Please feel free to help yourself to coffee, tea, or whatever you'd like.
Remuneration package Feel free to interrupt me anytime with questions.
Remuneration package I wish I felt free to speak with my boss on this matter, but I don't know how she'd react.