EnglishPod.com OK, well I'm sure you have a number of questions to ask me regarding the position.
Yes, well Miss Childs did give me an overview of the position over the phone, but there were some details I'd like to clarify.
Well, feel free to ask me anything, and I'll try to fill in the details.
Could I first ask about the renumeration package?
Yes, of course.
That's quite an important point, isn't it?
As a junior sub-editor, we offer a starting salary of 150,000 Hong Kong dollars per annum.
This doesn't include a generous housing allowance also.
I understand.
And are there other bonuses included?
Well, apart from full health insurance, we do offer a company staff bonus scheme linked to readership numbers.
But we could go through all the details of that at a later date.
Well, Mr.
Parsons, I am flexible when it comes to salary.
The opportunity to work in Hong Kong with your company is the most important thing for me.
Excellent.
Well, what other questions do you have, Rebecca?