EnglishPod.com Man, I'm freaking out.
You gotta help me.
Whoa, whoa.
Take it easy.
Relax.
Jeez, you're sweating like a pig.
What's going on?
I can't go through with this.
I just can't.
I'm not ready for marriage.
What was I thinking?
I'm only 35 years old.
I've got my entire life ahead of me.
Adventure's waiting.
I can't settle down yet.
What are you talking about?
It wasn't more than a month ago that you were rambling on about how you are tired of living the life of a bachelor and how you envy your friends that have a family.
I know, I know.
Let's think this through.
First of all, you cannot leave Amy at the altar.
Not only will she be humiliated and kill you, but she is the woman that you love and the woman of your dreams.
Why would you want to end that or jeopardize it like this?
Second of all, you were just getting cold feet.
You know deep down inside that you'd want to marry her.
So cut the crap and do it.
You're right.
I'm being crazy.
Okay, I'm ready.
Let's do this.
Great.
That was a close one.
You had me going there for a minute.
I thought I was going to have to slap some sense into you.