The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Showing concern for the needs and feelings of other people.
Thoughtful A physical desire of food.
Appetite Make someone to feel scared and uncomfortable.
Give the creeps.
Start to know, become familiar with someone.
Get to know Expression to emphasize surprise or frustration.
On earth Say you will not or cannot do something.
Decline Rope into Polite way to ask guests to make themselves comfortable.
Make yourself at home.
Being a friendly and caring host to the guests.
Hospitable Potluck A party to celebrate moving into a new house.
Housewarming Let's try that faster.
Say you will not or cannot do something.
Decline Being a friendly and caring host to the guests.
Hospitable Polite way to ask guests to make themselves comfortable.
Make yourself at home.
A physical desire of food.
Appetite A party to celebrate moving into a new house.
Housewarming Start to know, become familiar with someone.
Get to know Showing concern for the needs and feelings of other people.
Thoughtful Make someone to feel scared and uncomfortable.
Give the creeps.
Potluck Expression to emphasize surprise or frustration.
On earth Rope into Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Thoughtful Thanks for the Christmas gift.
It's exactly what I want.
You're so thoughtful.
Thoughtful This is very thoughtful of you to help me out.
Thoughtful Thank you for being so thoughtful.
Appetite Mmm, dinner smells so good.
It's giving me an appetite.
Appetite You're sure eating a lot.
You must have a big appetite.
Appetite I'm getting sick.
I have a fever and I've lost my appetite.
Give the creeps Horror movies give me the creeps.
Give the creeps Stop showing these images to me.
They are giving me the creep.
Give the creeps I saw this really scary clown.
It gave me the creep.
Where on earth is my phone?
How on earth did you learn English in one month?
What on earth is it?
Decline It's not polite to decline Molly and Jim's dinner invitation.
Decline Decline Unfortunately, I'm going to have to decline the invitation to your party.
I'm busy that day.
Decline Everyone is going to attend the wedding.
No one declined our invitation.
Last night, Pete roped me into going for a drink after work.
Renee is always roping me into doing her work for her.
You're not going to rope me into spending the whole day shopping?
Get to know Karen and Victor got to know each other in university.
Get to know After you get to know him, Alan is a really nice guy.
Get to know I'm spending some time getting to know my team.