The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A person through whom the spirits of the dead are alleged to be able to contact the living.
Medium Having great special talent or ability.
Gifted Sensitive to influences or forces of a non-physical or supernatural nature.
Psychic Of, pertaining to, treating or characteristic of history or past events.
Historic To do or perform repeatedly.
Practice Any of a set of 22 playing cards bearing allegorical representations used for fortune telling.
Tarot The powdery residue of matter that remains after burning.
Ash Irrational fear of what is unknown or mysterious.
Superstition Foolish religious reverence, ritual or incantation.
Hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
Let's try that faster.
Any of a set of 22 playing cards bearing allegorical representations used for fortune telling.
Tarot The powdery residue of matter that remains after burning.
Ash To do or perform repeatedly.
Practice A person through whom the spirits of the dead are alleged to be able to contact the living.
Medium Having great special talent or ability.
Gifted Foolish religious reverence, ritual or incantation.
Hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
Irrational fear of what is unknown or mysterious.
Superstition Sensitive to influences or forces of a non-physical or supernatural nature.
Psychic Of, pertaining to, treating or characteristic of history or past events.
Historic Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Gifted My daughter is very gifted, maybe I should enroll her into a special school.
Gifted They only make fun of him because he is gifted and they are not.
Gifted She is gifted with the piano, she will be famous one day.
Hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
I think the idea of aliens is just a bunch of hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
I believe that religion is only hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
Hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
The professor tried to convince his students that the theory wasn't hocus-pocus mumbo-jumbo.
Psychic Psychic I can tell you your future, I'm psychic.
Psychic My friend predicted who would win the basketball match, he must be psychic.
Psychic If people are really psychic, wouldn't they predict the lottery numbers?
Superstition I have a superstition that if I see a black cat, I have to turn around three times.
Superstition Superstition Sumo wrestlers have a funny superstition where they throw salt over their shoulder.
Superstition My friend doesn't believe in superstitions, he thinks it's silly to believe in things like that.
Ash Could you please not smoke in here?
All the ash is falling on my couch.
Ash This fire is scary, the whole sky is full of ash and smoke.
Ash Next time you smoke, please use an ashtray.