EnglishPod.com Look at this newspaper article about this famous local medium.
It says that she is really gifted and so popular now that she's booked solid with appointments for the next 12 months.
You don't really believe in all that hocus pocus mumbo jumbo, do you?
Well, I have had many friends that went to a psychic and got their palms read and most of the things the psychic told them came true.
Of course it does.
They tell you general and obvious things like that you'll be successful or have a big house.
I think most of the times they're just scam artists.
Well, historically it's a practice that many cultures share.
Reading the tarot cards.
In the east they would even read tea leaves.
I even heard that there are people that make you smoke a cigar and then read your ashes.
All superstitious nonsense.
I would still like to go to one and see what he or she has to say just for kicks.
Great.
I'll make an appointment.