The EnglishPod Audio Review.
Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Smart and noticeable, but in a rather vulgar way.
Flashy.
Bark in a high-pitched tone.
Nag.
Yap.
Give something and receive something in return.
Exchange.
An occasion for buying at special price.
Sale.
Help someone.
Do someone the favour.
Let's try that faster.
Give something and receive something in return.
Exchange.
Smart and noticeable, but in a rather vulgar way.
Flashy.
Bark in a high-pitched tone.
Yap.
Help someone.
Do someone the favour.
An occasion for buying at special price.
Sale.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Flashy.
I don't like jewellery with lots of diamonds, because I think it is too flashy.
Her sequined dress was way too flashy.
Flashy.
The Las Vegas strip is known to have flashy hotels, flashy casinos and flashy cars.
Yap.
I tried to think of an excuse to leave as my date kept on yapping about sports statistics.
She yapped on all night about how her and her prom date were meant for each other.
Yap.
He kept yapping on and on about how he was right and his father was wrong.
Exchange.
Most stores have an exchange policy if you want to return what you bought.
When I got home, I found out that the colour of the tablecloth didn't match the kitchen at all, so I took it back to the store and exchanged it for a different colour the next day.
Exchange.
In exchange for your sparkle sticker, I will give you two of my big stickers.
Sale.
Many stores expand their Boxing Day sales up until New Year's Eve.
The mall is usually very crowded on Boxing Day because of the special sales.
Clearance sales usually have big discounts because the purpose of the sale is to get rid of all the old merchandise.
Do someone the favour.
Can you do me the favour of turning off the television?
It's on all the time.
Do someone the favour.
Can you do us the favour of handing over your wallet so no one will get hurt?
Can you do me the favour of letting me know you have to use the bathroom before we get into the car?
Thanks for watching!