Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Suggestion.
Talk about something briefly.
Mention.
To be thoroughly wet.
Soak.
As regards oneself.
Personally.
Talk about something briefly.
Mention.
In a hurry.
Rush.
Idea about what someone should do.
Suggestion.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Mention.
Did I mention that we are having Chinese for dinner?
He forgot to mention that he was already married.
Mention.
I don't want to mention to my husband that I lost my engagement ring.
Rush.
Sorry, I have no time to chat.
I'm in a bit of a rush.
Rush.
There was a huge rush to get the movie tickets before they ran out.
You're always in a rush, just calm down.
Personally.
I think you're better off going to university rather than clown academy.
I think starting my career in the retail industry would be better for me, personally.
Personally.
I prefer slow songs over faster pop music.
Suggestion.
Don't take it so seriously.
It was only a suggestion.
Suggestion.
That's a great suggestion.
Thanks for the help.
Suggestion.
If you have any suggestions, please tell me.
I'm all ears.
Soak.
I'm going to soak these potatoes in water for a while.
I'm soaked in a threezing after that water fight.
Soak.
Let's soak him in beer so everyone thinks he's drunk.