The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To give examples to make something easier to understand.
illustrate change topic sidetrack To talk to or write to you at a later time.
get back to you have rest take five Let's try that faster.
To give examples to make something easier to understand.
illustrate have rest take five To talk to or write to you at a later time.
get back to you change topic sidetrack Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
illustrate Let me show you some pictures to illustrate my idea better.
illustrate He likes to illustrate his points using many different examples.
illustrate I know this concept is a little complicated.
So to prevent misunderstandings, let me illustrate further.
Our professor likes to insert personal answer notes into his lectures.
Good presenters often illustrate their main points with specific answer notes.
Lucy's grandmother is fun to talk with because she always has an answer note about when she was young.
sidetrack I was going to take out the trash, but I got sidetracked.
sidetrack He gets sidetracked easily, so keep an eye on him and make sure he does his work.
sidetrack When Rachel puts them onto something, she is very determined and doesn't get sidetracked.
get back to you Mr Jones is not in right now.
Can I take a message and ask him to get back to you?
get back to you I don't know the answer to your question, but let me look it up and get back to you.
get back to you I'm busy at the moment, but I'll get back to you tomorrow morning.
take 5 We've been working on this project for hours.
Let's take 5 and do this later.
take 5 I'm so hungry, let's take 5 and grab a bite to eat.
take 5 Let me take 5 and fix this technical problem.