The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The quality of always being on time.
Punctual Blocked so you can't move forward.
Backed up Later than planned, late.
Behind schedule Sleep later than planned.
Sleep Become busy, unable to leave.
Got tied up The quality of often being late.
Tardiness Move very quickly Hustle Going to be late Running late To go beyond a limit Ran over Stuck in traffic Soon In a sec Very big Huge Traffic jam An accident where many cars crash into each other.
Pile up Let's try that faster.
Going to be late Soon Move very quickly Hustle Sleep later than planned To go beyond a limit Ran over Become busy, unable to leave.
Got tied up The quality of often being late.
Tardiness An accident where many cars crash into each other.
Pile up Blocked so you can't move forward.
Backed up The quality of always being on time.
Punctual Later than planned, late.
Behind schedule A lot of cars stopped from moving.
Traffic jam Very big Huge So many cars on the road that you cannot drive or move forward.
Stuck in traffic Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Stuck in traffic Hello Daniel, it's me.
Listen, I'm going to be late today because I'm stuck in traffic.
Stuck in traffic We should leave early this morning or else we'll get stuck in traffic.
Stuck in traffic We should have taken the other highway.
Now we'll be stuck in traffic for at least an hour.
Ran over The meeting ran over by more than 30 minutes.
Ran over I always leave an extra 15 minutes in my schedule just in case meetings run over a bit.
Ran over Frank always forgets about the time and runs over the time limit of his presentations.
Running late Jane is running late.
She'll be here in 10 minutes.
Running late Traffic is really bad, so I'm running late.
Running late I'm running a bit late, so please start without me.
Got tied up Sorry I'm late, honey.
I got tied up at the office.
Got tied up I was tied up on the phone all afternoon and didn't get any work done.
Got tied up I got tied up in traffic on the way here.
The accident backed up traffic for miles.
Don't take the 405 freeway today.
There was an accident so there are cars backed up for miles.
Our highway system is very inefficient.
Traffic is backed up for miles every morning.