EnglishPod.com Where is everyone?
We were supposed to start 15 minutes ago.
Joe called and said she'd be here in a sec.
She said she got tied up with a client.
Sorry I'm late everyone.
There was a huge traffic jam on the highway this morning.
Morning everyone.
Were you stuck in traffic as well Jess?
There was a huge pile up on the highway.
And traffic was backed up for miles.
Scott just called and said that he's running late.
His last meeting ran over, but he's on his way now.
Guys, this is not acceptable.
If I say the meeting starts at 10, the meeting starts at 10, not 10-01, and definitely not 10-20.
Alright, let's get started.
So the first thing I wanted to talk about is our...
I'm really sorry everyone.
I know I'm late, but really it's not my fault.
I was getting a coffee at Starbucks and the line was way, way too long.
I was waiting for 20 minutes to get my coffee.