Call someone to feel admiration, impress, to finish or end, wrap up, to grow or expand suddenly, boom, to tell information again using fewer words, sum up, at the beginning of something, at the outset, to finish or end, wrap up, at the beginning of something, at the outset, to grow or expand suddenly, boom, to tell information again using fewer words, sum up, call someone to feel admiration, impress.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Impress.
He is trying really hard to impress her, but she doesn't seem to notice.
She was really impressed with the progress we had made while she was gone.
Impress.
I think you will be impressed by the developments in our company.
Wrap up.
Let me wrap up my work before we go out to dinner.
Well, that just about wraps it up.
Any questions?
Wrap up.
He wrapped up the discussion with the Q&A session.
At the outset.
He expressed his feelings at the outset, but no one listened to him.
I should have stated my objections at the outset before we started working.
At the outset.
She made her intentions known at the outset, so there wouldn't be any misunderstanding.
Boom.
Even though we are going through hard financial times, some businesses are booming.
He bought a lot of houses when the economy was booming, but now he is deep in debt.
Boom.
The demand for the new iPhones is booming.
Sum up.
Let's sum up the key points we've agreed on so far.
I think this poem accurately sums up my feelings.
Sum up.
I didn't get to watch the news this morning.
Can you sum up the top stories for me?