EnglishPod.com I'm really looking forward to lighting them.
Son, firecrackers aren't toys, they are dangerous.
No, fireworks are awesome.
Wow, don't you remember?
Last year when I set off the firecrackers, you covered both your ears and hid behind your mother.
Dad, I was scared because I saw a bug, that's all.
Haha, really?
Oh, and I can't wait to watch the dragon dance.
Dad, can I sit on your shoulders this time?
Hey, I offered last year.
Well, anyways, I was just thinking of the red envelopes.
I want to make a list of all the things I'm going to buy with my red envelope money.
I can't wait.
I'm going to have so much money.
Mom, can I get a pen and a piece of paper?
I want a new transformer.
No, two transformers.
Optimus Prime.
Wheeljack.
I'll get a PSP game.