The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Very happy about something.
Excited Small lump of dough that is steamed or boiled, traditional Chinese New Year food.
Dumpling A cylinder filled with explosive substance that makes loud noise when it explodes.
Firecracker Excited and happy about something that will happen in the future.
Look forward to.
Eager or excited about doing something or for something to begin.
Can't wait.
Caused something to explode.
Set off Chinese New Year based on the cycles of the moon.
Lunar New Year Chinese New Year Spring Festival A calendar based on the cycles and phases of the moon.
Lunar calendar Very excited about something that will happen in the future.
Can hardly wait.
Not happy or willing to wait for something.
Impatient Let's try that faster.
Small lump of dough that is steamed or boiled, traditional Chinese New Year food.
Dumpling Excited and happy about something that will happen in the future.
Look forward to.
A cylinder filled with explosive substance that makes loud noise when it explodes.
Firecracker Chinese New Year based on the cycles of the moon.
Lunar New Year Very happy about something.
Excited Very excited about something that will happen in the future.
Can hardly wait.
Not happy or willing to wait for something.
Impatient Eager or excited about doing something or for something to begin.
Can't wait Chinese New Year Spring Festival A calendar based on the cycles and phases of the moon.
Lunar calendar Caused something to explode.
Set off Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Excited I'm so excited about my trip to Europe next month.
Excited Johnny is going to be so excited when he receives this gift.
Excited Chelsea is so excited about her first baby.
I bet I'm going to get so much money for Chinese New Year.
I bet the boss is going to give us a big bonus this year.
I bet I'm going to have a great time tonight.
Dumpling My grandma taught me how to make dumplings.
Dumpling Have you tried the dumplings?
They're amazing.
Dumpling Do you want to have some dumplings for lunch?
Firecracker Are you going to buy firecrackers for Chinese New Year?
Firecracker Firecracker There are firecrackers everywhere on New Year's Eve.
Firecracker I don't like firecrackers.
They're too loud.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to see you.
Mmm.
Smells delicious.
I can't wait for dinner.
I can't wait to open my presents.
Look forward to I'm really looking forward to Spring Festival.
Look forward to I'm looking forward to I'm looking forward to meeting with you tonight.
Look forward to I have been looking forward to hearing from you.
Set off Be careful while I set off the firecracker.
Set off The police are searching for the person who set off the explosion last night.
Set off The smoke set off the building's fire alarm.