The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Be remembered, comes to mind, spring to mind, to stop before you do something, hesitate, think something will probably happen, expect, list of people or items most likely to be chosen, shortlist.
Does that seem good to you?
How does that sound?
Let's try that faster.
Think something will probably happen, expect, be remembered, comes to mind, spring to mind, to stop before you do something, hesitate.
Does that seem good to you?
How does that sound?
List of people or items most likely to be chosen, shortlist.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Spring to mind.
I'd love to help you with an idea for the ad campaign, but nothing springs to mind.
Now, this is a brainstorming session, so just call out whatever springs to mind.
Spring to mind.
If any further comments or suggestions spring to mind, please do give me a call.
If you have any questions at all, don't hesitate to ask.
Please don't hesitate to get in touch with me if I can be of any assistance.
Hesitate.
George was about to say something else, but he hesitated and the opportunity passed.
Expect.
It was lovely to meet you, Sarah.
When can we expect to see you again?
Expect.
John, can I expect to see the finished report by Friday?
When can we expect to hear your decision, Ms.
Walsh?
Shortlist.
We've shortlisted three candidates for the position.
Well, I made the shortlist, but I still have to add two more interviews if I want the job.
Shortlist.
The Russian dancer was shortlisted for the role, but in the end, they chose someone else.
Johnny, if you're very good this morning, I'll take you out for ice cream.
How does that sound?
Let's go over the Anderson account first, then move on to the Jones account.
I suggest we start our trip in Beijing, then travel to Tianjin, and from there to Qingdao.
How does that sound to you?
We'll be right back.