EnglishPod.com Well, Rebecca, is there anything else you need to know for now?
I don't think so, Mr Parsons.
I think you have covered all the main points for me.
Okay, well, listen.
Here's my business card with my mobile number.
If any other questions spring to mind, don't hesitate to contact me.
Of course, you can also call Miss Childs, too.
Great.
Um, when can I expect to hear from you?
Well, we are finishing the shortlist interviews tomorrow, so we will certainly have a decision made by early next week.
Miss Childs will call you to discuss more on Monday or Tuesday.
How does that sound?
That sounds perfect.
Thank you very much for taking the time to speak to me, Mr Parsons.
The pleasure's all mine, Rebecca.
I hope to hear from you very soon.
Absolutely.
Thanks for coming, Rebecca.
Goodbye.