EnglishPod.com Come in.
Mr.
Parsons?
Ah, you must be Rebecca.
Please do come in.
Thank you for making some time to see me, Mr.
Parsons.
It's a pleasure to meet you finally.
The pleasure's all mine, Rebecca.
Have a seat, please.
Now, would you like any refreshments, tea, or coffee?
A coffee would be lovely, thank you.
Black, no sugar.
No problem.
Sally, can we have two coffees, please?
One, no milk or sugar.
Certainly, Mr.
Parsons.
So, Rebecca, I understand you had a first interview with Ms.
Childs last week?
Yes, that's correct.
She filled me in on the details of the job on the telephone.
Great.
Well, I'm glad to say she recommended you for a second interview, and here we are.
Perhaps we can start by discussing your background and resume details a little.
Yes, of course.