The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Use to change the topic of a conversation.
By the way Think about if something is possible.
Wonder A public performance of music.
Concert Go and get Pick up Very well known and well liked Popular Buck Not fair, not just Unfair A set of clothes that usually consists of a jacket and a skirt or a pair of pants that are made out of the same material.
Suit Play Drop off No way Blend Let's try that faster No way Buck Think about if something is possible.
Wonder Play Not fair, not just Unfair Drop off Concert Use to change the topic of a conversation.
By the way Blend A set of clothes that usually consists of a jacket and a skirt or a pair of pants that are made out of the same material.
Suit Go and get Pick up Very well known and well liked Popular Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Concert There is a rock concert tonight.
Do you want to go?
Concert Nightwish is playing live in concert tonight.
Let's go.
Concert I went to an amazing classical music concert last night.
Wonder I was wondering, can I use your computer?
Wonder Carrie was wondering if she could stay at your house on Saturday.
Wonder We were wondering if you could buy the tickets for us.
Do you think you can have those reports finished by today?
Do you think I can have some of your sandwich?
Do you think you can help me with my homework?
Popular Brad Pitt is one of the most popular actors in the world.
Popular When I was in high school, I was the most popular kid in school.
Popular The TV series Friends was a very popular show.
Would you mind buying a soda for me?
Would you mind cooking dinner tonight?
I'll be home late.
Would you mind blowing your voice?
I'm trying to watch a movie.