EnglishPod.com Hey, how was your first day of class?
I'm a level 2 and I'm loving my class this semester.
It's great being in a class of international students.
Mine was okay, except that no one in my class speaks English.
I guess it will force me to converse in Chinese more in class, so at least I should improve a lot this semester.
That's both fortunate and unfortunate.
It's the United Nations in my class.
We have people from all over the world.
There are three Germans, a Pole, a Scott, two French, an American, a Brazilian, a Chilean, a New Zealander, though he prefers to call himself a Kiwi.
Who else do we have?
Oh, we have a Moroccan, a Tagolese, a Pakistani, and two Indonesians.
That's quite the array of nationalities.
Everyone in my class is from Asia, except me.
There are a few South Koreans, several Japanese, Malaysian, Thai, Singaporean, Filipino, Kazakhstani, and one Russian.
Well, I think you're pretty lucky, actually.
You'll have the opportunity to learn so much about Asian culture.
I guess so, but I think it's going to be hard to relate to my classmates, especially with the language barrier.
I think I might change classes.
Don't!
Stay the course!
Your spoken Chinese will be eternally grateful.
I bet you it will even surpass mine with all that practice.
I highly doubt it.
Your girlfriend is Chinese.
Well, there is that, yes.