The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An international political organization.
United Nations A large group or quantity of people or things.
Array Chance Opportunity Trouble communicating because speak different languages.
Language barrier Remain or persevere to the end.
Stay the course Let's try that faster.
Trouble communicating because speak different languages.
Language barrier A large group or quantity of people or things.
Array An international political organization.
United Nations Chance Opportunity Remain or persevere to the end.
Stay the course Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
United Nations She has friends of all different nationalities and they teach her a lot about different cultures.
United Nations This city has cuisine from many different countries.
You could say it's the United Nations of Dining.
United Nations Our office is like the United Nations.
We have employees from all over the world.
Array Array Erica has an array of dolls she collected from all her travels.
Array There was a large array of people at the party and I had a lot of fun getting to know everybody.
Array She has an array of accessories to choose from every morning.
Opportunity If I make a good impression today, he might give me the opportunity to work for his office full-time.
Opportunity I am moving to the city where there are more opportunities for me.
Opportunity Even though you messed up, I will give you an opportunity to fix the problem.
Language barrier Language barrier At first, it was hard to relate to my Chinese roommate because of the language barrier.
Language barrier Language barrier Even though they seem to really like each other, the language barrier makes it hard for them to have a deeper relationship.
Language barrier There are some expressions that are universal, regardless of the language barrier.
Stay the course Even though it might seem impossible, I'm sure that if you stay the course, you'll definitely find a solution.
Stay the course We will meet some challenges, but we will succeed if we stay the course.
Stay the course Even though the war is going badly, the president has decided to stay the course.