The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A container used to give its shape to something.
Mold Considered valuable by collectors.
Collectible Opposable plastic figurine of a character.
Action figure A kind of toy Yo-Yo An animated television series Spongebob Squarepants A toy set of Lego Pirates Lego set A group of similar things that belong together Set A fictional superhero team X-Men A modeling compound used by children Play-Doh A chest filled with valuables Treasure chest A chest filled with valuables Treasure chest A fictional superhero team X-Men Considered valuable by collectors Collectible A container used to give its shape to something Mold A modeling compound used by children Play-Doh A group of similar things that belong together Set An animated television series Spongebob Squarepants Opposable plastic figurine of a character Action figure A kind of toy Yo-Yo A toy set of Lego Pirates Lego set Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Set The little girls took out their tea set and had a tea party.
Set This Lego set comes with five men, a dragon and two horses.
Set Own all three sets of exotic toy animals and create your own zoo.
Mold He pressed the Play-Doh into the mold.
Mold Mold She poured the cake batter into the cake mold and then placed it in the oven.
Mold He gently lifted the mold off of the sand and smiled at the sand castle he had made.
Collectible Collectible I keep this doll on the shelf in its original box because it is a collectible doll.
Collectible I have a lot of collectible items such as baseball cards and model airplanes.
Collectible Collectible Every year for my birthday my uncle gives me a collectible coin.
Action figure This action figure can shoot a laser from its arm.
Action figure My sister has several toy story action figures.
Action figure The actress thought it was weird to see her face on her character's action figure.
Yo-Yo This guy in my school does crazy tricks with his yo-yo during recess.
Yo-Yo She looped the string around her finger through the yo-yo, grabbed the string several times and performed a trick.
Yo-Yo The only thing I know how to do with a yo-yo is how to throw it.