Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A piece of paper that proves you bought something.
Receipt.
Go back to the original place.
Return.
Control a device for computer.
Keyboard.
Things that a company makes or sells.
Product.
To move to and fro, vibrate, quiver.
Flicker.
To cause or allow to run or fall from a container.
Spill.
Give something and receive something in return.
Exchange.
Having a mistake or error.
Defective.
To get your money back.
Refund.
Fragile, easily damaged.
Delicate.
Let's try that faster.
Give something and receive something in return.
Exchange.
To cause or allow to run or fall from a container.
Spill.
Fragile, easily damaged.
Delicate.
To move to and fro, vibrate, quiver.
Flicker.
Having a mistake or error.
Defective.
A piece of paper that proves you bought something.
Receipt.
Things that a company makes or sells.
Product.
To get your money back.
Refund.
Controller device for computer.
Keyboard.
Go back to the original place.
Return.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Receipt.
Hello, could I please have the receipt?
Would you like a receipt?
Receipt.
Your receipt entitles you to a 5% discount on the purchase price.
Delicate.
Please mark any items you do not want damaged as delicate.
This glass face is very delicate, so please wrap it up.
Delicate.
I'm delicate like glass, please don't hurt me.
Exchange.
Could I please exchange this item for another one of similar price?
Sorry, we don't do exchanges, only refunds.
Exchange.
Can we please exchange business cards?
Defective.
This car is defective, I want my money back.
If you have any of our products that are defective, please return them for a full refund.
Defective.
Sorry, but your car warranty is defective, please update it.
Refund.
My new television is broken, I want a refund.
Sorry, but you damaged this product yourself, we can't give you a refund.
Refund.
That movie was so bad, I want a refund.