The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To rub your skin with something sharp.
Scratch Behaving in a secret and usually dishonest manner.
Sneaky To allow to exist or happen.
Put up with A liquid used to prevent being bitten by bugs.
Bug spray A small flying insect that bites the skin.
Mosquito Let's try that faster.
A liquid used to prevent being bitten by bugs.
Bug spray A small flying insect that bites the skin.
Mosquito Behaving in a secret and usually dishonest manner.
Sneaky To allow to exist or happen.
Put up with To rub your skin with something sharp.
Scratch Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Mosquito Mosquito bites are very itchy.
Mosquito Some mosquitoes can spread diseases through their bites.
Mosquito Only female mosquitoes bite.
Scratch The cat scratched me with its claws.
Scratch Will you please scratch my back?
Scratch Be careful not to scratch the table.
Sneaky That was a sneaky trick.
Sneaky The sneaky thief crept into the open window.
Sneaky The kid snuck into the movie without paying.
Bug spray Pass me the bug spray.
I'm being eaten alive.
Bug spray Try to avoid getting the bug spray in your eyes.
Bug spray Let's try this natural bug spray.
It's made with garlic.
Put up with I can't put up with the noise any longer.
Turn down that music.
Put up with If you can put up with the smell then stinky tofu is actually very tasty.
Put up with I have put up with him for too long.
I want a new roommate.