The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Have a manicure.
Get someone's nails done.
Treat with excessive indulgence.
Pamper.
Smooth with a file.
Cover.
Surface.
Coat.
To place in contact with, to lay or spread on.
Apply.
Let's try that faster.
Have a manicure.
Get someone's nails done.
Cover.
Surface.
Coat.
Treat with excessive indulgence.
Pamper.
To place in contact with, to lay or spread on.
Apply.
Smooth with a file.
File.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Get someone's nails done.
My girlfriends and I are getting together tonight to get our nails done.
At the birthday party, the girls did each other's nails with purple nail polish.
Get someone's nails done.
Your nails look horrible.
You should go to the manicurist to get your nails done before the wedding.
Pamper.
I like to pamper myself every once in a while.
He pampers her with flowers and chocolates all the time.
Pamper.
She likes to pamper her dog.
She buys him pillows and toys and gives him treats twice a day.
File.
The manicurist filed my nails until they were smooth.
He filed down the rough edges of the piece of metal.
File.
She keeps a nail file in her purse at all times.
Coat.
The new coat of paint was fading already.
I waited until the last coat of nail polish dried before putting on my gloves.
Coat.
The apple had a coat of melted sugar around it.
Apply.
My manicurist applied a clear base coat, two coats of color, and a clear top coat on my nails.
He applied a new coat of paint on his truck.
Apply.
The child applied two stickers to the front of his notebook.
The end.