The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An area of land for the enjoyment of the public Park Field to excess, packed Crowded A plank used to balance Seesaw A smooth surface for sliding on Slide A box for holding sand, large enough for children to play in Sandbox Overexcited Overexcited Hyper The action of hitting the golf ball Swing Very tired Exhausted Let's try that faster Overexcited Overexcited Hyper A plank used to balance Seesaw An area of land for the enjoyment of the public Park A box for holding sand, large enough for children to play in Sandbox A smooth surface for sliding on Slide Very tired Exhausted The action of hitting the golf ball Swing Field to excess, packed Crowded Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Exhausted I'm so exhausted, I need to do more exercises.
Exhausted I don't want to go hiking, I'm too exhausted.
Exhausted Cooking is too exhausting, I want to get a delivery.
Hyper He is so hyper after eating all that sugar.
Hyper I never give my son chocolate, because he always ends up hyper after eating it.
Hyper I feel so hyper, I feel like smashing stuff.
Seesaw I love seesaws, they are so much fun.
Seesaw I fell off the seesaw, I don't ever want to go on one again.
Seesaw The fat kid always makes the other kid bounce off the seesaw.
Sandbox Look how dirty you are, were you playing in the sandbox?
Sandbox I found this watch in the sandbox, how lucky am I?
Sandbox I don't want you playing in the sandbox, the dog uses it as his toilet.
Swing I'm so bored today, let's go play on the swings.
Swing Dad, swing me higher, swing me faster.
Swing These swings are so old, look there is a hole in the swings.