The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To lift weights in order to make your muscles strong.
Pump iron.
A long metal rod to which heavy discs are attached at each end for weight lifting.
Barbell.
To hurt a muscle tendon or ligament by stretch.
Pull a muscle.
An exercise machine that consists of a continuous moving belt on which to walk or jog.
Treadmill.
Suggestions help.
Pointer.
An aerobic exercise that takes place on a specially designed stationary bicycle.
Spinning.
The size and shape of a person's body.
Physique.
An instrument or machine for weighing.
Scale.
Having a strong and muscular body or shape.
Ripped.
An exercise performed to work out the abdominal muscles.
Sit up.
Let's try that faster.
An exercise machine that consists of a continuous moving belt on which to walk or jog.
Treadmill.
Suggestions help.
Pointer.
To hurt a muscle tendon or ligament by stretch.
Pull a muscle.
An exercise performed to work out the abdominal muscles.
Sit up.
An aerobic exercise that takes place on a specially designed stationary bicycle.
Spinning.
Having a strong and muscular body or shape.
Ripped.
A long metal rod to which heavy discs are attached at each end for weight lifting.
Barbell.
To lift weights in order to make your muscles strong.
Pump iron.
The size and shape of a person's body.
Physique.
An instrument or machine for weighing.
Scale.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Pointer.
I'm going to give a presentation tomorrow.
Do you think you can give me a few pointers?
Pointer.
Here, let me give you a few pointers about learning English.
You gave me some great pointers.
They were really helpful.
Ripped.
For most guys in the gym, figuring out how to get ripped is a priority.
What do you think of guys that are ripped?
In my opinion, they aren't attractive.
Ripped.
Wow, you are really ripped.
What is your secret?
Pump iron.
I always listen to the soundtrack from Rocky when I'm at the gym pumping iron.
It's a good idea to pump iron regularly to maintain a healthy body.
Pump iron.
Pull a muscle.
Carl joined a gym recently.
He says he wants to pump iron and become ripped.
Pull a muscle.
Muscle strains, also called pulled muscles, are common sports injuries.
If you do not warm up before a physical activity, you can easily pull a muscle.
Pull a muscle.
Anyone can pull a muscle because of overuse, muscle fatigue, or through a fall.
Physique.
Research has found that male physiques with slim waists are rated as being attractive.
Many people believe Bruce Lee had one of the greatest physiques in modern history.
Physique.
It's a good idea to take vitamin supplements to maintain a healthy physique.