EnglishPod.com Yeah, I just moved here and I'd like to activate my cell phone and I'm not sure if I should go with a prepaid plan or a monthly rate plan.
I see.
Well, can I have a look at your phone?
Unfortunately this phone can't be used in the US.
It's not compatible with our 3G network.
What?
Really?
I don't really want to have to buy a new phone.
Well, you're in luck.
You see, if you sign up for our 3-year plan, we'll throw in a handset for free.
Really?
What's the catch?
There's no catch.
You just choose a plan, sign a 3-year contract, and that's it.
Actually, we're running a special promotion right now and we're giving away a BlackBerry Curve with our special MegaValue $40 plan.
So what does this plan include?
Well, you get 900 anytime minutes and you can also enjoy free mobile-to-mobile calling to other Tell Mobile clients, a thousand text messages per month, and unlimited evening and weekend minutes.
Oh, and we also offer a rollover option.
All this for $40 per month?
That's right.
Plus the activation fee and the emergency services fee, the monthly service fee, and any charges for extra minutes and...