The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
An object or machine made for a specific purpose.
Device A part of a cell phone package that lets you go on the internet.
Data package A computer chip you put in your cell phone.
A phone that attaches to the network by a wire.
Write and send a text message.
Cause something to start working.
Activate A program where you pay for cell phone time in advance.
Prepaid rate plan A program that needs you to pay every month.
Monthly rate plan Able to work well together.
Compatible with You are lucky right now.
We have what you need.
In luck Give something extra for free.
Throw in What is the hidden drawback?
What's the catch?
Cell phone time you can use at any time.
Any time minutes Short messages sent by mobile phone.
Text message Without limit, as much as you want.
Unlimited Cell phone minutes you can use on evenings and weekends.
Evening and weekend minutes Allow unused minutes to be used the next month.
Rollover Mobile phone Handset The amount of money you need to pay.
Fee The amount of money you need to pay.
Charge Let's try that faster!
Cause something to start working.
Activate Cell phone minutes you can use on evenings and weekends.
Evening and weekend minutes Short messages sent by mobile phone.
Text message What is the hidden drawback?
What's the catch?
You are lucky right now.
We have what you need.
In luck Allow unused minutes to be used the next month.
Rollover A part of a cell phone package that lets you go on the internet.
Data package The amount of money you need to pay.
Fee A computer chip you put in your cell phone.
SIM card Mobile phone Handset The amount of money you need to pay.
Charge Write and send a text message.
Text Give something extra for free.
Throw in Without limit, as much as you want.
Unlimited Cell phone time you can use at any time.
Any time minutes An object or machine made for a specific purpose.
Device A phone that attaches to the network by a wire.
Landline Able to work well together.
Compatible with A program that needs you to pay every month.
Monthly rate plan A program where you pay for cell phone time in advance.
Prepaid rate plan Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Compatible with Our application is compatible with most smartphones.
Compatible with My roommate and I are just not compatible.
All she ever does is study, and I like to stay up late and party.
Compatible with I'm sorry, your computer is not compatible with our software.
It's too old.
Throw in If you buy two pizzas, we'll throw in another one for free.
Throw in Tell you what, I'll buy this computer if you throw in a pair of headphones.
Deal?
Throw in The salesman threw in a subscription to the local newspaper for buying his product.
Isn't that great?
Activate In order to activate this computer software, you need to call customer service and get a code number.
Activate I received my credit card today.
I have to go to the bank and have it activated before I can use it.
Activate I want to activate an email account with Gmail, but I don't know how.
This is too good to be true.
There has to be a catch.
You're going to give me a free phone and three months of free service?
What's the catch?
Don't trust car salesmen.
There's always a catch with them.
In luck If you have a headache, you're in luck.
I have some Tylenol with me now.
In luck You're in luck.
I have the last copy of that book here.
In luck We're in luck.
I just found someone who can give us directions.
We're in luck.