The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Do something.
An action is required.
Don't just stand there.
Choose a place to sit.
Take a seat.
A short cut of hair to make one look clean.
Very fashionable.
Resembling silk, very smooth.
Having a smooth and bright appearance.
Shiny, very good to look great.
A million bucks, hair that grows on the sides of a man.
Sideburns, hair in form of round shape.
Curly, soft.
Fluffy.
Grow long.
Grow out.
A kind of hairstyle which very curly hair is formed into a round ball.
Afro.
A type of hairstyle where the hair is cut very short with an electric razor.
Buzz cut.
A hairstyle which consists of shaving both sides of the head, leaving a strip of noticeably longer hair on top.
Mohawk.
A type of hairstyle where the hair on top is left a bit long and styled upwards, resulting in square looking haircut.
Flat top.
A hairstyle in which most or all of the hair on the head is pulled away from the face, gathered and secured at the back of the head with a hair tie or clip, and allowed to hang freely from that point.
Ponytail.
Formed by intertwining three or more strands of hair so that the result is similar to a woven textile.
Braid.
Let's try that faster!
A shortcut of hair to make one look clean.
Trim.
A type of hairstyle where the hair on top is left a bit long and styled upwards, resulting in square looking haircut.
Flat top.
Hair that grows on the sides of a man.
Sideburns.
A kind of hairstyle which very curly hair is formed into a round ball.
Afro.
Hair in form of round shape.
Curly.
Very fashionable.
Fancy.
Grow long.
Grow out.
Having a smooth and bright appearance.
Shiny.
A type of hairstyle where the hair is cut very short with an electric razor.
Buzz cut.
Resembling silk.
Very smooth.
Silky.
Hairstyle in which most or all of the hair on the head is pulled away from the face, gathered and secured at the back of the head with a hair tie or clip, and allowed to hang freely from that point.
Ponytail.
Very good.
To look great.
A million bucks.
Formed by intertwining three or more strands of hair so that the result is similar to a woven textile.
Braid.
Soft.
Fluffy.
A hairstyle which consists of shaving both sides of the head, leaving a strip of noticeably longer hair on top.
Mohawk.
Choose a place to sit.
Take a seat.
Do something.
An action is required.
Don't just stand there.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Help me take these boxes into the house.
Don't just stand there.
The house is on fire.
Call the fire department.
Don't just stand there.
Don't just stand there in the rain.
Come inside.
Fancy.
He was practicing some very fancy tricks on his bike.
When I dance, I don't like to try any fancy moves.
Fancy.
That was some very fancy driving.
How did you do it?
Shiny.
Wow.
I really like your shiny new shoes.
They look great.
Shiny.
Your engagement ring is beautiful.
The diamond is so shiny.
Shiny.
I like the paint color of your new car.
It's so shiny.
A million bucks.
That dress is amazing.
You look like a million bucks.
A million bucks.
I really like how you painted your house.
It really looks like a million bucks.
A million bucks.
After getting no surgery, he really looks like a million bucks.
Fluffy.
I love the fluffy white fur on my rabbit.
It's so cute.
Fluffy.
I need to have a fluffy pillow to sleep at night.
Susan has really nice hair.
Her curls are fluffy and beautiful.