EnglishPod.com Look in a digital world even the strongest must fight for survival Two people possess a secret so valuable, so powerful, they have to defend it at all costs.
I don't care where they are, I don't care what it takes.
You find them and bring them to me.
They only had one chance and their chance was to fight back.
With a little help from the governor, nothing will prevent them from doing their job.
Double the action, get down, triple the excitement, get down again.
This summer, nothing will stand in their way.
I'm going to make them an offer again with you.
Two hosts, one podcast.
EnglishPod.
Coming to a theater near you.