The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Succeed in making the finding of a jury in a trial.
Reach a verdict.
Responsible for doing something bad.
Guilty.
A respectful title used to or of certain judges.
Your honour.
A body of persons sworn to judge.
Jury.
To charge someone with a crime.
Accuse of.
To do something, usually a crime.
Commit.
The lawyers against the defendant.
Prosecution.
One who steals from pockets.
Pickpocket.
A declaration of truth or fact.
Testimony.
The person being sued or accused.
Defendant.
People affected by a painful or sad experience.
Victim.
Not guilty.
Innocent.
Refer to something that is not suitable.
So-called.
Something that shows the thing is true.
Evidence.
One who is called on to testify before a court.
Witness.
Let's try that faster.
To do something, usually a crime.
Commit.
A body of persons sworn to judge.
Refer to something that is not suitable.
So-called.
Responsible for doing something bad.
Guilty.
A declaration of truth or fact.
Testimony.
One who steals from pockets.
Pickpocket.
The lawyers against the defendant.
Prosecution.
Something that shows the thing is true.
Evidence.
To charge someone with a crime.
Accuse of.
One who is called on to testify before a court.
Witness.
The person being sued or accused.
Defendant.
Not guilty.
Innocent.
Succeed in making the finding of a jury in a trial.
Reach a verdict.
People affected by a painful or sad experience.
Victim.
A respectful title used to or of certain judges.
Your honor.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Accuse of.
Martha accused me of stealing her boyfriend.
This man is being accused with murder.
Accuse of.
The teacher accused the students of being lazy.
Testimony.
In your testimony, you stated that you were there at the moment of the crime.
The witness gave her testimony in court today.
Testimony.
The judge discarded her testimony since it was inaccurate.
So-called.
I have to go to my so-called job today.
I hate it.
So-called.
I was betrayed by my so-called best friend.
My so-called supervisor makes me do all the work while he is on the phone all day.
Reach a verdict.
The jury has reached a verdict and we find the defendant not guilty.
We disagree with the verdict and will appeal to the court's decision today.
Reach a verdict.
The judge still hasn't reached a verdict in this case.
Evidence.
There is evidence of life on Mars.
The forensic scientists recollect and analyse evidence found at the scene of the crime.
Evidence.
There is no evidence that proves your theory.