EnglishPod.com.
Your Honor, ladies and gentlemen of the jury, my client, Robert Malone, has been accused of a crime he did not commit.
The prosecution has accused my client of being a pickpocket.
I know we have heard the testimony of many people here today.
People who claimed the defendant, my client, stole their wallets.
I feel sorry for these victims, I really do.
But my client is innocent.
Let's look at the facts.
Number one, these so-called witnesses did not actually see the defendant steal anything.
Number two, when the police stopped him, he did not have any of the stolen wallets.
There is no evidence.
Therefore, ladies and gentlemen of the jury, I ask you to think carefully before giving your verdict.
Look at the facts.
Look at the evidence.
My client is innocent.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury, have you reached a verdict?
Yes, Your Honor.
Our verdict is not guilty.
Thank you so much.
You were great.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You're welcome, Robert.
I knew you were innocent, so my job was easy.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Thanks once again.
Hey, where's my wallet?