EnglishPod.com Hi ladies, thanks for picking me up.
It's awful weather out there.
Absolutely.
It's been raining for hours.
How are you, Melissa?
Are you okay?
I'm great, thanks Mr.
Campbell.
Do you have any business trips planned soon, Mr.
Campbell?
Of course, I'm always traveling.
I'll leave for London next Monday and then I'll fly to Boston from there.
It's going to be a busy month.
How about you, Michelle?
Do you have any vacation plans?
Yes, Mike and I will travel to Beijing to see Mike's parents for the Spring Festival and hopefully next year we will visit London.
I hear it's a wonderful city.
I couldn't agree more.
London is really fantastic.
It's my favorite city.
I'm sure you'll have a great time.