The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
holiday vacation to a complete degree absolutely really bad awful to have something set to do in the future plan a day or time of religious or other celebration festival let's try that faster to a complete degree absolutely to have something set to do in the future plan holiday vacation really bad awful a day or time of religious or other celebration festival now say the word and hear it in a sentence vacation I can't wait to go on vacation.
I've been working hard for this.
vacation It's our first vacation overseas.
We are really excited.
vacation on our last vacation, it rained all the time.
absolutely Do you believe in God?
Absolutely.
There is no doubt in my mind.
absolutely Should we go buy a pet bear?
Absolutely.
Maybe I should say sorry to my friend.
Absolutely not.
Awful.
That movie was just awful.
I want my money back.
Awful.
You truly are an awful person.
Don't talk to me.
Awful.
My last vacation to that place was an awful experience.
I never want to go back.
Have you seen the local festival?
It's great to watch.
festival Chinese festivals are always so colourful and noisy.
festival I heard Japan has some crazy festivals.
I want to see them.
plan Do you have anything planned for the weekend?
plan I need to plan a holiday.
I'm too stressed.
plan I have a plan to buy some penguins.