EnglishPod.com Okay, I'm ready for my driving lesson.
Should I start the car?
Hold on there, Fiddy Paldi.
First, let's go over things one more time.
Now, before you even think of starting the car, make sure your seat is at a comfortable position and you can grip the steering wheel firmly.
Next, check your rear-view mirrors to make sure you can see properly.
We've been through this a million times.
Let's get going already.
I'm ready.
Fine.
Start the car.
Okay, now gently step on the clutch and shift to first gear.
Good.
Now accelerate gently and let go of the clutch as you do it.
There we go.
Good.
I'm doing it.
I'm driving.
This is awesome.
Let's turn some music on.
Keep your eyes on the road.
No music.
We are coming up to a red light.
Step on the brakes.
What are you doing?
I said the brakes.
Look out for those people.
Get off the sidewalk.
Get out of my way.
This is just like playing video games.
It's the police.
Pull over.
They'll never take me alive.