EnglishPod.com Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Carrie, are you okay?
You seem a bit down.
I just got off the phone with my boyfriend.
He's always getting upset and losing his temper over nothing.
It's so hard to talk to him at times.
Maybe it's just that he's stressed out from working or something.
He does have a pretty nerve-wracking job, you know.
Yeah, but he's always in a really foul mood.
I try to find out what's bothering him, or get him to talk about his day, but he always shuts down and brushes me off.
Men are like that, you know.
They can feel nervous, anxious, or on edge, and the only way they can express it is by trying to hide it through aggressiveness.
I guess you're right.
What do you think I should do?
He wasn't always as grouchy, you know.
Talk to him, try to cheer him up when he's down, and if that doesn't work, I say get rid of him and get a new one.
You are something else, you know that.