The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Feeling sad, not happy.
Down in the dumps.
Sad or unhappy.
Down Having sad feelings or emotions.
Have the blues.
To feel very worried or anxious.
Stress out.
To fluster, unnerved.
Rattled.
Causing a person to feel very nervous.
Nerve-wracking.
Makes me angry, upsets me.
Grinds my gears.
Refuses to talk about something with someone.
Brushed me off.
Upset, very angry.
Pissed off.
To make someone happier.
Cheer up.
Let's try that faster.
Causing a person to feel very nervous.
Nerve-wracking.
Sad or unhappy.
Down.
Having sad feelings or emotions.
Have the blues.
Refused to talk about something with someone.
Brushed me off.
Upset, very angry.
Pissed off.
Feeling sad, not happy.
Down in the dumps.
To fluster, unnerved.
Rattled.
Makes me angry, upsets me.
Grinds my gears.
To make someone happier.
Cheer up.
To feel very worried or anxious.
Stress out.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Down.
Ben is feeling a bit down today since his girlfriend broke up with him.
Are you okay?
You seem down today.
Down.
Whenever I'm feeling down, I go out with my friends and then I feel much better.
Stress out.
David has been really stressed out lately.
His boss is putting a lot of pressure on him in his new job.
Stress out.
I can't talk right now.
I'm stressed out about this exam I have tomorrow.
If I don't pass it, my dad is going to kill me.
Stress out.
Are you okay?
You seem to be really stressed out lately.
What's going on?
Nerve-wracking.
I think being a doctor is one of the most nerve-wracking jobs in the world.
Sky-diving was one of the most nerve-wracking experiences of my life.
I almost had a heart attack.
Nerve-wracking.
The final match between Brazil and Italy was incredibly nerve-wracking.
Brush me off.
When she told me my project would be a better television film than a feature film, I thought she was brushing me off.
I asked her out on a date many times, but she always brushed me off making sure that my project was better than a feature film.
Brush me off.
Carolyn went to the doctor without an appointment, and the receptionist brushed her off and told her to come back the next day.
Cheer up.
I hate it when people try to cheer me up when I feel sad.
I just want to be left alone.
Cheer up.
I don't know what else to do.
I've tried everything to cheer Mandy up, but she won't stop crying.
Cheer up.
You know what really cheers me up when I'm sad?
Shopping.