The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Application A telecommunication system Network Place with internet connectivity Hotspot A phone with wireless internet capacity Smartphone Management system Android OS Let's try that faster!
Place with internet connectivity Hotspot By accident Accidentally Management system Android OS A phone with wireless internet capacity Smartphone Advanced, fashionable Lead A telecommunication system Network Software program Application Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Accidentally I accidentally scratched his car with my bike.
Accidentally They accidentally left the lights on while they were on vacation.
Accidentally How can a person accidentally burn their house down?
Application With this application you can see which restaurants are nearby your current location.
Application I've downloaded many free applications, but I can never justify buying pay applications.
Application He designs iPhone applications for a technology company.
Network All of the computers in this office are connected by a network.
Network Our brains are a system of nerves and connections that control all of our body's processes.
Network Wireless The wireless network is down.
Can you pass me that cable so I can connect to the internet?
Hotspot He is always checking his emails.
He only goes to restaurants with wireless hotspots.
Hotspot This cafe is perfect.
All you can drink coffee and a wireless hotspot.
Hotspot I have to find a wireless hotspot in this airport so I can send out an email right away.
Smartphone Apple's iPhone revolutionized the smartphone industry.
Smartphone I'd really like to buy a smartphone, but they're almost as expensive as a laptop computer.
Smartphone Buying a smartphone has made my life much more convenient.
I don't have to bring my computer with me everywhere now.
Thanks for watching!