EnglishPod.com Good afternoon, passport and arrival card please.
Here you are.
Where are you coming from?
China.
Is this your country of birth or residence?
I just work there.
What is the purpose of your visit to the United States?
I'm here on vacation.
How long do you plan to stay in the United States?
Almost three weeks.
Sir, you didn't fill out the information on your arrival card of where you'll be staying.
Oh, I'm sorry, but there are a couple different places I will travel to within the United States, so I wasn't sure what to put.
You must specify an address on the place where you will spend most of your time.
Okay.
Here you are.
Do you have enough means to support yourself while you're here?
Yes, I have some traveler's checks and two credit cards.
Very good.
Do you have anything to declare?
Nope, I only have my clothes and camera.
Very well, sir.
Welcome to the United States.
Enjoy your visit.