The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A plastic protective piece placed inside the mouth to protect the teeth.
Mouthguard Causes horror or disgust.
Gruesome To prepare to fight.
Square off Shorts worn for swimming or athletics.
Trunks Land Land An elasticated belt with a pouch to support the genitals.
Worn by male athletes.
Jockstrap Avoid being hit by something.
Dodges A quick strong blow with the head.
Headbutt Hit hard multiple times.
Pounded An illegal blow below the waist.
Low blow Let's try that faster.
To prepare to fight.
Square off Hit hard multiple times.
Pounded Land Land An illegal blow below the waist.
Low blow Causes horror or disgust.
Gruesome A quick strong blow with the head.
Headbutt An elasticated belt with a pouch to support the genitals.
Worn by male athletes.
Jockstrap Avoid being hit by something.
Dodges Shorts worn for swimming or athletics.
Trunks A plastic protective piece placed inside the mouth to protect the teeth.
Mouthguard Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Gruesome Last night's match was one of the most gruesome fights I've ever seen.
Both fighters were bleeding heavily.
Gruesome Wow, that is one gruesome looking cut.
You might need to go to the doctor and get some help.
Cut stitches Gruesome The police describe the scene of the crime in gruesome detail.
Square off The two countries are moving their armies close to the borders as they prepare to square off in a border dispute.
Square off Italy and Brazil are squaring off in the final game this afternoon.
Square off Lisa and Daniel squared off against each other in the marketing meeting today.
They were both pretty angry.
Wow, Apollo just landed an oppressive right hook to Rocky's ribs.
That's going to hurt.
Land.
Hey, I didn't lose too badly in the fight yesterday.
I landed a few good punches here and there.
Land.
Land an uppercut while he moves closer to you and you will be sure to win the fight.
Dodges.
See that guy dodging through the traffic?
He's going to get hit by a car if he's not careful.
Dodges.
Well, the storm turned south so it looks like we managed to dodge a bullet.
Look, you're the one who is in charge of sales and the numbers are down.
It's your problem so stop trying to dodge your responsibilities.
Pounded.
If you say one more thing about my mother, I'm going to pound you.
Rocky was knocked out in the fifth round.
He was getting pounded all night long.
Pounded.
I don't think that movie is going to win any awards.
It was pounded by the critics.