EnglishPod.com Rocky Balboa square off against his lifetime rival Apollo Creed.
This will be a gruesome match for sure.
Both fighters are in the ring and we are about to begin.
In the blue corner, weighing in at 220 pounds, the former heavyweight champion of the world, the master of disaster, the one and only Apollo Creed.
In the red corner, weighing 218 pounds and with a record of 47 wins and 37 knockouts, the undefeated, undisputed heavyweight champion of the world, the Italian Stallion, Rocky Balboa.
There's the bell and this fight is underway.
Apollo quickly attacks Rocky with quick, strong jabs.
Rocky dodges successfully and counter attacks with a strong right hook.
Apollo is cut.
Rocky landed a strong blow to his right eyebrow and cut him.
This is his chance.
Rocky quickly throws a left, right, another left.
Apollo is getting pounded.
Apollo recovers with a powerful haymaker and catches Rocky off guard.
He's down.
The ref starts the count.
One, two, three, four, five.