The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
The sister of one's father or mother.
Aunt.
A son of one's husband or wife by a previous marriage.
Stepson.
A woman who was formerly a particular man's wife.
Ex-wife.
Let's try that faster.
A brother of one's father or mother.
Uncle.
A male sibling.
Brother.
A woman who was formerly a particular man's wife.
Ex-wife.
A son of one's husband or wife by a previous marriage.
Stepson.
The sister of one's father or mother.
Aunt.
The son or daughter of an uncle or aunt.
Cousin.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Ex-wife.
My ex-wife is really crazy.
Maybe I should move away.
Ex-wife.
There is a reason why you are my ex-wife and that is because you annoy me so much.
My ex-wife got all of my money in the divorce settlement.
Cousin.
My cousin is coming over to my place for a vacation.
I can't wait to go hunting with him.
Cousin.
I think I'm falling in love with my cousin.
What should I do?
Cousin.
My cousin is so annoying.
I can't believe I'm related to him.
Uncle.
My uncle is so funny and wacky.
I wish he came over more often.
Uncle.
She has this uncle who always drinks too much alcohol at Christmas time.
My uncle lives in New York so I can always get free accommodation.
Stepson.
It's very hard to have a stepson as I don't know how I should discipline him.
My friend told me his stepson never calls him dad.
Stepson.
My stepson is always making trouble just because I'm not his real dad.
Aunt.
My aunt always brings me a present when she comes over.
Her aunt is so kind.
She always makes me a cup of tea.
Aunt.
I can't believe my aunt tried to steal my husband from me.