The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A specified place to practice shooting.
Shooting range.
Object to be aimed at in shooting practice.
Target.
A small gun with a container for bullets.
Revolver.
To look at something carefully.
Inspect.
Let's try that faster.
A specified place to practice shooting.
Shooting range.
To look at something carefully.
Inspect.
A small gun with a container for bullets.
Revolver.
Object to be aimed at in shooting practice.
Target.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Shooting range.
I went to the shooting range last week and shot myself in the foot.
Before you can be efficient with a gun, you must practice at the shooting range.
Shooting range.
To attend this shooting range, you must be a member.
Revolver.
My grandfather has an old revolver from the Civil War.
That police officer is old school.
He still carries a revolver.
Revolver.
I prefer a revolver over any other pistol because it's easier to handle.
Target.
Try to hit the target right in the middle to improve your aim.
Don't shoot the target that looks like an old lady.
Target.
Shoot all the targets that have a criminal holding a gun.
Inspect.
Before opening the restaurant, the kitchen must be inspected.
He forgot the gun needed to be inspected and he almost shot himself.
Inspect.
He inspected the engine before he bought the car.