EnglishPod.com Hey, Michel.
Jump in quick.
It's pouring out there.
Oh, hi Melissa.
Are you going to the conference too?
I was planning to pick up Mr.
Campbell.
Yes, he told me.
We need to pick him up at his hotel and then go to the conference.
Oh, I see.
Okay, so I heard you got married.
Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
I'm very excited.
We were going to get married next year, but then we decided to get married on holiday instead.
It was wonderful.
That sounds so romantic.
Jack and I were hoping to get married in Europe next year, but we had to postpone our plans.
We just don't have the money.
I know what you mean.
I think Shanghai is getting more and more expensive.
Don't you?
I sure do.
In my opinion, it's actually becoming more expensive than back home.
Definitely.
Oh, there's Mr.
Campbell.
Driver, can you stop here, please?