EnglishPod.com I'm so relieved that your ankle wasn't broken.
I feel just awful about this whole thing.
I want to make it up to you.
Let me take you out to dinner tonight, my treat.
Oh, that sounds great.
I'd love to.
Here's my address.
Pick me up at eight?
Perfect.
Thank you for such a lovely evening.
The food was amazing and I had a great time.
Me too.
You look so beautiful tonight.
I wish this night would never end.
There's something that I have to tell you.
But what is it?
I woke up today thinking that this would be just like any other day.
But I was wrong.
The twist of fate brought us together.
I crashed into your life and you into mine.
This may sound crazy, but I'm falling in love with you, Veronica.