The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Relaxed and happy that something difficult has been stopped.
Relieved Do something good as a balance to a bad or hurtful action.
Make it up.
I will pay.
My treat.
Go somewhere in order to get someone or something.
Pick up.
Normal.
Ordinary.
Unplanned events that have a big impact on the future.
Twist of fate.
Hit something causing serious damage.
Crash.
Start being in love.
Fall in love.
Go on a date.
Invite or ask someone to go on a date.
Invite.
Ask you out.
Invite someone to go and do something.
Take you out.
Decline an invitation.
Turn down.
An expression to show excitement about something.
Look forward to.
Be in a relationship with someone.
See someone.
Flirt.
Let's try that faster.
I will pay.
My treat.
Normal.
Ordinary.
Hit something causing serious damage.
Crash.
Go on a date.
Decline an invitation.
Turn down.
Invite or ask someone to go on a date.
Ask you out.
An expression to show excitement about something.
Look forward to.
Go somewhere in order to get someone or something.
Pick up.
Relaxed and happy that something difficult has been stopped.
Relieved.
Start being in love.
Fall in love.
Invite someone to go and do something.
Take you out.
Do something good as a balance to a bad or hurtful action.
Make it up.
Unplanned events that have a big impact on the future.
Twist of fate.
Flirt.
Be in a relationship with someone.
See someone.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Relieved.
They were relieved to hear that the company would not be making any layoffs.
I'm so relieved to hear your voice.
I was worried something happened to you.
Relieved.
She was relieved to know that she didn't have cancer.
Make it up.
I'm sorry I forgot your birthday.
How can I make it up to you?
Make it up.
I feel terrible for calling your mother fat.
I want to make it up to her so I got her these flowers.
Make it up.
John forgot our anniversary again.
He's going to have to make it up to me.
Pick up.
The dinner is at seven tonight so we'll pick you up at six o'clock.
Are you going to pick her up on the way home?
Pick up.
Sorry but I cannot pick you up today.
I have to go somewhere else.
Ordinary.
It was just an ordinary day at work.
Nothing special happened.
Ordinary.
We had the ordinary problems that you find when starting a new business.
Ordinary people can't afford to buy Hummers.
Crash.
Watch out.
You're going to crash into that tree.
Crash.
On my way to work this morning I was looking at my phone and I crashed right into a telephone pole.
I saw a bush crashing into a car this morning.
Luckily no one was injured.
Fall in love.
This guy is such a gentleman.
I feel like I'm falling in love with him.
Fall in love.
After their first date she totally fell in love with him.