EnglishPod.com You want to go get a facial with me today?
Dude, what are you talking about?
Only girls do that.
Not at all.
Guys also get facials.
Manicures and pedicures.
There's nothing wrong with looking after your skin and looking good.
True.
So what should they do to you at your beauty spa?
Well, first they exfoliate my face, getting rid of all the dead skin.
Then I get a face mask with nutrients that keep my skin healthy and young.
Afterwards, they apply some moisturizer and you leave feeling like a million bucks.
That doesn't really sound like something I would be interested in.
In any case, I just wash my face every night and use sunscreen during the day.
Well, you should come with me one day.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Uh, no.