The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A treatment to beautify the face.
Facial.
A cosmetic treatment of the hands and fingernails, including trimming and polishing of the nails.
Menocure.
Professional care and treatment of the feet.
Pedicure.
A luxurious resort or result hotel.
Spa.
To remove the surface of something, such as skin and dirt.
Exfoliate.
A substance formulated to prevent sunburn, skin cancers and other conditions caused by excessive exposure to the sun.
Sunscreen.
Let's try that faster.
A cosmetic treatment of the hands and fingernails, including trimming and polishing of the nails.
Menocure.
A substance formulated to prevent sunburn, skin cancers and other conditions caused by excessive exposure to the sun.
Sunscreen.
A treatment to beautify the face.
Facial.
A luxurious resort or result hotel.
Spa.
To remove the surface of something, such as skin and dirt.
Exfoliate.
Professional care and treatment of the feet.
Pedicure.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sunscreen.
Don't forget to put some sunscreen on today.
I forgot to put my sunscreen on and now I'm sunburn everywhere.
Sunscreen.
If you don't put sunscreen on you could get skin cancer.
Exfoliate.
I have a lot of dry skin, maybe I need to exfoliate.
It's good to exfoliate once in a while to let your face freshen up.
Exfoliate.
I like to exfoliate my skin with a hot rock.
Facial.
Hey girlfriend, do you feel like getting a facial?
I'm so stressed at work, I need to get a facial and relax.
Facial.
I look so young because I get a facial every week.
Manicure.
Your nails are really long, maybe you should get a manicure.
I think I'll get a manicure before my wedding.
Manicure.
My husband loves it when I get a manicure.
Pedicure.
Your toes are disgusting, you need to get a pedicure.
I think if I get a pedicure I won't be afraid to walk along the beach.
Pedicure.
If I get a pedicure I can play sport again without hurting my toes.
Thanks for watching!