The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Great snow.
Blizzard.
A prolonged period of scanty rainfall.
Drought.
A very big rain and windstorm.
Hurricane.
A large sea wave produced by an earthquake.
Tsunami.
Something tech relating to or caused by an earthquake.
Seismic activity.
Let's try that faster.
A very big rain and windstorm.
Hurricane.
A prolonged period of scanty rainfall.
Drought.
Something tech relating to or caused by an earthquake.
Seismic activity.
Great snow.
Blizzard.
A large sea wave produced by an earthquake.
Tsunami.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Blizzard.
With the blizzard came strong gusts of wind.
Freezing temperatures.
And near zero visibility because of all the blowing snow.
Blizzard.
The blizzard warning will remain in effect until tomorrow morning.
When the winds will die down to about 30 kilometers per hour.
Blizzard.
If you really need to venture out into that blizzard with your car.
You're going to have to go at a crawl.
Because of the near whiteout conditions and the danger of drifting.
Drought.
The lack of rain in the spring and the above average temperatures caused a drought in the late summer.
We have to start conserving water because of the drought.
Drought.
For about half a decade in the 1930s.
The prairies in Canada and the United States experienced a severe drought.
During which there were numerous dust storms and the land became a wasteland.
Hurricane.
Several mudslides occurred in this region shortly after the hurricane passed through.
North Atlantic hurricanes are formed off the tip of Africa.
Build as they travel across the Atlantic Ocean.
And then finally hit the Caribbean and the southern United States at full force.
Hurricane.
The weather became very calm all of a sudden.
And we knew that the eye of the hurricane was passing over us.
Seismic activity.
He measured the earthquakes using a seismograph and noticed the increase in seismic activity.
Seismic activity can cause new land masses to form.
And the destruction of others.
Seismic activity.
The seismic activity caused earthquakes, volcanic eruptions and multiple tsunamis.
Tsunami.
When there is a massive earthquake on the ocean floor, a lot of water is displaced.
Forming a tsunami as this water travels towards land.
Tsunami.
Indian Ocean Tsunami.
The Indian Ocean tsunami in 2004 was caused by one of the largest earthquakes ever recorded.
Tsunami.
She looked out over the land, still flooded in areas by water left by the tsunami that had ravaged her home just days before.