Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A temporary fashion or notion.
Fad.
A wolf with extraordinary strength.
Werewolves.
A dead corpse likes to eat brain.
Zombie.
Live forever.
Immortal.
To lead on by exciting hope or desire.
Entice.
Cool, fashionable.
Hip.
Extraordinary power.
Superhuman strength.
Let's try that faster.
Cool, fashionable.
Hip.
Movie.
A dead person who sucks the blood of a living person.
Vampire.
Live forever.
Immortal.
A story.
Tale.
A temporary fashion or notion.
Fad.
A wolf with extraordinary strength.
Werewolves.
Extraordinary power.
Superhuman strength.
A dead corpse likes to eat brain.
Zombie.
To lead on by exciting hope or desire.
Entice.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Fad.
The fad was to wear purple shoes.
So my dad bought purple shoes too.
Fad.
The yo-yo is a big fad.
It will be unpopular in a year.
Fad.
I'm not going to follow the fad.
I will do my own thing.
Entice.
I like to entice my brother to do the laundry by the allure of money.
Can I entice you with some chocolate?
Entice.
I was enticed to the bar by the offer of free drinks.
Hip.
My dad thinks he is so hip.
Maybe ten years ago.
Hip.
Have you seen that new hip show?
He is so hip.
Everyone wants to be like him.
Tail.
My dad likes to tell the tale of how he caught the biggest fish.
My brother is always telling the tall tale that he is an alien.
Tail.
My favourite tale is of vampires.
Immortal.
Nothing in this life is immortal except maybe a vampire.
After winning the race, he felt immortal.
Immortal.
The spider just won't die.
It's immortal.