EnglishPod.com Hi there, can I help you folks?
I'm just browsing, seeing what's on the lot.
My daughter wants a car for her birthday, you know how it is.
Dad!
I'm 16 already, and I'm like the only one at school who doesn't have a car.
She's right, you know.
Kids these days all have cars.
Let me show you something we just got in.
A 1996 sedan, excellent gas mileage.
It has dual airbags and anti-light brakes, a perfect vehicle for a young driver.
Dad, I love it!
It's awesome!
Can we get this one please?
I see, what can you tell me about this one?
Oh, that's just an old World War II tank that we use for TV commercials.
Now about this sedan...
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
Tell me more about this tank.
Well, sir, if you are looking for quality and safety, then look no further.
Three inches of reinforced steel protect your daughter from short-range missile attacks.
Does the sedan protect her from missile attacks?
It does not.
Well, I don't know.
Let me sleep on it.
Did I mention the tank is a tank?
I'll take it!
Dad!