EnglishPod.com Hi, I'm looking for a pair of shoes for my son.
Sure thing.
Here we are.
If you're looking for dress shoes, we have several different styles of Oxford for boys.
We also carry athletic shoes, hiking boots...
Oh, Jacob, how about these sneakers?
Mom, they've got Velcro!
Well, then how about these?
What is this style called?
They're tennis shoes.
They're very popular with teens and young adults.
Oh, Mom, can I get these?
What are those?
They're Chuck Taylors.
Everyone has them.
Can I please?
I don't know.
Would they go with your clothes?
The backs are really high and the way the tongue just sticks up, they're almost like a boot.
And the sole doesn't look like it would have a very good grip.
They're only $45.
And they've got cool fluorescent orange shoelaces.
Mom!
Okay, try them on.
What size are your feet?
Here's a size 9.
We'll try a size 43 on you first and see how that fits.
A what?
They come in European sizes.
He should be a size 43.
I'll be right back.