The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A shoe used as a component of formal wear.
Dress shoe A canvas shoe with a pliable rubber sole.
Tennis shoe The flap of material under the laces of a shoe.
Tongue A way of grasping and holding firmly.
Grip A long, thin material used for fastening a shoe.
Shoelaces The underside of footwear.
Sole Let's try that faster.
The underside of footwear.
Sole The flap of material under the laces of a shoe.
Tongue A way of grasping and holding firmly.
Grip A long, thin material used for fastening a shoe.
Shoelaces A shoe used as a component of formal wear.
Dress shoe A canvas shoe with a pliable rubber sole.
Tennis shoe Tennis shoe Tennis shoe I love tennis shoes because they're comfortable.
I can wear them every day and when I go out they still look great.
Tennis shoe Tennis shoes used to be very plain, but now they come in many different colors and many different styles.
Tennis shoe My tennis shoes are old and ratty, but I still love them.
Tongue I put my foot back in my sneaker, pulled up the tongue, tightened my laces, and I kept on running.
Tongue The tongues of these shoes keep falling down.
Tongue The shoe tongue is supposed to keep the laces from rubbing against the foot.
Sole The soles of my shoes were starting to wear down.
Sole I went to the cobbler and got him to put rubber soles on my shoes.
Sole After dancing for several hours, the soles of my feet were sore.
Grip My new sneakers have a much better grip than my old ones.
Grip My shoes lost their grip and I slipped on the polished floor.
Grip As I was climbing the tree, I lost my grip, fell, and broke my arm.
Shoelaces In the Olympics, the shoelaces of one figure skater broke in the middle of his performance.
Shoelaces My brother got me pink shoelaces with Hello Kitty on them for my birthday.
Shoelaces My mom tightened my shoelaces, made a knot, and then told me to go play outside.
Thanks for watching!