EnglishPod.com Now of course with all this cutting edge technology there must be a catch you might ask yourself.
I bet the retail price will be too much for most consumers you might say.
Well you'd be wrong.
Yes of course the X420 is aimed at the luxury market but if you compare the price of our leading competitors the X420 represents incredible value for money.
At only 15,000 RMB it is far more affordable and far more attractive than almost every leading brand and model.
So what differentiates us from our competitors?
Well if we compare Orange's luxury MP40 range then we can really highlight some of the differences.
Now of course Orange has an enviable record for producing revolutionary and top class products and I must admit the MP40 is a breathtaking machine.
However for most consumers the MP40 is simply far too expensive to consider.
Compared with the X420 it is more expensive and there's no doubt that considering the quality and workmanship that goes into the X420 we really win hands down on value for money.
Also if you compare the after-sales service we offer I think we can proudly boast the best customer service facilities in the whole laptop sector.
As opposed to most of our rivals we guarantee quality, we guarantee service and we guarantee reliability.
The questions we must ask ourselves are what does the Alpha brand stand for and also how can we set ourselves apart from our competitors?
The answer to both of these question is the same my friends.
Alpha stands first and foremost for quality, for excellence and for service.
If we always stick to this philosophy then I'm confident that we will really be able to expand our market share significantly.
Okay let me move on now to give you an idea of our marketing campaign for the X420.