EnglishPod.com Well, everyone, I'm sure you'd like to join me in thanking Michael for what was a really inspirational presentation.
Sincere thanks, Michael.
Now, I'm sure many of you will be keen to ask some questions, so I'd like to open up a Q&A session.
Please raise your hand if you have any questions at all.
Yes, Janice, go ahead.
Yes, thank you, Jonathan.
I would just like to go back to the comment Mr.
Ford made in regards to our competitors, particularly Orange.
Now, as you know, Orange has established themselves as the market leader in the high-end laptop market.
How does Mr.
Ford expect to compete with a company that has such a huge reputation and huge resources?
Well, Janice, first of all, thanks for a very good question.
I think you have hit the nail on the head, actually.
Orange are the global leaders precisely because of their size and power.
But although we can't compete in terms of size, I do believe we hold an advantage in terms of dedication to customer service.
Yes, I admit this is a David and Goliath battle, but don't forget who won that contest.
Mr.
Ford, could you elaborate on the actual technical details of the X420 a little more?
I'd love to, but I think we're a little pressed for time right now.
However, Jonathan has all the technical specs for you on the PowerPoint presentation, which you can look over in your own time.
Mr.
Ford, one final question.
Would you like to join me for a game of golf this Sunday?