EnglishPod.com Hi Daniel, how are you holding up?
I'm greatly sorry for your loss.
Thank you, I'm doing much better.
I've begun organizing everything for the funeral.
How's that going?
It's a lot harder than I imagined.
There are many things that you have to arrange.
I booked a time and date with the funeral home, but I still have a lot of things to do.
Have you bought a burial plot and a casket?
No, Wendy is being cremated.
She always talked about how she didn't want to be buried.
I already chose a cremation urn and we plan to spread the ashes in the ocean.
I see.
That sounds like something she would have really liked.
I'm sure the memorial service will be tasteful.
You're doing a great job.
Thanks.
It hasn't been easy, but luckily we have life insurance and Wendy left behind a detailed will that will sort out any other legal matters.