The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Continue to live through hardship.
Hold up.
The act of burying, especially the internment of a dead body.
Burial.
Burn up something and reduce to ash.
Cremate.
Being in keeping with good taste.
Tasteful.
Having many details.
Detail.
Continue to live through hardship.
Hold up.
Having many details.
Burn up something and reduce to ash.
Cremate.
Being in keeping with good taste.
The act of burying, especially the internment of a dead body.
Burial.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Hold up.
Craig is holding up well after the surgery.
He continued to hold up even with all the stress.
Hold up.
Our family is having a difficult time holding up after my father's death.
Burial.
Burial plot are expensive in Japan.
My parents bought burial plot that are next to each other.
Burial.
Each burial plot in our cemetery has an individual ID number.
Cremate.
Cremation is more and more popular these days.
I want to be cremated when I die.
Cremate.
Many people choose to be cremated nowadays.
Tasteful.
This is a very tasteful color you use for your home.
I think that this place is charming and tasteful.
Tasteful.
The wedding we attended was elegant and tasteful.
Detail.
There are detailed instructions on how to assemble the computer.
Mike left detailed contact information in case you need to contact him.
Detail.
This book contains detailed information about Italy.