EnglishPod.com Dad!
Dad!
Wake up!
It's Christmas!
Timmy, it's too early for this.
Look, it's six in the morning.
Go back to bed.
No way!
Santa already came and left all our presents.
Can we go open them, please?
Please?
Of course we can, honey.
Bill, come on, get dressed.
Fine.
Not like Santa brought me any gifts.
Bill, honestly, you can be such a grouch sometimes.
Look at all these presents under the Christmas tree.
Awesome!
All right, Timmy, knock yourself out.
We should get ready and head to the market to buy everything for Christmas dinner tonight.
Yeah, you're right.
It's the first time we're hosting Christmas dinner at our house, so everything has to be perfect.
I got the list right here.
Ham, turkey, mashed potatoes, ingredients for the gravy, and of course, yams.
My dad offered to bring the eggnog, so we should be set.