The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A bad-tempered person.
Grouch Go ahead.
Do as you please.
Knock oneself out.
Go directly to.
Head to.
Hold an activity.
Host Ready for something.
Set Let's try that faster.
A bad-tempered person.
Grouch Ready for something.
Set Go directly to.
Head to.
Go ahead.
Do as you please.
Knock oneself out.
Hold an activity.
Host Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Grouch That old man is such a grouch.
He yells at anyone who even steps into his yard.
Grouch My friend was really grouchy today after they lost the football game.
Grouch I was really grouchy because I hadn't eaten all day.
Knock oneself out.
Here we are, the amusement park.
Alright kids, knock yourself out.
Knock oneself out.
You guys are going to have a great time at the zoo.
Knock yourself out.
Knock oneself out.
Knock yourself out at the dance tomorrow night, alright?
Head to.
I need to head to the corner store to get more milk.
She headed to the church for the Christmas Eve service.
Head to.
You need to head to the doctor's office right now and get that cough checked out.
Host I'm hosting a games night at my house on Thursday nights.
Host He decided to host the party at his parents' place.
Host My sister is hosting a birthday supper for her friend.
Set Once I get the ribbon, we should be set to start wrapping the presents.
Set We should be set to go as soon as my friend arrives.
Set With this new job, I should be set for life.