EnglishPod.com So you're applying for a B2 visa.
Where's your final destination and what's the purpose of your trip to the United States?
I'm going to visit my brother.
He's just had a baby.
He lives in Minneapolis.
And how long do you plan to remain in the United States?
I'll be here for approximately three weeks.
So here's my return ticket for the 26th of March.
And who's sponsoring your trip?
My brother.
Here.
This is an invitation letter from him.
I will stay with him and his family in their home.
Alright.
Tell me about the ties you have to your home country.
Well, I own a house.
Actually, I'm leaving my dog there with my neighbors.
I have a car at home.
I know my job.
I'm employed by Tornel as an engineer.
Actually, I only have a three-week vacation, so I have to go back to work at the end of March.
And what evidence do you have that you are financially independent?
Well, I do have assets in my country.
Like I said, I own a house.
And see, here's a bank statement showing my investments and my bank balance.
I'm sorry, sir.
We cannot grant you a B2 visa at this time.
Instead, you are granted a resident visa!
Congratulations!
You are the millionth person to apply for a visa!
You win!
Congratulations!