EnglishPod.com.
Good morning, golf aficionados.
My name is Rick Fields, and you guessed it, I'm here with my main man, Bob Copeland.
Thank you, Rick.
As you can see, ladies and gentlemen, we are here in beautiful Pebble Beach, where the top golfers in the world are vying to win the grand prize of $1 million.
Whoa, that's a lot of cash.
Let's go to the course and see how Tiger Woods is doing.
All right, we're here at the 8th hole, it's par 4, and it has some very difficult hazards which many golfers find difficult to avoid.
Although I did see Jack Nicklaus hit a hole-of-one on this very same hole.
Tiger Woods is about to tee off, and let's see if he has the same luck as Jack.
Tiger is asking his caddie for his driver, and he seems to be very nervous.
Oh, no, not a good swing at all.
It's definitely not his day today.
On the 7th hole, he got a bogey, and before that, he barely made par.
He will definitely not get a birdie on this shot.
It seems that his ball has flown somewhere deep into the trees.
He's having a hard time finding it, and even his caddie has climbed a tree to try and spot it.
Oh, no, a bear!
Run, Tiger, run!
Somebody call animal control!