The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Light golf stroke made on the putting green in an effort to place the ball into the hole.
Putt An enthusiastic admirer or follower.
A fan.
Aficionado An area of short-cut grass around the hole on a golf course.
Green My right-hand man.
My important helper.
Main man The action of a ball moving away from its straight path.
Break Money in the form of bills or coins.
Cash A hazard on a golf course considering of a depression partly filled with sand.
Sand trap Golf club with an angled metal head.
Iron An obstacle, such as some water, found on a golf course.
Hazard Using only one shot to put the ball in the hole.
Hole in one Hit the ball for the first time on a hole.
Tee off Person who carries the golf clubs and gives advice.
Caddy The club you use to hit the ball long distances.
Driver The action of hitting the golf ball.
Swing Not a good day for that person.
Not someone's day.
Score that is one higher than it should be in golf.
Bogey Get the score you should for a certain hole.
Make par One point lower than the score you should get.
Birdie The action of hitting the ball.
Shot A difficult time doing something.
Difficulty Hard time The number of strokes considered necessary to complete.
Par Let's try that faster.
Light golf stroke made on the putting green in an effort to place the ball into the hole.
Putt The person who carries the golf clubs and gives advice.
Caddy The number of strokes considered necessary to complete.
Par The action of hitting the ball.
Shot Hit the ball for the first time on a hole.
Tee off A difficult time doing something.
Difficulty Hard time Get the score you should for a certain hole.
Make par The action of hitting the golf ball.
Swing An area of short cut grass around the hole on a golf course.
Green One point lower than the score you should get.
Birdie Golf club with an angled metal head.
Iron My right hand man.
My important helper.
Main man A hazard on a golf course considering of a depression partly filled with sand.
Sand trap Using only one shot to put the ball in the hole.
Hole in one The action of a ball moving away from its straight path.
Break Not a good day for that person.
Not someone's day An obstacle such as some water found on a golf course.
Hazard The club you use to hit the ball long distances.
Driver An enthusiastic admirer or follower.
A fan.
Aficionado Score that is one higher than it should be in golf.
Bogey Money in the form of bills or coins.
Cash Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Hole in one That was amazing.
I have never seen somebody hit a hole in one before.
Hole in one The odds of hitting a hole in one are one in 33,000.
Hole in one Brad almost made a hole in one today at the golf course.
We were all very excited.
Tee off Don't be late.
We tee off at 9 a.m.
sharp.
Tee off Tiger Woods is about to tee off the ninth hole.
Let's go see.
Tee off One of the most difficult parts of golfing is the tee off.
Par Par This hole is a par four, which means you have four or fewer swings to put the ball in the hole.
Par With a bit of luck, I made par on the 18th hole.
Par Par You need to make par in order to win.
Don't screw up.
Birdie He was so lucky.
He got a birdie on this hole.
I thought he would just make par.
Birdie Par When a golfer puts the ball in the hole one stroke under par, we call that a birdie.
Birdie Jim is such a great golfer.
He has been sinking birdies all day.
Hard time Hard time I'm having a really hard time finding my camera.
Have you seen it?
Hard time When I was in school, I had a hard time with math and chemistry.
Hard time I'm having a hard time hitting the ball more than 100 meters.