EnglishPod.com I'm hungry.
Let's go grab a bite to eat.
Sure.
How about we go home and prepare a couple of sandwiches?
Nah, let's get a burger and fries.
What you ever do is have unhealthy fast food.
Pizza, fries, burgers, and hot dogs.
You have to start eating better.
What are you talking about?
I have salads sometimes.
Yeah, right.
I'm serious.
You should also cut down on your sugar intake as well.
You drink carbonated drinks that are high in fructose syrup.
It's really not healthy.
Fine.
I'll start drinking water and having home cooked meals that are low in fat.
Are you happy now?
It's a start, but I'll be happy when I see you stick to your promise.