The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Get food that can be eaten quickly.
Grab a bite.
Something frequently done.
All you ever do.
Reduce the amount taken or used.
Cut down.
What do you think?
How about...
Continue doing something.
Stick to.
Let's try that faster.
Reduce the amount taken or used.
Cut down.
Get food that can be eaten quickly.
Grab a bite.
What do you think?
How about...
Something frequently done.
All you ever do.
Continue doing something.
Stick to.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Grab a bite.
Do you want to go grab a bite after work?
Let's grab a bite before we go to school.
Grab a bite.
Derek and I are going to grab a bite with Catherine.
How about...
How about we go to the movies tonight?
How about you pick me up at three?
How about...
How about we go to my parents' house for Christmas this year?
All you ever do.
All you ever do is complain.
All you ever do is play computer games.
All you ever do.
All my parents ever do is yell at me.
Cut down.
We need to cut down on unnecessary expenses.
The doctor said I should cut down on my sugar intake.
Cut down.
Our company had to cut down operational costs.
Stick to.
It's hard for me to stick to this diet.
You have to stick to your promise.
Stick to.
I will stick to my New Year's resolution this year.