EnglishPod.com Mother, father, I'd like to introduce you to my fiancé Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Welcome.
Thanks for having me.
Nice to meet the both of you.
I've heard so much.
So, Cindy told you about bringing home her last boyfriend then.
Ha!
That idiot.
Shh!
Thurston!
You're going to scare the poor boy.
Come in and have a drink.
Dinner will be on in just a bit.
What'll you be having?
Whiskey?
Bourbon?
Pick your poison.
If you have a lemonade, that'd be great.
Lemonade?
Why, sure.
There's some in the fridge.
Mother makes her own lemonade from scratch.
It's the best.
So, what are your hobbies, son?
If you want, we can do some hunting tomorrow.
I've just picked up a new rifle I've been meaning to try out.
Should be a real hoot.
Um, I'm not really, uh, I don't really hunt.
You don't hunt?
Well, I'll be damned.
Bob is an animal rights activist.
He doesn't believe in harming animals.
Dinner's ready.
Let's go out to the patio where the pig is roasting.
Roast pig?
I'm a vegetarian.