EnglishPod.com All right, so this is what we're gonna do I've carefully mapped this out so don't screw it up mr.
Rabbit you and mr Fox will go to the bank wearing these uniforms We've managed to get replicas of the one the guards wear for when they pick up the money Got it No problem boss When you get inside tell them that you're filling in for Carl and Tom and say that they're on another route today Don't lose your cool.
Just act natural.
What if they want to call and confirm?
You let him what don't worry We have the phones tapped so the call will be patched through to me and I'll pretend to be the transport company Haha, you're so clever boss.
Hahaha.
Okay, shut up Only take as much money as you can fit in these bags.
Don't get greedy.
Are you ready?
Let's go Thanks for watching!