EnglishPod.com I've decided to grow my own garden.
What?
You don't know the first thing about gardening.
On the contrary, I've been reading a lot of books about the subject.
Oh yeah?
Tell me then, smarty pants.
How will you go about setting up your garden?
Well, first I need to buy some things such as fertilizer, seeds, and tools.
What type of tools?
You know, the basics.
A rake, shovel, spade, and a hoe.
Right.
Well, it seems like you have all your bases covered.
What's next?
I'll till the soil and then sow the seeds.
I'll then add some fertilizer and voila!
Gardening all done!
Well, good luck with your garden, especially considering we're in the dry season and it won't rain for the next three months.