EnglishPod.com What are you doing?
I'm just looking for a nice pillow on eBay.
You're shopping for a pillow online?
That's absurd!
Why?
I don't have to leave the house or browse a dozen stores to find what I'm looking for.
This way, I just search for it online, quick and easy.
I see.
But how do you pay for it?
How do you know you aren't going to be ripped off by the seller?
Well, the website handles a point system where if the seller does something wrong, people comment negatively, and then you know that he or she may not be trustworthy.
Wow, that sounds pretty safe.
So how do you pay?
Do you need a credit card?
You can use a credit card or your debit card.
They also let you use the PayPal system, which is really safe and fast.
I have never had any problems with someone hacking my information or anything.
Do you think I can find a sweater for my dog online?
You can find anything.
Are you sure you want to start shopping online, though?
Once you step into this world, there is no turning back.
Let's do it!