The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A game where you try to knock pins down with a bowl.
To make smooth and glossy, especially by rubbing or friction.
Polish Any narrow or well-defined passage, track, channel or course.
Lane To strike in collision.
Knock A sunken channel on each side of the lane.
Gutter An expert player.
Pro To strike in collision.
Knock To make smooth and glossy, especially by rubbing or friction.
Polish An expert player.
Pro A sunken channel on each side of the lane.
Gutter A game where you try to knock pins down with a bowl.
Any narrow or well-defined passage, track, channel or course.
Lane Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Pro Did you see him play in that match?
He is so pro.
Pro I think that guy playing is a pro.
Pro You can't beat me.
I'm too much of a pro.
I need to polish my shoes.
They are so dull.
Polish The floor is so rough it needs to be polished.
Polish After the polishing, the ice rink was super smooth.
Bowling I'm so bored.
Let's go bowling.
Bowling Bowling I hate bowling.
I always fall over.
Bowling I always practice my bowling.
I want to have a perfect game.
Gutter The gutter is full of rubbish.
Someone should clean it up.
Gutter I like bowling but my ball always goes into the gutter.
Gutter Watch out.
I saw a rat in the gutter.
Knock If I knock these pins over I will have a perfect score.
Knock I knocked into my friend while we were go-karting which caused him to crash.
Knock Hey, be careful.
You nearly knocked over my vase.