EnglishPod.com Alright, so the first thing you need to know about bowling is that you should never cross that line where the lane begins.
Why not?
Because they polish and oil it to make the ball slide down.
If you step there you'll slip and fall.
Okay, so I got my bowling shoes, my ball, our names on the scorecard, so now how the heck do I play this?
You throw the ball down the lane and try to knock down all the pins.
If you do, that is called a strike.
If you don't knock them all down on the first try, then you get a chance to get the spare.
After 10 frames, we add up the points and see who has the most.
300 is a perfect score, but very hard to get.
Got it.
Okay, I'm gonna give it a go.
Oh no, my ball went in the gutter.
I told you, it's harder than you think.
Now let a pro show you how it's done.