EnglishPod.com Now if I look here, I see that you completed a BA in English.
Yes, that's right.
After graduating from high school in New York, I attended York University in the UK.
My major was English and my minor was Business.
I completed my BA in 2004.
Yes, I'm pleased to see that you also got a distinction.
Yes, that's right.
I've always enjoyed studying.
My friends say I'm a bit of a bookworm, but my father always pushed us to succeed at school.
Well, it looks like his encouragement paid off, Rebecca.
So how about extracurricular activities at university?
Well, I've always been keen on writing, so I became the editor for the university student newspaper, which I really loved.
Also, I volunteered for a group called Shelter to help the homeless in New York.
What did that involve?
Providing warm meals and shelter, especially in the winter months.
I found it really fulfilling to be part of that group.
I'm sure.
Okay, now let's move on to your work experience, shall we?
Yeah, okay.
Okay.