The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Distinction A person who likes reading and studying.
Bookworm To affect positively.
Payoff Extra activities Extracurricular Willing or eager to do something.
Keen on Want to do something without being forced or pay.
Volunteer Contain Involve Full of happiness and satisfaction.
Fulfilling To encourage or persuade someone to do something.
Push Let's try that faster.
Willing or eager to do something.
Keen on Want to do something without being forced or pay.
Volunteer A second subject studied in college.
Minor Full of happiness and satisfaction.
Fulfilling Extra activities Extracurricular To affect positively.
Payoff Bachelor of Arts BA Contain Involve Excellence Distinction A person who likes reading and studying.
Bookworm To encourage or persuade someone to do something.
Push The main subject studied in a college.
Major Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Major You're almost finished with your first year of college.
Have you decided on a major yet?
Major Mark graduated with a double major in Philosophy and East Asian Studies.
Major Major I attended the University of Washington where I majored in Economics.
Distinction It may be difficult for some English learners to hear the distinction between the words eyes and ice.
Distinction Only the best of the best students at British universities receive distinction.
Distinction And Bo Shishun had the distinction of being the tallest man in the world.
Keenon I think Tom is keen on Sherry.
He's always flirting with her.
Keenon I'd rather not go to McDonald's for lunch.
I'm not keen on fast food.
Keenon Payoff My boss is really keen on golf these days, so we bought him monogrammed golf balls as a gift.
Payoff All that studying really paid off.
I got 100% on my final exam.
Payoff My daughter doesn't like going to violin lessons three times a week, but I tell her that all this practice will pay off someday.
Payoff We took a risk with this marketing campaign, but it really paid off.
Our customer base nearly doubled.
Extracurricular What extracurricular activities did you participate in while you were in college?
Extracurricular Many students in Asian countries have to study so much they have no time for extracurricular activities.
Extracurricular Extracurricular I'm a happily married man with no extracurricular relationships.