The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A skiing race where you must go through flags.
Slalom The building that has restaurants and stores on the ski hill.
Lodge Winner Champion Powder, soft light snow.
Pow Start skiing Hit the slopes Avalanche, lots of snow falling off the mountain.
Avi A person who operates the chairlift.
Lifty Fitting very tightly.
Snuggly A steep hill with high sides shaped like a bowl.
Bowl Make something attach by pressing down.
Snap A bottom part that attaches the boot to a ski.
Binding A pair of glasses used to protect one's eyes.
Goggles Bright light that is reflected by the snow.
Glare A space on the mountain which is used for skiing.
Slopes A bump on a ski hill.
Mogul A covering of the hands with each finger separated so as to keep it warm.
Ski glove A slow easy turn where you make a V with the skis.
Snowplow turn Turn on your skis with your edges.
Carving A line of chairs with a moving cable that carries people up the mountain.
Chairlift A party or drinks after skiing.
Apres ski Ski on the area that has never been skied before.
Grab some freshies Falling so hard that you lose all your ski equipment.
Yard sale Used to describe a skier that jumps really really high.
Catch some major air Small hill Bump Awesome, cool, used by ski lovers.
Gnarly Fall Take a spill Let's try that faster.
Avalanche, lots of snow falling off the mountain.
Avvy Fall Take a spill A steep hill with high sides shaped like a bowl.
Bowl A bottom part that attaches the boot to a ski.
Binding A slow easy turn where you make a V with the skis.
Snowplow turn A pair of glasses used to protect one's eyes.
Goggles A covering of the hands with each finger separated so as to keep it warm.
Ski glove Falling so hard that you lose all your ski equipment.
Yard sale A party or drinks after skiing.
Apres ski The building that has restaurants and stores on the ski hill.
Lodge A person who operates the chairlift.
Lifty Small hill Bump Bright light that is reflected by the snow.
Glare Winner Champion Awesome, cool, used by ski lovers.
Gnarly A line of chairs with a moving cable that carries people up the mountain.
Chairlift A space on the mountain which is used for skiing.
Slopes A skiing race where you must go through flags.
Slalom Used to describe a skier that jumps really really high.
Catch some major air.
Make something attach by pressing down.
Snap Powder, soft light snow.
Pow Fitting very tightly.
Snuggly A bump on a ski hill.
Mogul Start skiing.
Hit the slopes.
Ski on the area that has never been skied before.
Grab some freshies.
Turn on your skis with your edges.
Carving Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Hit the slopes.
It's a perfect day for skiing so I want to make sure that we hit the slopes before 9am.
You have a test in two days and you haven't studied?
You'd better hit the books.
Hit the slopes.
Wow, I have to be at my job interview in 15 minutes.
I need to leave and hit the road.
Catch some major air.
Tom and I went to the skate park last weekend and I took some great classes.
I took pictures of him catching some air.
Catch some major air.
The car hit the sidewalk and caught some air before it flipped and hit the street.
I'm always afraid of going too fast on the jumps and catching some air.
Gnarly Those were some gnarly dance moves.
You are amazing.
Gnarly Jack and I went to the beach yesterday and surfed some really gnarly waves.
Gnarly Take a spill Man, that concert last night was gnarly.
I can't believe we got front row seats.
Take a spill I was teaching my niece how to ride her bike and she accidentally took a spill.
My uncle was so angry.
Take a spill Did you see that?
The girl tripped on the sidewalk and took a nasty spill.
Take a spill Craig took a spill in his motorcycle and broke his arm.
Well, I think that about does it.
We've finished up all the work today and we're ready to go home.
That about does it for today's class everyone.
Thanks for coming.
That about does it for today's meeting.
See you all here next week.