Welcome, ski lovers of all ages.
My name is Rick Fields and here with me is the man that needs no introduction, Bob Copeland.
Thank you, Rick.
What a beautiful day here in Aspen, Colorado, where the sun is shining and we've got 12 inches of fresh powder.
It doesn't get much better than this.
That's right, Bob.
But today we have a special treat for our viewers.
We're joined here by Ian Rusey, four-time giant slalom champion.
And on this special edition of the show, Ian is going to teach us the basics of skiing.
So let's hit the slopes.
Well, first off, let's get those boots on.
You're going to want to make sure your boots fit snugly.
That's right.
Now snap them into your bindings.
And you're also going to want a good pair of goggles to protect your eyes.
It's a bright day today, so there's going to be a lot of glare out there on the slopes.
We don't want you hitting any of those moguls.
Bob, since you're a beginner skier and might take a few spills, it's a good idea to have a good warm pair of dry ski gloves.
Easy there, Rick.
Well, let's head over onto the chairlift and test your skills.
All right, we're up here on the bunny hill.
So Bob, why don't you do a few snowplow turns?
Gnarly run, Rick.
Nice carving.
You've got some mad skills.
That was sick.
You want to see gnarly?
Well, see that bump over there?
I'm going to catch some major air.
Ha ha ha.
Butt plant.
He lost his skis.
Yard sale.
Well, thanks for joining us here today.
I think that about does it.
Bob, Ian, time for some apres ski?
No way, man.
We're off to grab some freshies.