Good afternoon, sir.
Is there anything I can help you with today?
Um, yeah.
I'm looking for a nice gift to give my girlfriend.
Our fifth anniversary is next Friday.
Well, I would be happy to assist you in choosing the perfect gift for her.
Is there anything in particular that you have in mind?
No, not really.
I'm completely at a loss.
Well, you can give her a set of pearl earrings or this beautiful heart-shaped pendant.
What is her favorite gemstone?
That purple one.
I'm sorry.
I've never bought jewelry for anyone and I'm kind of nervous.
Don't worry.
We specialize in providing our customers a relaxed, pressure-free shopping environment.
That stone is an amethyst.
We have a range of beautiful amethyst pieces.
Take a look at this bracelet.
It's 18 karat rose gold studded with amethyst and blue topaz.
It's a great statement piece.
Oh, wow.
That's really pretty.
Jess would love that.
But I was thinking of something a little more delicate.
Perhaps a necklace?
We have this beautiful platinum pendant or you could also get her a locket.
You could also get her a timepiece.
It's both glamorous and functional.
If you tell me a little more about your girlfriend, maybe I can help you find something for her.
Jess?
Well, she's very smart.
She has a great sense of humor.
She's very feminine.
Perhaps you could give her a ring.
Well, actually, I was thinking about asking Jess to marry me.
I've just been so nervous.
Well, sir, I believe your fifth anniversary is a great time to propose.
Okay, I've decided.
I'm going to pop the question.
Fabulous.
We should look at engagement rings then.
Now, that's a whole other section.