The EnglishPod Audio Review.
Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Register at a hotel or airport
Check in
Under the name
Booking
Reservation
An approval, verification.
Confirmation.
Confusion.
Mix up.
Free improvement of quality.
Complimentary upgrade.
Full.
Overbooked.
Let's try that faster!
Name used for the reservation.
Under the name
Booking
Reservation
Register at a hotel or airport
Check in
Booking
Reservation
An approval, verification
Confirmation
Full
Overbooked
Booking
Reservation
Full
Overbooked
Name used for the reservation
Under the name
Free improvement of quality
Complimentary upgrade
Name used for the reservation
Under the name
An approval, verification
Confirmation
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.