The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A kind of literary or artistic work.
Genre When a person pretends to play the guitar when listening to music.
Air guitar Abbreviations Acronym To sing without any instruments or music.
Acapella Extra time to determine a winner after a tie.
Sudden death A demand by an audience for an additional performance at the end of a concert.
Encore The outcome or result depends on you.
The pressure is on.
A part of a song repeated after each verse.
Chorus A person or thing that gains wide appeal or fame.
Hit Used when you want to bet twice as much.
Double or nothing Let's try that faster!
To sing without any instruments or music.
Acapella A part of a song repeated after each verse.
Chorus Extra time to determine a winner after a tie.
Sudden death A kind of literary or artistic work.
Genre When a person pretends to play the guitar when listening to music.
Air guitar A demand by an audience for an additional performance at the end of a concert.
Encore A person or thing that gains wide appeal or fame.
Hit The outcome or result depends on you.
The pressure is on.
Abbreviations Acronym Used when you want to bet twice as much.
Double or nothing Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Genre I think mystery is one of the most fascinating literary genres.
Genre I was reading in the newspaper that there are over 200 music genres in the world.
Genre My family doesn't like to watch certain movie genres such as horror, musicals, and action.
Acronym Did you know that LASER is the acronym for Light Amplification by the Stimulated Emission of Radiation?
Acronym Acronym The most well-known acronym in the world is OK, although people still aren't sure what it stands for.
Acronym ATM is a well-known acronym for Automatic Teller Machine.
The pressure is on.
The pressure is on the president to guide his country out of the recession.
Carl is really stressed out lately.
The pressure of the entire project is on him since his promotion.
The pressure is on.
The pressure is on our entire team to successfully come up with a new product for the Asian market within a month.
Sudden Death Sudden Death The soccer game is in Sudden Death now.
The first player to score wins the game.
Sudden Death We went out to a bar last night to watch the football game.
The winner was decided by Sudden Death.
Sudden Death Double or Nothing What an exciting volleyball game that was.
I can't believe the game was decided by Sudden Death.