EnglishPod.com.
Welcome back, music lovers, to I Love That Song, the game show where we test your musical knowledge to the extreme.
Let's get started.
Team A, guess this tune.
Carrying Your Love With Me by George Strait.
The genre is country music.
You're right.
100 points to Team A.
Now for our next cut.
Song Song by Cisco.
I believe the genre is R&B.
100 big points for Team B.
For all of our viewers, the acronym R&B stands for rhythm and blues.
On that note, DJ, play our next song.
Superstar by the Carpenters.
And the genre?
Adult Contemporary.
That's right.
100 points.
Uh oh, that sound means it's double or nothing.
The songs are more difficult and the points are doubled.
Let's hear our next song.
Too Easy.
That song is Kingslayer by the Finnish power metal group Nightwish.
You are correct.
Very impressive, Team A.
And it seems we have a tie.
It's time now for the tiebreaker round.
Each team will be played three songs and they must tell us the genre of each song in less than five seconds.
Team A, are you ready?
Ready.
Let's hear it.
Hip Hop, classical and gothic metal.
You're right.
Team B, the pressure is on.
If you get all of them right, we will move on to Sudden Death.
If you miss one, you lose.
DJ, let's hear it.
Rap, disco and and...