The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Written document that provides information about a person's achievements.
Report A position or degree in a scale as of quality, rank, size or progression.
Grade A branch of knowledge as a course of study.
Subject A symbol used in rating conduct, proficiency or attainment.
Mark Something that has been done or accomplished.
Achievement Fulfilling all demands or requirements.
Satisfactory Formal test taken at the end of a course.
Exam Let's try that faster.
A branch of knowledge as a course of study.
Subject A symbol used in rating conduct, proficiency or attainment.
Mark A position or degree in a scale as of quality, rank, size or progression.
Grade Formal test taken at the end of a course.
Exam Written document that provides information about a person's achievements.
Report Fulfilling all demands or requirements.
Satisfactory Something that has been done or accomplished.
Achievement Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.