EnglishPod.com We now stand ten years past the midpoint of a century that has witnessed four major wars among great nations.
Three of these involved our own country.
Despite the carnage of these conflicts, America is today the strongest, the most influential, and the most productive nation in the world.
We are understandably proud of this preeminence, yet we realize that America's leadership and prestige depend not merely upon our unmatched material progress, riches, and military strength, but on how we use our power in the interests of world peace and human betterment.
Throughout America's adventure in free government, such basic purposes have been to keep the peace, to foster progress and human achievement, and to enhance liberty, dignity, and integrity among peoples and among nations.
We pray that peoples of all faiths, all races, all nations, may have their great human needs satisfied, that those now denied opportunity shall come to enjoy it to the full, that all who yearn for freedom may experience its spiritual blessings, that those who have freedom will understand also its heavy responsibilities, that all who are insensitive to the needs of others will learn charity, that the scourges of poverty, disease, and ignorance will be made to disappear from the earth, and that in the goodness of time all peoples will come to live together in a peace guaranteed by the binding force of mutual respect and love.
Now on Friday noon I am to become a private citizen.
I am proud to do so.
I look forward to it.
Thank you and good night.