The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To help something grow or develop.
Foster Badly affected by disease, pain, grief, etc.
Stricken To feel a strong desire or wish for something.
Yearn In U.S.
politics, a member or supporter of the Democratic Party, the more liberal of the two main political parties in the U.S.
Democrat More important, skillful, or successful than other.
Preeminence Belonging to the Republican Party, the more conservative of the two main political parties in the U.S.
Republican Someone or something that causes a great amount of trouble.
Scourge In the U.S., the wife of the President-elect.
First Lady To be in a particular place or position.
We now stand.
An operation or series of operations energetically pursued to accomplish a purpose.
Campaign Let's try that faster.
In the U.S., the wife of the President-elect.
First Lady To be in a particular place or position.
We now stand.
Belonging to the Republican Party, the more conservative of the two main political parties in the U.S.
Republican Badly affected by disease, pain, grief, etc.
Stricken To help something grow or develop.
Foster To feel a strong desire or wish for something.
Yearn An operation or series of operations energetically pursued to accomplish a purpose.
Campaign More important, skillful, or successful than other.
Preeminence Someone or something that causes a great amount of trouble.
Scourge In U.S.
politics, a member or supporter of the Democratic Party, the more liberal of the two main political parties in the U.S.
Democrat Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
We now stand.
We now stand before you to declare our love and be united in marriage.
I stand before this court and declare my innocence.
We now stand.
Together, we now stand before this great challenge and we will fight it arm in arm to defeat poverty.
Yearn We must fight for those who yearn for their freedoms.
Yearn In the past of all great men, you will find a yearning to learn and to succeed.
Yearn I'm yearning to find someone who will love me for me.
Preeminence Now, please welcome Dr.
Frank Hicks, the world's most preeminent expert on nuclear biology.
Preeminence He's been a leader in his field for 25 years, and his preeminence has never been questioned.
Preeminence Carol Dixon is one of the most preeminent experts in green technology.
Foster It is our creed to foster and maintain a spirit of fraternity.
Foster To restore our country to the glory of its past, we must foster an attitude of determination and social service.
Foster Unsanitary conditions help foster the spread of disease.
Scorch One day we hope to eliminate the scourge of cancer.
Scorch Malaria is a disease that continues to be a scourge to the developing world.
Scorch NATO promises to wipe out the scourge of terrorism.