The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Related to business.
Corporate.
The action of controlling an area of a business.
Management.
Person who finished university.
Graduate.
Graduate Management Admissions Test.
GMAT.
Pertaining or proceeding by analysis.
Analytical.
Type of information based in quantities.
Consisting of or in the form of words.
Verbal.
Master of Business Administration.
MBA.
A wealthy and privileged person.
Fat cat.
Let's try that faster.
Graduate Management Admissions Test.
GMAT.
Person who finished university.
Graduate.
Related to business.
Corporate.
Type of information based in quantities.
A wealthy and privileged person.
Fat cat.
Pertaining or proceeding by analysis.
Analytical.
The action of controlling an area of a business.
Management.
Master of Business Administration.
MBA.
Consisting of or in the form of words.
Verbal.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Fat cat.
Look at all those fat cats in the government.
I bet they only got into university because of their fat cat parents.
Fat cat.
The poor get poorer because of fat cats like you.
Graduate.
Now that I've finished my undergraduates degree, I think I might do postgraduate studies.
There are many graduate entry jobs after university.
Graduate.
The graduates may look good on paper.
They don't have much real world experience.
Management.
Our management is really tight when it comes to the budget.
Management has decided to lay off some staff in order to cut down costs.
Management.
She has been with this company for four years now and management still hasn't given her a raise.
Verbal.
He gave the verbal command to shoot the prisoner.
I believe I can teach better verbally than visually.
Verbal.
Although he saw the visual command, he was still waiting for a verbal order.
Corporate.
I don't like this corporate culture.
It's always about money.
Corporate.
These corporate guys think they're so good.
The corporate watchdog was introduced to ensure proper ethics and laws were being obeyed by firms.