The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A deranged psychotic or morbidly obsessed person.
Sicko Doing something wrong or illegal.
Red-handed To affect in an unwanted way.
Invade Having a feeling that people will harm you.
Paranoid Situation where you have only the information you need.
Need-to-know basis Let's try that faster!
Having a feeling that people will harm you.
Paranoid To affect in an unwanted way.
Invade A deranged psychotic or morbidly obsessed person.
Sicko Situation where you have only the information you need.
Need-to-know basis Doing something wrong or illegal.
Red-handed Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Sicko That sicko just brushed against me again.
Sicko Get your hands off me, you sicko!
Sicko Our society is full of these types of sickos.
Red-handed The little boy was caught red-handed stealing cookies out of the pantry.
Red-handed Caught red-handed, you little thief!
I knew someone was stealing my change.
Red-handed The graffiti artist was caught red-handed.
He was identified by the paint on his hands.
Paranoid Paranoid Don't be paranoid, Bob.
Even if there were aliens, they wouldn't want to abduct you.
Paranoid Paranoia is characterized by extreme anxiety and fear.
Paranoid I don't think he is just being paranoid.
There really is a vampire waiting outside.
Invade The troops invaded at dawn.
Invade Invade The place is invaded by tourists every summer.
Invade I must insist you not come in.
It really is an invasion of privacy.
Need-to-know basis Need-to-know basis The details of my date last night are on a need-to-know basis.
Need-to-know basis If you don't have a specific need-to-know, I can't tell you.
Need-to-know basis Need-to-know basis Access to the report of the UFO crash are on a need-to-know basis.