EnglishPod.com Dan, Dan.
Dude, you have to come over to my house right now.
Is everything okay?
Just get over here.
Come in!
Quickly!
So, since when is your house a bank?
What do you mean?
I mean, what's up with the four locks and iron bars on your windows?
Security, Dan!
Security!
You can never be too safe, you know.
A lot of sickos out there.
Just the other day, they caught that peeping Tom red-handed.
Had a high-power telescope and binoculars by his window.
What's the matter with you?
Why are you acting all paranoid?
Paranoid?
I'm not paranoid!
I'm cautious!
You see, Dan, we have to be on guard at all times.
People just invade your privacy as if they knew you.
Telemarketers, solicitors, even your bank.
They have way too much information.
I like to keep everything on a need-to-know basis.
Okay.
Well, what did you want to see me about?
You're being watched!
Be careful, Dan.
Be careful.