EnglishPod.com I hate coming to high school reunions.
It'll be great, honey.
We will get to see your old classmates and catch up to see how they've been doing.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, look.
There's Robert Matthews.
Rob!
Hey, Bill.
Wow.
Great to see you.
Likewise.
It's been a long time.
This is my wife, Dorothy.
Pleasure to meet you.
So, Bill, how have you been?
Can't complain.
We have two children who are in college and my business is going well.
How about you?
Ah, you know me.
I'm a dedicated bachelor.
I never married, although I do have a beautiful daughter with Mary.
You remember her.
We were high school sweethearts.
It didn't really work out between us, but I really can't complain either.
That's good.
Have you seen Frank?
I was hoping he would come tonight.
You didn't hear?
Frank passed away last year.
Are you serious?
Nah, I'm just janking your chain.
He'll be here soon.
I saw him last week.
He told me he would show up.