The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Meet each other.
Catch up.
Have strong loyalty to someone or something.
Dedicated.
Also.
Likewise.
Deceive someone in a friendly or playful way.
Yank your chain.
The person who you loved in high school.
High school sweetheart.
Let's try that faster.
Deceive someone in a friendly or playful way.
Yank your chain.
Meet each other.
Catch up.
Also.
Likewise.
The person who you loved in high school.
High school sweetheart.
Have strong loyalty to someone or something.
Dedicated.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Catch up.
Lisa is back from Holland, and we are having lunch today to catch up.
Hi Jonas, I haven't seen you in a long time.
Do you want to grab a drink after work to catch up?
Catch up.
I haven't seen my college friends in a while, so the party will be a good time to catch up.
Dedicated.
He's a dedicated husband and father.
He's a real family man.
Dedicated.
She's a dedicated researcher of marine biology.
We need to hire a dedicated translator once we start doing more business with Vietnam.
Likewise.
I told Edward I'd liked him, but he didn't say likewise.
My parents want me to get a PhD, and likewise it's my dream to become a doctor.
Likewise.
I ordered a mocha coffee and a muffin, and Janet did likewise.
High school sweetheart.
John married his high school sweetheart last year in a small wedding ceremony.
Laurie stayed with her high school sweetheart all through college.
High school sweetheart.
Robbie and Vanessa were high school sweethearts, but they've both moved on and started families now.
Yank your chain.
My uncle Tommy loves to joke around and yank your chain.
Just don't take anything he says too seriously.
Yank your chain.
I hate it when people yank my chain when I'm trying to be serious.
Chill out.
I was just yanking your chain.