EnglishPod.com Have you thought about getting her some sleepwear?
We've got these lovely silky nighties, or how about some nice panties in a bra set?
Look, here's a nice satin push-up bra, and you can choose a few different styles of undies to go with it.
Sure, that's fine.
This is so awkward.
What lengths do I pick?
What size is she?
Well, do you want a thong?
Some bikini briefs?
Maybe this nice pair of lacy boy shorts?
Just pick something and get the hell out of here.
I'll go with these two.
This is mortifying.
I just want to get this over with, and she better thank me for this.
Here you are, sir.
I'm sure she'll enjoy them.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm going to have to take a look inside your bag.