The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Journey to a place.
Trip.
To fill with terror or alarm, make greatly afraid.
Terrify.
Fear.
An abnormal fear of drafts of air, gases or airborne matter.
Aerophobia.
Constant, habitual.
Chronic.
Irrational fear of a specific object, activity.
Phobia.
The fear of public speaking.
Glossophobia.
A pathological fear of heights.
Acrophobia.
To excrete through the pores of skin.
Sweat.
Being worried about what might happen.
Nervous.
Fool or joke.
Kidding.
An abnormal fear of being in enclosed or narrow places.
Claustrophobia.
To admit or acknowledge something damaging.
Confess.
A strange person.
Weirdo.
Let's try that faster.
Fool or joke.
Kidding.
To fill with terror or alarm, make greatly afraid.
Terrify.
Journey to a place.
Trip.
Being worried about what might happen.
Nervous.
Irrational fear of a specific object, activity.
Phobia.
To admit or acknowledge something damaging.
Confess.
A strange person.
Weirdo.
Constant, habitual.
Chronic.
A pathological fear of heights.
Acrophobia.
To excrete through the pores of skin.
Sweat.
An abnormal fear of being in enclosed or narrow places.
Claustrophobia.
The fear of public speaking.
An abnormal fear of drafts of air, gases or airborne matter.
Aerophobia.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Chronic.
I feel sick.
I have a chronic headache that won't go away.
Chronic.
I don't listen to my neighbour anymore as he is a chronic liar.
When I was watching that horror movie I was in a chronic state of suspense.
Phobia.
I have a phobia of spiders.
Whenever I see one I run for the hills.
Phobia.
She tried to cure her phobia of heights by going bungee jumping.
My dad said the only way to cure your phobia is to tackle it head on.
Confess.
I must confess that I love chocolate milkshakes.
Can I confess something to you if you promise to keep it a secret?
Confess.
The judge reduced his sentence after he confessed to his crime.
Nervous.
I always get so nervous when I go on the roller coaster.
She looked very nervous when she walked in for her job interview.
Nervous.
I was so nervous on a date with a girl I liked that I accidentally spilled wine on her dress.
Kidding.
My dad likes to tell me that he is an alien.
I know he is kidding.
Kidding.
I'm going to eat you.
Haha.
Just kidding.
Kidding.
You must be kidding.
Another parking ticket.