Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod, my name is Marco.
My name is Katherine and today we're talking about fear.
That's right, today we're going to talk about phobias, different types of fears that you have.
Many people are scared of different things and that's what we're going to talk about today.
Okay, so let's listen to today's dialogue and find out what the people in our dialogue are very, very afraid of.
Are you excited about your trip next month?
Yes and no.
I can't wait to go to Europe but at the same time I'm terrified.
Why?
Well, I have aerophobia.
I have a chronic fear of flying.
Oh really?
I have an uncle who is also terrified of flying.
It's not that bad though, I mean it is pretty scary to be up in this big machine flying through the air at 700 miles per hour.
I actually have arachnophobia.
You're scared of spiders?
I actually have two more phobias, acrophobia and glossophobia.
I guess that explains why you're afraid of flying but public speaking is not that bad.
Are you kidding?
When I get on stage my palms start to sweat.
I get really nervous and I can hardly speak.
Wow.
I must confess that I am a bit claustrophobic.
I hate being in an elevator for more than five seconds.
We are such weirdos, right?
Alright, we're back so let's take a look at those phobias on Language Takeaway.
Language Takeaway.
The first phobia that we have is called aerophobia.
That's right, aerophobia and that means that you are scared of flying.
Okay, so we can tell because phobia means fear of something but it's not just a fear.
It means that if you go on an airplane you get very very upset.
You think that you're going to die.
That's right.
Okay and so phobia is a very serious fear.
But aero like aeroplane is the prefix so aerophobia is a fear of going on airplanes.
That's right and another phobia that we have is arachnophobia.
So again as you see in the prefix arachnid is related to a spider.
That's right so this comes from the origins of English.
I'm not sure if it's Greek or Latin but arachnophobia like arachnid has to do with spiders.
So I'm afraid of spiders if I have arachnophobia.
That is right and now taking a look at two more types of phobias here we have acrophobia and glossophobia.
So let's take a look at the first one, acrophobia.
So acrophobia, acro has to do with heights.
So I don't like to be on tall buildings.
I don't like to maybe look down from heights.
That means I'm afraid of heights.
That's right you're afraid of being at a very high altitude.
Acrophobia.
Now glossophobia is an interesting one because this one you are scared of public speaking or you get very nervous when you're in front of a group of people.
Right so this is actually a very very common fear but if it's a serious fear it's a phobia.
So glossophobia means that when you go in front of people you get very very anxious, upset, your stomach hurts, you have wet hands.
So that's a very serious fear.
That's right.
And for our last phobia we have claustrophobia I think is one of the most common ones.
If you have claustrophobia you're afraid of smaller tight spaces.
That's right so people who, so you heard the word claustrophobic, people who are claustrophobic or people who suffer from claustrophobia don't like to be in small tight places like elevators for example.
Tunnels.
So now you brought up an interesting point.
Our last phobia we said claustrophobic and now we must make the difference between for example claustrophobia and being claustrophobic.
So a phobia, you hear the word I, you hear the ending I A, claustrophobia is a noun okay that means I can talk about I have it, I have this fear but when you're talking about the adjective, something that describes you, you would have to use the ick ending.
I'm claustrophobic, he is acrophobic, they are aerophobic.
Okay so that is the adjective form.
So if I say I have arachnophobia it means I have this fear or I can say I am arachnophobic.
Great so this can be used for all other kinds of phobias so when you learn those words remember that there's two different kinds, there's the ia, there's the ia, phobia which is the noun and ick which is the adjective.
Alright let's listen to our dialogue again and we'll be back in a bit with Fluency Builder.
Are you excited about your trip next month?
Yes and no.
I can't wait to go to Europe but at the same time I'm terrified.
Why?
Well I have aerophobia, I have a chronic fear of flying.
Oh really?
I have an uncle who is also terrified of flying.
It's not that bad though, I mean it is pretty scary to be up in this big machine flying through the air at 700 miles per hour.
I actually have arachnophobia.
You're scared of spiders?
I actually have two more phobias, acrophobia and glossophobia.
I guess that explains why you're afraid of flying but public speaking is not that bad.
Are you kidding?
When I get on stage my palms start to sweat, I get really nervous and I can hardly speak.
Well, I must confess that I am a bit claustrophobic.
I hate being in an elevator for more than five seconds.
We are such weirdos, right?
All right, so we've picked out a couple of different phrases today.
Let's take a look at those now on Fluency Builder.
Fluency Builder.
So in the beginning of today's dialogue the character said, I cannot wait to go to Europe but at the same time I'm terrified.
So at the same time.
So in this case we're saying that we are happy but also we are scared.
So two things at once at the same time.
Right, so this is a little bit different from when we talk about I can do two things at the same time.
I can walk and chew gum.
When we're talking about feelings or emotions you say, you know, I'm happy but at the same time I'm also scared.
That means that I have these two feelings and actually they're opposite feelings.
Right, exactly.
Usually they are opposite feelings.
So like you say, you're happy but at the same time you're nervous.
It's like saying on the other hand.
All right, now when we talked about all these fears, we're afraid of flying, we are afraid of spiders, we describe them as a chronic fear.
Okay, so this adjective chronic is very important because it has to do with time.
Okay, so I have a chronic fear of heights.
That means this is a fear I've always had and I will always have.
You can also say she has chronic back pain.
That means it comes back again and again.
It's not just one time.
It's all, it's some person's whole life maybe.
Not every day but it comes back.
Right, okay, so that's if you say you have a chronic something you're explaining that you've had it for a while or you will always have it.
Something usually very serious also.
And going back to one of the phobias, we mentioned glossophobia and the other person said, well you know public speaking is not that bad.
It's not something to be so afraid of.
And the other person replied by saying, are you kidding?
Are you kidding?
So this is actually a way of showing some sarcasm when you're talking because public speaking is not that bad.
The person wants to say, no it is that bad, it is awful.
So, are you kidding is a way to say, no I totally disagree.
Right, so you're being a little bit sarcastic but at the same time you're also acting a bit surprised.
Like, I can't believe you said that.
Like if I said, I really like the Twilight movies, Marco.
Are you kidding?
Those movies are terrible.
Alright, so Marco does not agree with my opinion.
Alright, now when we're talking about public speaking we mentioned that you get on stage.
So this is very important because this is the action, to get on stage and speak.
Okay, so if you have a stage or maybe even, you don't have a stage, but you're talking about performing in front of other people, like a speech or a play, you say, you get on stage.
And it's important to remember this as a phrase, so whenever I get on stage I start to sweat.
Now you may want to add the, there you want to say, to get on the stage.
But it's not necessary.
It's not incorrect but the usual, or let's say more correct form would just be, use the phrase to get on stage.
When I get on stage I get very nervous.
You don't have to say, when I get on the stage.
Or she's normally very shy but when she gets on stage she opens up and becomes very, very talkative.
That's right.
Alright, so that's all the phrases we've picked out for you.
Let's listen to our dialogue one last time and we'll be right back.
Are you excited about your trip next month?
Yes and no.
I can't wait to go to Europe but at the same time I'm terrified.
Why?
Well, I have aerophobia.
I have a chronic fear of flying.
Oh really?
I have an uncle who is also terrified of flying.
It's not that bad though.
I mean, it is pretty scary to be up in this big machine flying through the air at 700 miles per hour.
I actually have arachnophobia.
You're scared of spiders?
I actually have two more phobias, acrophobia and glossophobia.
I guess that explains why you're afraid of flying but public speaking is not that bad.
Are you kidding?
When I get on stage my palms start to sweat.
I get really nervous and I can hardly speak.
Well, I must confess that I am a bit claustrophobic.
I hate being in an elevator for more than five seconds.
We are such weirdos, right?
Alright, so talking about all these phobias.
Now one of these phobias was actually made into a movie, I think in 1990, arachnophobia.
This very chronic fear of spiders.
That's right.
I remember when I was younger and this movie came out everybody started talking about how they were arachnophobic.
They had this horrible fear of spiders.
Did you ever see that movie?
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
It was terrifying.
It was supposedly some South American spider that made its way into the United States in a box in a crate or something.
Now many people handle phobias differently.
Do you have any phobia?
Are you claustrophobic?
Are you arachnophobic?
I don't have any phobias and I'm not really afraid of anything, so I'm pretty lucky that way.
I know a number of people who are afraid of heights, arachnophobic, so that's pretty common.
And actually if you look it up, you will find in the dictionary maybe hundreds of phobias.
People who are afraid of open spaces, people who are afraid of closed spaces, or people who are afraid of marriage, they even have a phobia determined for this type of person.
So it's very interesting.
Now this is going to be a challenge.
Why don't you look up a couple of different phobias and share it with us?
Maybe some of the craziest ones or the funniest ones or maybe the strangest ones you can find.
That's right.
So look them up.
Share them with us.
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
All right.
We'll see you guys there.
Bye.