EnglishPod.com Are you excited about your trip next month?
Yes, and no.
I can't wait to go to Europe, but at the same time I'm terrified.
Why?
Well, I have aerophobia.
I have a chronic fear of flying.
Oh really?
I have an uncle who is also terrified of flying.
It's not that bad though.
I mean, it is pretty scary to be up in this big machine flying through the air at 700 miles per hour.
I actually have arachnophobia.
You're scared of spiders?
I actually have two more phobias.
Acrophobia and glossophobia.
I guess that explains why you're afraid of flying, but public speaking is not that bad.
Are you kidding?
When I get on stage my palms start to sweat.
I get really nervous and I can hardly speak.
Well, I must confess that I am a bit claustrophobic.
I hate being in an elevator for more than five seconds.
We are such weirdos, right?