EnglishPod.com Hey, Four Eyes, what's up, man?
How have you been?
Not bad.
Just went to the mall and picked up some junk.
Check out my new adidas.
Those are dope.
You are gonna be getting mad props from the gang, man.
Anyways, have you seen Betty lately?
Dude, don't even go there.
That girl started trippin' cuz I went to the movies with Veronica the other day.
I was like, look, you knew how I was before you got with me.
That's right.
You're such a playa, man.
Dude, there's Mad Max.
Let's go say hi.
Max, what's up?
Are you okay?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
I got an F in English class.
My life is over.
Dude, you're over it.
You need to lay off the books for a while and have some fun.
Come on, let's bounce.
Where are we going?
Oh crap.
My dad is gonna go postal when he finds out about this.
I'm gonna open the can of whoop-ass on you if you don't come with me right now.
Okay, okay.
Gee.