EnglishPod.com Morning.
Hi there Mr.
Anderson, how are you on this fine morning?
Fine, thank you.
It sure is cold this morning, isn't it?
I barely even got out of bed.
Yeah, it's pretty cold alright.
Did you catch the news this morning?
I heard that there was a fire in Byron Street.
No, I didn't hear about that.
Did you happen to watch the football game last night?
The Patriots scored in the last minute.
No, I don't like football.
Oh, by the way, I saw you with your daughter at the office Christmas party.
She's really beautiful.
She's my wife.
Oh, here's my floor.
Nice talking to you.
Goodbye.
Oh sir, this is the 56th floor.
We're on the 70th.
That's okay, I'll take the stairs.