The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Avoid the subject by talking about something else.
Beat around the bush.
Increase in salary.
Raise.
To think about something before making a decision.
Take into consideration.
Give with the choice of accepting or rejecting.
Offer.
The quality of being loyal.
Loyalty.
Let's try that faster.
The quality of being loyal.
Loyalty.
Avoid the subject by talking about something else.
Beat around the bush.
Increase in salary.
Raise.
To think about something before making a decision.
Take into consideration.
Give with the choice of accepting or rejecting.
Offer.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Beat around the bush.
Stop beating around the bush and tell me what you came here to say.
We can't keep beating around the bush like this because sooner or later they are going to find out.
Beat around the bush.
He tried to beat around the bush but his father knew better and forced the truth from him.
Raise.
He was so happy when he got the raise that he didn't stop smiling for a week.
My boss just gave me a raise.
Raise.
Do you think we can afford to give a raise to all of our employees?
Take into consideration.
Can you please take our family's needs and wants into consideration before you decide to spend the rest of our money gambling?
Be better used at their current position or in their new position.
Take into consideration.
We need to take into consideration how offering our employees a 15% raise will affect our finances.
Loyalty.
Many businesses rely on customer loyalty to survive, which means that they have to make sure they treat their customers well.
My loyalty is to my country.
Loyalty.
His loyalty to the company is unshakable, so we can count on his vote.
Offer.
I am willing to offer you a salary 10% higher than what they are offering you.
She offered her help to her sister, but her sister didn't take it.
Offer.
I would offer you something to eat, but I have nothing in my cupboards.