EnglishPod.com Excuse me, sir.
May I talk to you?
Bill!
Sure, come on in.
What can I do for you?
Well, sir, as you know, I have been an employee of this prestigious firm for over ten years.
Yes?
I won't beat around the bush.
Sir, I would like a raise.
I currently have three companies after me, and so I decided to talk to you first.
A raise?
Son, I would love to give you a raise, but this is just not the right time.
I understand your position, and I know that the current economic downturn has had a negative impact on sales.
But you must also take into consideration my hard work, proactiveness, and loyalty to this company for over a decade.
Taking into account these factors and considering I don't want to start a brain drain, I'm willing to offer you a 10% raise and an extra five days of vacation time.
How does that sound?
Great!
It's a deal.
Thank you, sir.
Before you go, just out of curiosity, what companies were after you?
Oh, the electric company, the gas company, and the water company.