The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To include something as a part.
Encompass Based on or relating to ideas or concepts.
Conceptual An understanding of something.
Grasp An invisible area in open space.
Black hole The branch of physics that deals with energy and matter on an atomic level.
Quantum machines Involving or based on a suggested idea or theory.
Hypothetical A science that deals with the action of heat.
Thermodynamics A magnetic field that is produced by a current of electricity.
Electromagnetism The area of physics which deals with nuclei.
Nuclear physics Involving or based on a suggested idea or theory.
Hypothetical An understanding of something.
Grasp Nuclear physics The branch of physics that deals with energy and matter on an atomic level.
Quantum machines A science that deals with the action of heat.
Thermodynamics To include something as a part.
Encompass A magnetic field that is produced by a current of electricity.
Electromagnetism Based on or relating to ideas or concepts.
Conceptual An invisible area in open space.
Black hole Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Even though he makes a good case for his theory, it has never been proven.
I barely understand basic math, so there's no way I could understand theoretical mathematics.
Sometimes theories of social interaction don't hold up when you apply them to the real world.
Encompass This manual encompasses everything that you will need to know when you go abroad.
Encompass Encompass I had so much to say during my presentation that I went 20 minutes over and still didn't encompass everything.
Encompass This book encompasses all the different ethnic groups of the world.
I don't understand the American concept of the bigger the better.
The new concept car will be on display at next month's car show.
Even after months of research, they still could not get a conceptual understanding of the subject matter.
Grasp Once you practice your new vocabulary a few times, you will begin to grasp it.
Grasp I had a good grasp on the topic, but I don't think I could teach it to anybody.
Grasp If you are going to work in China, it would greatly help if you had a solid grasp of the language.
The scientists designed an experiment in order to test their hypothesis.
Hypothetically speaking, would you rather be a bird or a fish?
The researcher gave us some hypothetical situations in order to see how we would react.
Thanks for watching!