The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Increase in size, quantity or worth.
Raise From one house to the next.
Door to door.
Short private road from a street to a house.
Driveway Agree to pay for an event or activity.
Sponsor The act of giving to a fund or cause.
Donation Seek to obtain by persuasion, entity or formal.
Solicit A person or an action which collects money for particular purposes.
Fundraiser Seek to obtain by persuasion, entity or formal.
Fundraiser The act of giving to a fund or cause.
Donation Increase in size, quantity or worth.
Raise Short private road from a street to a house.
Driveway Agree to pay for an event or activity.
Sponsor From one house to the next.
Door to door Raise After four months of doing odd jobs for my neighbors, I finally raised enough money to buy a bicycle.
They were raising money for the people who had lost their homes in the earthquake.
Raise At the end of the fundraiser, the hospital had raised enough money to buy the new machine.
Sponsor He sponsored several kids in the fundraiser.
Air Canada sponsored the Vancouver Olympics.
Every month, I give money to the child I sponsor in Asia.
Driveway Eighty percent of the profits will go to the people in need, while the other twenty percent will be spent on administrative costs.
Driveway Two-thirds Z of the profits will go towards the new drum set for the band.
Driveway She was quite surprised when she learned that only a small percentage of the profits would actually be helping kids go to summer camps.
He gave a huge donation to the organization.
Donation I made a donation to my sister's drama fundraiser.
Donation We received so many donations that we raised twice the amount we had set as our goal.
Solicit I solicited around my neighborhood last week to raise money for our school band trip.
Solicit The organization encouraged its members to go door-to-door soliciting for their cause.
Solicit Many buildings don't allow soliciting.