EnglishPod.com Hi Isabel, you wanted to see me?
Yes, Anthony.
Come on in and have a seat.
Is everything okay?
You seem a bit preoccupied.
Well, Anthony, this is not going to be an easy conversation.
The company has made some decisions which will have a direct impact on your employment.
Okay.
I don't want to beat around the bush, so I'm just going to come out with it.
We're going to have to let you go.
What?
Why?
I mean, just like that, I'm fired?
I'm sorry, but to be honest, you're a terrible employee.
What?
I resent that.
Anthony, you were caught making international calls from the office phone.
You called in sick eight times this month, and you smell like alcohol.