The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Worried, thinking about something else.
Preoccupied.
Connected to, related to.
Direct.
Strong influence or effect.
Impact.
Avoid saying something by talking about other things.
Beat around the bush.
Say something directly.
Come out with it.
Have someone fired or dismissed.
Let someone go.
Use to say something directly.
To be honest.
Find something very insulting.
Resent.
Call the office to say that you can't come to work because you're sick.
Call in sick.
Money or benefits you give someone when they are fired.
Severance package.
End an employment because of business reasons, not performance.
Lay off.
The action of ending employment because of business reasons.
Lay offs.
A letter written to tell an employee he is fired.
Dismiss the letter.
End the employment of a person.
Fire.
Terminate.
Let's try that faster.
Strong influence or effect.
Impact.
End the employment of a person.
Fire.
Terminate.
Have someone fired or dismissed.
Let someone go.
End an employment because of business reasons, not performance.
Lay off.
The action of ending employment because of business reasons.
Lay offs.
Avoid saying something by talking about other things.
Beat around the bush.
Use to say something directly.
To be honest.
Call the office to say that you can't come to work because you're sick.
Call in sick.
Find something very insulting.
Resent.
Say something directly.
Come out with it.
Worried.
Thinking about something else.
Preoccupied.
A letter written to tell an employee he is fired.
Dismiss the letter.
Money or benefits you give someone when they are fired.
Severance package.
Connected to.
Related to.
Direct.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Preoccupied.
James is really preoccupied.
I think he's having some family problems.
Preoccupied.
Oh, were you talking to me honey?
I'm sorry, I'm just really preoccupied with work.
Preoccupied.
John was so preoccupied with his deadline that he forgot to attend his cousin's wedding ceremony.
Impact.
Our overtime costs are having a direct impact on our profits.
The news scandal is having a direct impact on the President's approval ratings.
Impact.
This decision is going to have a direct impact on our success.
Beat around the bush.
You really shouldn't have chosen John as your debate contest partner.
You know, he's always beating around the bush.
Beat around the bush.
Please don't beat around the bush.
If you want to break up, just say so.
Beat around the bush.
Stop beating around the bush and tell me what you have to say.
Come out with it.
What are you trying to say?
Just come out with it.
Come out with it.
When will they come out with it?
We know their boyfriend and girlfriend.
Come out with it.
Don't keep secrets from me.
Just come out with it.
Let someone go.
Due to the economic crisis, we will be letting some employees go.
I can't believe it.
After 12 years of working here, they let me go.
Let someone go.
If you continue to make this mistake, we're going to have to let you go.