EnglishPod.com Welcome to Galenet.
How can I help you?
Hi.
I would like to get an internet plan for my house.
Of course.
We have three different plans with different prices you can choose from.
The first one is the cheapest, but most basic plan, which is $30 a month.
This is for broadband internet with a download speed of 512 kbps.
I have no idea what kbps means.
I just want to be able to get online, play games, and chat with my friends.
Oh, and watch movies online as well.
Well, this connection might be a bit too slow for your needs.
I suggest you get the premium package for $50 a month, which includes a connection speed of 2 megabytes.
That way, you can play games online without any lag.
This package also includes a wireless router and a personal firewall, absolutely free.
Do I have to pay an installation fee?
Lucky for you, this month we aren't charging our normal installation fee.
You are saving yourself $100 right there.
And we'll throw in this pen drive.
Awesome!