The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
A fast internet connection.
Broadband internet.
A device that allows data to be transferred between individual computers and networks.
Modem Act of transferring data between computers.
Download Form of broadband internet service delivered over telephone network, relatively slow.
Digital subscriber line Form of broadband internet service delivered over cable television network, relatively fast.
Cable internet Over the internet Online An individual's necessary requirements.
Someone's needs Software which detects harmful viruses on a computer.
Antivirus software A delay Lag Not using wires to send and receive data.
Wireless Device used to protect a computer against intruders.
Firewall Process of making ready for use.
Installation To offer for free.
Throw in Let's try that faster!
Form of broadband internet service delivered over telephone network, relatively slow.
Digital subscriber line A device that allows data to be transferred between individual computers and networks.
Modem A delay Lag Not using wires to send and receive data.
Wireless Over the internet Online Process of making ready for use.
Installation Device used to protect a computer against intruders.
Firewall Form of broadband internet service delivered over cable television network, relatively fast.
Cable internet Software which detects harmful viruses on a computer.
Antivirus software Act of transferring data between computers.
Download To offer for free.
Throw in A fast internet connection.
Broadband internet An individual's necessary requirements.
Someone's needs Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Download Now that I have broadband internet, I can download music and videos for free.
Download This website has a lot of free software that you can download.
Download That's a big file you are trying to download.
It might take up to 3 hours to complete.
Someone's needs This software is designed to meet all your needs.
Someone's needs You don't take into consideration my needs when making these decisions.
Someone's needs To understand the needs of your children, you should talk to them regularly.
Wireless Our office is installing a new wireless network so that we can use our laptops and smartphones.
Wireless I love the fact that the PS3 has a wireless controller.
It's much more convenient.
Wireless My new sound system comes with a pair of wireless speakers.
Now I can play music anywhere in the house.
Firewall We have a firewall at the office which prevents us from accessing sites such as Facebook and MySpace.
Firewall It's important to have a good firewall set up to prevent unauthorized access to your network.
Firewall I always turn off my firewall because it prevents me from opening certain websites.
Throw in If you buy two pizzas, we will throw in another one for free.
Throw in Tell you what, I'll buy this computer if you throw in a pair of headphones.
Deal?
Throw in The salesman threw in a subscription to the local newspaper for buying his product.
Isn't that great?