The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Beer served from a barrel, not in a bottle or can.
On tap.
Buy one and take one free.
Two for one.
A period of time at a bar when drinks are sold cheaper than usual.
Happy hour.
A sale, a special price.
Special.
A measuring unit which is equal to 0.473 liters.
Pint.
A small dish served before a meal.
Appetizer.
A dish with tortilla chips and melted cheese cooked together.
Nachos.
Fried Italian cheese.
Null.
Dollar, informal.
Buck.
Alcoholic drink made from one or more liqueur and other ingredients.
Cocktail.
A relaxed casual bar where beer is served.
Pub.
A menu or list of drinks served in a restaurant or bar.
Drinks list.
Strong alcohol drink such as gin, rum, vodka, etc.
Liquor.
A chair with no back used for sitting on at a bar.
Barstool.
Let's try that faster.
Beer served from a barrel, not in a bottle or can.
On tap.
Strong alcohol drink such as gin, rum, vodka, etc.
Liquor.
A dish with tortilla chips and melted cheese cooked together.
Nachos.
Alcoholic drink made from one or more liqueur and other ingredients.
Cocktail.
A menu or list of drinks served in a restaurant or bar.
Drinks list.
A measuring unit which is equal to 0.473 liters.
Pint.
Fried Italian cheese.
Null.
Dollar, informal.
Buck.
A small dish served before a meal.
Appetizer.
A sale.
A special price.
Special.
Buy one and take one free.
Two for one.
A period of time at a bar when drinks are sold cheaper than usual.
Happy hour.
A chair with no back used for sitting on at a bar.
Barstool.
A relaxed casual bar where beer is served.
Pub.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
On tap.
We have four types of beer on tap.
What's on tap?
On tap.
We don't have any beer on tap.
Special.
Do you have a happy hour special?
I'll have the lunch special.
Special.
Can we have the two for one special?
If you can't drink coffee, what about a cup of tea?
My computer can't connect to the internet.
What about yours?
I'm quite busy in the afternoon.
What about tomorrow?
Appetizer.
Would you like to start with some appetizers?
What appetizers do you have?
Appetizer.
There aren't that many appetizers on the menu.
Two for one.
All shirts are now two for one.
We're having a two for one sale.
Two for one.
Appetizer.
The store is having a two for one sale.