The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
That subject is too personal, impolite.
Mind your own business.
Phrase you use when you don't want to answer a question.
That's personal.
Arrive.
Come in from Too much information.
TMI.
Too interested in others' private matters.
Nosey.
About a person's private thoughts, feelings, etc.
Personal.
Because of that.
In that case, To look for private information about someone.
Snoop.
A polite phrase to use where you are saying something sensitive.
If you don't mind me saying so.
Do not misunderstand me.
Don't get me wrong.
Where would you like to go?
Where to?
In foreign countries.
Overseas.
To live in a place your whole life.
To be born and raised.
The United States.
The good old U.S.
of A.
Let's try that faster.
Because of that.
In that case, Where would you like to go?
Where to?
Arrive.
Come in from In foreign countries.
Overseas.
The United States.
The good old U.S.
of A.
About a person's private thoughts, feelings, etc.
Personal.
Do not misunderstand me.
Don't get me wrong.
To live in a place your whole life.
To be born and raised.
Too interested in others' private matters.
Nosey.
To look for private information about someone.
Snoop.
Too much information.
TMI.
A polite phrase to use where you are saying something sensitive.
If you don't mind me saying so.
That subject is too personal.
Impolite.
Mind your own business.
Phrase you use when you don't want to answer a question.
That's personal.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Come in from Where are you coming in from so late at night?
Come in from Flight number 441 just came in about an hour ago.
Come in from I think I'll be coming into Chicago at about noon tomorrow.
If you don't mind me saying so.
I think the curry could be a little hotter next time.
The problem, if you don't mind me saying so, is pretty simple.
You need a new computer.
If you don't mind me saying so.
You look really good in that dress.
Phil is always asking so many personal questions.
Frankly, I think he is just too nosy.
Nosy People should just mind their own business and stop being so nosy.
Nosy I don't mean to be nosy, but did I hear you say you are from Canada?
Don't get me wrong.
It's not that I think you stole my computer.
It's just that you were the only one who can get into my room.
Don't get me wrong.
I do have a few problems with the plan, but don't get me wrong.
I still think it's a great idea.
Don't get me wrong.
I think Jon is a nice guy, but he is a bit disorganized.
In that case 30 people are coming to the party.
In that case, we'll need some more beers.
Charles is having an affair.
In that case, I think Mary needs to get a divorce.
In that case The car is that expensive?
In that case, I don't think I will be able to afford it.