EnglishPod.com Thank you for organizing this great baby shower for me.
I've always been to baby showers but never actually had one held for me.
Let's get started!
OK, let's start opening some presents!
Oh look!
What a great little bib for the baby!
This will definitely come in handy.
Oh wow, you also got me a stroller!
That's so great!
Thank you!
This next one is from Betty!
A hot chair and a car seat!
Wow, Betty, thank you so much!
I really appreciate it.
One more from Carla!
A playpen and crib?
Thanks Carla, this is just what I needed.
OK, that's all of them.
No more gifts!
Now, who wants to guess when the baby is due?
Umm, I think my water just broke.
Get me to a hospital!
Thanks for watching!