The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
To quickly get something to eat.
To grab a bite.
A cosmetic applied to thicken, lathen, and darken the eyelashes.
Mascara.
A cosmetic coloring material applied to the eyelid.
Eyeshadow.
Passing reasonable bounds, intolerable or shocking.
Outrageous.
In a basic way, fundamentally or essentially.
Basically.
Let's try that faster.
A cosmetic coloring material applied to the eyelid.
Eyeshadow.
In a basic way, fundamentally or essentially.
Basically.
To quickly get something to eat.
To grab a bite.
A cosmetic applied to thicken, lathen, and darken the eyelashes.
Mascara.
Passing reasonable bounds, intolerable or shocking.
Outrageous.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
To grab a bite.
As soon as I got home from work, I grabbed the bite to eat, then went out again to pick up my kids.
Let's grab a quick bite at this rest stop.
And then we're back on the road for another few hours.
To grab a bite.
I really need to grab a bite to eat soon, or else I'll pass out.
Eyeshadow.
I love wearing eyeshadow in bold colors, but I have to be careful not to look like a clown.
She applied a light eyeshadow to her lid, and a darker eyeshadow to her crease.
Eyeshadow.
Which shade of eyeshadow should I wear tonight?
Mascara.
Many women say that the one makeup item they could not live without is mascara.
First, curl your lashes with an eyelash curler, and then apply some mascara to your eyelashes.
Mascara.
Be sure to wear waterproof mascara on the day of your wedding.
Outrageous.
The prices in this store are outrageous.
I find it outrageous that he would even suggest I was involved in the scandal.
Outrageous.
Her demands were so outrageous that I laughed in her face.
Basically.
Basically, she's saying that we shouldn't buy from this company because they mistreat their workers.
This is basically a copy of the other computer program we were using, just easier to operate.
Basically.
These restaurants all serve basically the same type of food.