EnglishPod.com Good morning Angela, how have you been lately?
Morning Michael, I've been very busy lately.
One of our other vendors is going out of business and I've been searching for a suitable replacement.
Well, rest assured that you can count on us to be here for the long run.
Please sit down.
Coffee?
No thanks.
I've been trying to cut down on the caffeine.
I could never do that.
I'd be a zombie if I didn't have my morning coffee fix.
Let's get down to business then.
Yes, I've come to talk with you about ordering the 8 megapixel cameras for our new Mi Phone.
The demand for phone cameras is growing and Pear has been falling behind in the market.
That's great.
I'm glad to hear that Pear has finally jumped on the bandwagon.
Right now our contract is for the 5 megapixel cameras.
Is Pear still interested in having those?
No, we're changing all the cameras to 8 megapixels.
We were hoping that by making your company our sole supplier for cameras, we could negotiate a better deal.
Surely.
Let's get started by drafting a new contract.