The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
Food remaining uneaten at the end of a meal.
Leftovers.
A large American bird similar to the chicken.
Turkey.
Of different kinds combined.
Mix.
To cut into small cubes.
Dice.
Small organisms.
Bacteria.
A micro-organism.
Germ.
To make hot or warm again.
Reheat.
To make or keep cold.
Refrigerate.
Becoming sick because of bacteria in food.
Food poisoning.
Let's try that faster.
A micro-organism.
Germ.
Small organisms.
Bacteria.
Becoming sick because of bacteria in food.
Food poisoning.
To cut into small cubes.
Dice.
To make or keep cold.
Refrigerate.
To make hot or warm again.
Reheat.
Food remaining uneaten at the end of a meal.
Leftovers.
A large American bird similar to the chicken.
Turkey.
Of different kinds combined.
Mix.
Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
Reheat.
Could you please reheat this?
It's a little cold.
Reheat.
I reheated this pizza for you.
I hate to reheat things.
It always makes the food taste really bad.
Food poisoning.
Could you please use gloves?
I don't want to get food poisoning.
Food poisoning.
My wife always gets food poisoning when she eats seafood.
You should never mix cooked and uncooked food.
Otherwise you will get food poisoning.
Leftovers.
There are plenty of leftovers from last night's dinner.
Please help yourself.
Leftovers.
I don't want to eat any leftovers.
I need some quality food.
Leftovers.
You can come up with some very creative meals thanks to leftovers.
Germ.
Always wash your hands to wash away germs.
Don't touch that.
It has so many germs.
Germ.
I hate taking the subway.
There are germs everywhere.
Mix.
I've prepared a bowl of mixed nuts for the party.
My father has mixed ancestry.
He is half Japanese and half Ecuadorian.
Mix.
I think having mixed classes will be good for the school.