What's for dinner?
Leftovers.
What?
Leftovers of what and from when?
From last night.
I took the leftover turkey, mixed it with some diced peppers and onions, add a little bit of mayonnaise and made some sandwiches.
Isn't that dangerous though?
I mean bacteria and germs reproducing on food that was left out or reheated?
Well I didn't leave the turkey at room temperature for more than an hour and I refrigerated soon after we finished eating.
Also when reheating I put it in the oven for 15 minutes at 100 degrees Celsius.
Well okay.
I'm just afraid of getting food poisoning.
Don't worry about it.
Making a new meal out of leftovers is almost an art.
Not only do you save money but you also get to be creative and have something different to eat.