The EnglishPod Audio Review Listen to the meaning, then say the vocabulary word.
to take or have something temporarily borrow dollar bucks to give something to someone temporarily lend pay back repay confident expectation of something hope trust security pledged for the payment of a loan collateral Let's try that faster.
pay back repay to take or have something temporarily borrow confident expectation of something hope trust to give something to someone temporarily lend dollar bucks security pledged for the payment of a loan collateral Now say the word and hear it in a sentence.
borrow Can I borrow your bike?
I forgot I borrowed your jacket last week.
borrow I'm sorry, you can't borrow my DVD player.
lend If I lend you my bike, will you give it back tomorrow?
lend My dad lent me his car.
lend Did I lend you my snowboard?
repay repay I have to repay this debt before the end of the month.
repay repay I am still waiting for you to repay me for these damages.
repay I can't repay the bank because I lost my job.
trust You need to trust people a little bit more.
trust If you want my trust, you have to earn it.
trust My dad always told me to trust no one and doubt everything.
collateral In order for me to get a loan, I have to sign over my house as collateral.
If you have no collateral, it's hard to get a loan.
collateral My dad offered his car as collateral in order to get this loan.